<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://rskelton.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://rskelton.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-07-21T11:30:04-04:00</updated><id>https://rskelton.com/</id><title type="html">Robert Skelton</title><subtitle>Finance | Tech | Cars | Renovations | Etc</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Suzuki Cappuccino - Interpreting the Japanese License Plate</title><link href="https://rskelton.com/Interpreting-Cappuccino-License-Plate/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Suzuki Cappuccino - Interpreting the Japanese License Plate" /><published>2020-07-21T08:15:14-04:00</published><updated>2020-07-21T08:15:14-04:00</updated><id>https://rskelton.com/Interpreting-Cappuccino-License-Plate</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rskelton.com/Interpreting-Cappuccino-License-Plate/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/plate.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Plate&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My 1991 Suzuki Cappuccino came with the Japanese license plate from when it was registered in Japan, so I wanted to &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vehicle_registration_plates_of_Japan&quot;&gt;find out what it meant&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the picture of my plate above. The plate is yellow with black text, which means it is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kei_car&quot;&gt;kei car&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The top line is 3 Japanese characters and a number. In my case, the 3 Japanese characters are &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nagano_(city)&quot;&gt;Nagano, Nagano&lt;/a&gt;, which is the office this plate was issued.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;09 is the next number, which is a class code. This is supposed to tell why a vehicle is used, like private transport, taxi, commercial, etc, but since my number is 2 digits, that is not how it is currently setup (3 digits), and I couldn’t find anything on what class code 09 meant. If you know, send it to me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next line has a hiragana text, which is found out translates to &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Se_(kana)&quot;&gt;“se”&lt;/a&gt;. I have no idea what this means.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the last bit is 4 numbers, which is just numbers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Plate&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I basically found out my car was a kei car (which I already knew) and was from Nagano. Neat.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Suzuki Cappuccino - Exterior LEDs</title><link href="https://rskelton.com/Suzuki-Cappuccino-Exterior-LEDs/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Suzuki Cappuccino - Exterior LEDs" /><published>2020-07-13T08:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2020-07-13T08:00:14-04:00</updated><id>https://rskelton.com/Suzuki-Cappuccino-Exterior-LEDs</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rskelton.com/Suzuki-Cappuccino-Exterior-LEDs/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For any car I own, I like to replace old bulbs with something a little brighter. The Cappuccino had 1 bad high beam, and the 2 small marker lights were just unplugged within the headlight housing. Here are the bulbs I replaced:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;parts-required&quot;&gt;Parts Required&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/300sizs&quot;&gt;H1 High Beams x2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/3frnutn&quot;&gt;H3 Low Beams x2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2C8xj0R&quot;&gt;194 Marker lights x2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/3gYvOkz&quot;&gt;BA15S Reverse light x1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;high-beams-and-marker-lights&quot;&gt;High Beams and Marker Lights&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To replace the high beams and marker lights, you actually have to take the headlight housing completely off, but it isn’t too hard. You do have to lift the front end of the car in order to rotate the wheels freely, so jack up the front end to where the wheels are off the ground.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, there are 2 10mm nuts to remove inside the engine bay, per headlight. One on top, and one behind the housing, close to the center of the engine bay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once those are off, go under each wheel and find 2 more 10mm nuts, located below and above the low beam bulb. These are pretty difficult to reach. If you have a fender liner, you’ll have to remove that in order to remove these nuts. Once those 2 nuts are off, rotate the front wheels to the opposite direction and remove the 2 nuts on the other side. You can see both of them in the following picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now the headlight housings will come out. The marker lights plug in at the bottom. The previous owner had installed LEDs, but in the wrong direction, and also left the harness unplugged. I dropped in some new &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2C8xj0R&quot;&gt;194 LEDs&lt;/a&gt; and plugged them in. These turn on with 1 click on the lighting stalk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the high beams, remove the old bulbs and water seal around them. You will not get to reuse the dust collector if you’re switching to LEDs, so remove that. Seat your &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/300sizs&quot;&gt;H1 LED bulb&lt;/a&gt; in the headlight housing then clamp it in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To plug the black and red wires for the LED to the harness, you actually need to reverse them. Yep, red to black, black to red. Makes sense, right? Test the high beams, then wrap them well in electrical tape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;low-beams&quot;&gt;Low Beams&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/3frnutn&quot;&gt;H3 Low beams&lt;/a&gt; is a similar process as the high beam, but you can reach them from within the wheel well without removing the headlight housing. So if you’re just replacing low beams, no need to jack up the car. The dust collector also won’t fit, but I didn’t remove mine. The polarity on these were correct, so red to red and black to black. Can’t explain that. Connect them, clamp them in good with some pliers or vice grips, and electrical tape it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/22.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/23.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/24.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/25.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/26.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/27.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you’ve replaced the low beams, then you can re-install the nuts and lower the car. Easy enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;results&quot;&gt;Results!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marker lights only
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
Marker lights and halogen low beams
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
Marker lights, halogen low beams, LED high beams
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/16.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
Marker lights, LED low beams
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/28.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
Marker lights, LED low beams, LED high beams
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;reverse-lights&quot;&gt;Reverse Lights&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reverse lights were a bit more tricky. There are 2 10mm nuts located behind the reverse lamp housing. Both of them broke off on me when removing it. I put in a new &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/3gYvOkz&quot;&gt;BA15S LED&lt;/a&gt; I just happened to have around. The reflector on the inside of the reverse housing was very rusted, so I cleaned it up before resealing. To attach back to the car, I drilled two holes in the back of the housing and zip tied it around the strong metal mesh. 50 miles and no movement, so it’ll do until I find a better reverse housing solution!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/17.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/18.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/19.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/20.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap_light/21.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Drive Cool Cars on a Budget</title><link href="https://rskelton.com/drive-cool-cars-on-a-budget/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Drive Cool Cars on a Budget" /><published>2020-07-12T09:05:14-04:00</published><updated>2020-07-12T09:05:14-04:00</updated><id>https://rskelton.com/drive-cool-cars-on-a-budget</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rskelton.com/drive-cool-cars-on-a-budget/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Oil&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of life’s biggest expenses is transportation, especially cars. I love cars, and love driving different cars. I get bored driving the same vehicle for more than a few years.. or months. You could imagine this would be expensive, but it doesn’t have to be. I’ve owned quite a few cars, and I’ve not lost much money on them at all. The biggest downside is that you have to pay registration and taxes on every car you buy, but some of that can be tax deductible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The list that follows is all of the cars I’ve owned, how much I paid and sold them for, how many miles I put on them, and about how expensive it was to own each one. I’ve included insurance costs, city/highway MPG, and the cost of oil changes and registration so that you can see how affordable each was to own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first 3 cars I owned in high school, so my parents helped me out by paying for gas, insurance, and registration. Most of my cars have been RWD sports cars that were manual, but a few SUVs and other vehicles too. I’ve had great experiences with the American and Japanese cars I’ve owned, an OK experience with the Italian Fiat, and terrible experiences with both Germans, so I’ll likely never buy another German car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-1993-ford-mustang-lx&quot;&gt;1. 1993 Ford Mustang LX&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $1,700 / 195,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $1,750 / 205,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 25/30, regular gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 2.3L 4-cylinder, 100HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $30 for standard oil change, every 3,000 to 5,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/93mustang.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1993 Mustang&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This car was bought by my parents for me and my brother to learn to drive a manual transmission. I broke the clutch in it, and the A/C compressor went out in it, which cost about $600 to fix both. We owned it for a few years as an extra car, and sold it for more than we paid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-1996-ford-mustang&quot;&gt;2. 1996 Ford Mustang&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $3,600 / 118,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $2,400 / 135,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 23/28, regular gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 3.6L 6-cylinder, 150HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $30 for standard oil change, every 3,000 to 5,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/96mustang.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1996 Mustang&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was the first car I bought myself, the older, silver Mustang in the middle of the picture. I put a $70 Cold Air Intake on it. Other than that, I did no major work on the car, so it had no expenses outside of gas and oil changes. I originally sold the car for $3,200, but the buyer blew a head gasket on the way home. This really surprised me, since after I had 17,000 issue-free miles, they broke a major part in a 5 mile drive home. Since they were family friends, I took it back, and sold it as is a week later for $800 less.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-1999-chevrolet-camaro&quot;&gt;3. 1999 Chevrolet Camaro&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $4,000 / 99,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $3,600 / 115,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 22/27, regular gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 3.8L 6-cylinder, 200HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $30 for standard oil change, every 3,000 to 5,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/camaro.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1999 Camaro&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought the Camaro before heading to college as something more exciting – it had T-Tops! The picture doesn’t portray how enthralled I was. I drove this at the beginning of my college career and had no issues with it. Just a couple hundred dollars upgrading the headlights and front grill, hey, I was 18! When I sold it after a few years, I didn’t lose much money to upgrade to my next car, which was a…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;4-2004-cadillac-cts-v&quot;&gt;4. 2004 Cadillac CTS-V&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $17,800 / 49,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $13,000 / 99,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 16/23, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $120/mo for full coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 5.7L 8-cylinder, 400HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $100 for full synthetic oil change, every 10,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/ctsv.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2004 CTS-V&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought this with the money I had saved from summer jobs and my first semester of Co-oping as a Test Engineer. It came with new tires, I got one set of new tires for free a few years later from my brother (he won them), and I sold it needing new tires. The CTS-V was an amazing car: a luxury sport sedan with a Corvette Z06 engine and a 6-speed manual transmission. I loved it! However, the insurance was really high, and so were the gas costs. This was the longest I had ever owned a car, which was about 4 years. I sold it when I moved down to Florida for my first real Engineering job. I still find myself wanting a car like this again, and they are still selling used years later for the same prices. No more depreciation on these, unfortunately for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;5-2008-chevrolet-corvette&quot;&gt;5. 2008 Chevrolet Corvette&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $27,500 / 36,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $26,500 /49,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 23/30, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $90/mo for full coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 6.2L 8-cylinder, 430HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $100 for full synthetic oil change, every 10,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $3,000&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/c6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2008 Corvette&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought the Corvette after getting my first paycheck as a full time employee after college. A bright blue Corvette with a targa top in perfect Florida weather, why not? A few months later, I was wondering how bad of a financial decision it really was. My dad and brother gave me 0% loans since I couldn’t pay for all of it at once, and I was paying them about $1,000/month to pay it off quickly. It took about 6 months to pay off. Finally selling my CTS-V really helped. I owned the Corvette for a little over a year, and luckily sold it for not much of a loss in order to pay off the down payment on my house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buying a Corvette and a house in the same year might not be the best financial decision, but it worked out for me once I sold the Vette. This was the nicest and fastest car I had owned at this point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The expenses on this were really low, since insurance is super cheap and it got relatively good MPG for a sports car. Everyone wonders how the insurance low, so think about this: Who buys a Corvette, and what do they do with them? Most Corvette owners are 60+ and retired, and they use their Corvette as a weekend car or cruiser, not a daily driver. This means they are garaged the majority of the time, and there are not very many insurance claims on them. This drives the insurance price pretty low, which was great for me! Most people in Corvette Clubs like to brag how few miles they put on their Vette, I was the opposite. I put about 13,000 miles on mine in the year I owned it, and loved every single one of them. It made me want to get back into one once I was more financially stable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;6-1999-porsche-boxster&quot;&gt;6. 1999 Porsche Boxster&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $5,500 / 85,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $5,000  / 89,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 19/25, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $50/mo for legal minimum&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 2.5L 6-cylinder, 200HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $95 for full synthetic oil change, every 7,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $500&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/boxster.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1999 Boxster&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought the Porsche as a replacement to Corvette, which I sold to pay towards the down payment on my house. The difference in selling my Corvette and buying a Porsche was over $21,000! My co-workers wondered why I “upgraded” from a Corvette to a Porsche, and their jaw dropped when they find out I only paid $6,000 after tax and registration for it. The insurance for full coverage on it was about $130/mo, which I thought was insane on a car that’s so cheap. Therefore, I just went for the legal minimum. My thoughts were that if I wreck it, I can just buy another car. I’m also quite confident in my driving abilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I called it my cheap beater Porsche, and that’s not too far off. I converted the non-functional automatic convertible top to a manually-operated top, and I just leave it down all the time. The back window was plastic that has faded to yellow, so it had terrible visibility when the top is up. I spent $50 on new tail light bulbs and a new headlight switch, since those didn’t work when I bought it. Luckily for me, I picked this up for a steal on Craigslist, and bought it the same day it was posted. I loved driving a cheap car that I don’t care about anymore! I kept this about 9 months. I put about $350 into new brakes and rotors. I did them myself, since the dealer quoted $2,700 to do it. When I sold it on eBay, it needed a new water pump, which was about $700 installed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I lost about $1,000 to drive this for close to a year, not bad. I sold it to buy my first automatic car, and first non-sports car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;7-2005-bmw-x5-48&quot;&gt;7. 2005 BMW X5 4.8&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $7,000 / 102,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $7,005 in trade-in / 108,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 14/19, premium gas (ouch)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $67/mo for legal minimum&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 4.8L 8-cylinder, 360HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: Never had to do any&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $700&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/x5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2005 X5&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought this awesome BMW SUV. It was $72,000 new, and I bought it for 10% of that. It was large inside, had a panoramic sunroof, Bluetooth, and heated seats in the front and back. Perfect for Florida! It came with huge 20″ rims that are 315 in the back. I got lots of compliments on the wheels. The car was enjoyable to drive, the A/C was so cold, and it felt like it owned the road. It’s not a sports car, but it’ll scoot. 360HP in this SUV is no slouch. It’s got torque to tow as well. The gas mileage is horrific on this car, and it holds 25 gallons of premium.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never bought new tires on it or did oil changes since I didn’t own it for long, but it had a TON of problems. The inside driver door panel was off for at least half the time I owned it, and I replaced almost every part in there myself. The window barely worked. I ended up using a zip tie to solder a piece of plastic together inside the door. The BMW and Porsche I had might have been lemons, It needed a water pump and coolant flush before I tried selling it private party, then ended up trading it in on this…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;8-2016-chevrolet-corvette&quot;&gt;8. 2016 Chevrolet Corvette&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $40,000 / 44,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $31,000 / 50,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 23/32+, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $110/mo for excellent coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 6.2L 8-cylinder, 455HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $0, included with CPO&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: ~$2,500&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/vette.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Corvette&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Newest car and by far the most expensive car I’ve ever owned. Something about lifestyle creep… I got a 1.49% interest rate 48 month car loan on a USED car. Found this 1-owner, higher mileage C7 Corvette at a dealer. It was the exact combo I wanted, blue exterior and brown/tan interior, 2LT, manual transmission. It was Certified Pre-Owned, so it has free oil changes and services for a few years, plus it was a better price than any 2016 for sale in the country at the time. I haggled for a while, got up to leave a few times, and got about 3k off the dealer price and got more than I paid for my BMW on trade in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 2016 came with a front camera so you don’t hit the front bumper parking, and a flat bottom steering wheel. This is such a nice car, and I’m making some money on the side &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/rent-other-peoples-cars-with-turo/&quot;&gt;renting it with Turo&lt;/a&gt;. I was really tired of how expensive the BMW was and how unreliable it was, so I was happy to pay a premium to get into a reliable American car again. Plus it has cylinder deactivation to run on 4-cylinders when you want to, which helped me get 36 MPG on a road trip to Tampa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since my Vette was CPO, I never paid for oil changes on it. I owned it for almost 2 years before trading it in for a nicer car for my wife. I lost more on this car than any car I’ve ever had.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;9-2007-lexus-gx470&quot;&gt;9. 2007 Lexus GX470&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $10,000 / 145,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: Not yet, and not planning on selling&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 15/19, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $60/mo for excellent coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 4.7L 8-cylinder, 270HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $70-80&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $1,700&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/lexus.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;GX470&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We needed something larger than a Corvette or Fiat to move our dogs around and do more home improvement projects, so I wanted to get something reliable SUV that would last a very long time. I did my research and decided on a Toyota 4Runner, with leather and a V8. So the 4th generation (2003-2009) Toyota 4Runner V8 Limited. Unfortunately, those are rare, and relatively expensive. Then I found out that Lexus made the same car, with more factory options and it’s even nicer than the 4Runner, has a V8, leather, and it sells for less than a V8 Limited 4Runner. That sold me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was originally planning to buy a 2003 model in Pennsylvania for $5,000, but it had rust, was a little rough, and the owner was seeming like he was never going to deliver it. I was paying him to drive it down, but he flaked on me 3 separate times. I had searches set up on every website you can think of, and not many come up for sale. One ended up showing up in Melbourne, FL, where I live, for 10k. It was more than I was wanting to spend, but it was much lower miles, newer, and nicer than I was planning on buying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was this one that I bought. I was going to go look at it, so I scheduled and appointment with this local car dealer for the next day. They called me that day and said the car had already sold, pending financing. Oh well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They called me back another day later and said financing fell through, so I went down that day and bought it, putting almost $7k of the purchase on a Capital One Venture card to get a signing bonus! This car was nearly perfect, super low miles for the model, recent maintenance on the timing belt and water pump, new battery, tires, brakes - it needs nothing. I got this car for below market (the car would’ve sold the next day if I didn’t buy it), and I plan on driving it until it dies. This is a car that needs very little maintenance since it’s a Toyota, it’ll run 3,4,500k miles, and I’m already loving it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you check the &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/category/cars/&quot;&gt;cars category&lt;/a&gt; of my website, I detail many of the mods I’ve been doing on my GX, I really love this car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;10-2013-fiat-500&quot;&gt;10. 2013 Fiat 500&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $20,000 / 19 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $2,000 / ~80,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 28/33, Mid grade gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $80/mo for excellent coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 1.4L 4-cylinder, 135HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $80-100&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $400, car already had taxes paid in Alabama, just had to plate it in Florida&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/fiat.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fiat&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife’s parents bought her this car in college. It was a decent little car for a while, it went almost 70,000 miles with not many issues. The last 10k miles we owned it, it went through 4 window regulators and the car died on her at work one day, ended up being a bushing in the shifter that prevented the car from starting. We decided it was time to upgrade her, and we bought her a…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;11-2018-ford-mustang-convertible&quot;&gt;11. 2018 Ford Mustang Convertible&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $22,000 / 33,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: Not yet, not for a while!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 21/32, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $60/mo for excellent coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 2.3L 4-cylinder, 310HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $50-70&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $1,500&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/mustang.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mustang&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sweet convertible Mustang! It has white paint with a rare red interior, there were only 3 for sale in America with that combo when we bought this. This car is fast for a 4 cylinder, and is just as nice as my Corvette was. It’s the Premium Plus package, so it has lots of digital displays, heated and cooled seats, CarPlay and Android Auto and tons of other great features. This is a super comfortable car that is also fun to drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We bought this CPO from Sarasota Ford over in Sarasota, FL. We drove both the Fiat and Corvette over and traded them both in. It was really sad to see my C7 go, but at the same time, it was way too expensive of a car for me. I got a little upset not having a fun manual sports car though, so I bought myself a…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;12-2004-honda-s2000&quot;&gt;12. 2004 Honda S2000&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $10,000 / 85,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $12,000 / 85,800&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 18/25, premium gas. Great smiles per gallon!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $50/mo for excellent coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 2.4L 4-cylinder, 237HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: None&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $700&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/s2000/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;S2000&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A great deal on an AP2 S2000, with very low miles. So now we have the Lexus, Mustang, and my S2000. This car doesn’t get driven with the top up, only down. It’s a fun little sports car to drive around town in, but not comfortable at all. It has some aftermarket bumpers and side skirts, and a paint job, and I hate all of those things. It was sports car red from the factory, and the previous owner painted it maroon. Maybe eventually I’ll convert it back to stock and get the nice red paint back on it, but for now I just use this to run errands around town, as long as I don’t have to carry too much stuff. This drives just like my old Boxster, which is great, but it’s a Honda, so it is reliable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I owned it for about 7 months, put in about $200 of parts into it, and sold it for a 4 figure profit. Waited a whole business day before putting down a deposit on my next car -  1991 Suzuki Cappuccino!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;13-1991-suzuki-cappuccino&quot;&gt;13. 1991 Suzuki Cappuccino&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $5,000 / 122,000 km&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: Not yet&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: ~35/50, premium gas. Insane MPG! It has a whopping 5 gallon gas tank&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $45/mo for some coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: .6L 3-cylinder Turbo, 63HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $40 or so, &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/Suzuki-Cappuccino-Oil-Change/&quot;&gt;did the first one myself the day after buying it&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $350&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Oil&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a very unique car. Never sold in America, and can only be imported once 25 years old, this right hand drive JDM kei car gets tons of attention. It is slow, difficult to drive, but it’s a blast. The top speed is about 83mph. I’ve got it up to 120…kmh. Everything is in Kilometers, so you have to convert in your head to know how fast you are going. It doesn’t matter too much, since it might be the slowest car on the road, barely can get up to the speed limit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has a 3 piece targa/t-top, a fold down back window, and it’s SO SMALL. Very fun so far. This will probably need a decent amount of work since it is old, and parts are hard to come by in the US, since it wasn’t sold here. If you want parts, you basically have to find someone in the UK (where it was sold 27-29 years ago), or in Japan, and get them to ship them to you. There is a pretty active following of these in a few Facebook groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So those are the cars I’ve owned, and the details on how much they cost to buy and own. Do you have any good stories about cars and how they impacted your plans? Leave them in the comments!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Suzuki Cappuccino - Oil Change</title><link href="https://rskelton.com/Suzuki-Cappuccino-Oil-Change/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Suzuki Cappuccino - Oil Change" /><published>2020-07-11T10:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2020-07-11T10:00:14-04:00</updated><id>https://rskelton.com/Suzuki-Cappuccino-Oil-Change</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rskelton.com/Suzuki-Cappuccino-Oil-Change/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Oil&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/drive-cool-cars-on-a-budget/&quot;&gt;I bought a 1991 Suzuki Cappuccino&lt;/a&gt;! First thing to do was an oil change. This is following &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4M3r7QcHHKA&quot;&gt;Larry’s Youtube Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;parts-required&quot;&gt;Parts Required&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Filter - I used a Fram FS4386. You can also use a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2W5Qmje&quot;&gt;Fram FG4967&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/3292e7S&quot;&gt;Baldwin B33&lt;/a&gt;, or others.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil - about 3 quarts, I used &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/328lP8o&quot;&gt;Mobil 1 5W-30&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;17mm wrench&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/3276yEI&quot;&gt;Oil filter removal tool&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Drain pan&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Funnel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Gloves, you definitely want to wear these&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Paper towels or shop towels to clean up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Drive car on ramps or lift the front end.
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Oil&quot; /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Remove oil cap in the engine&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Remove oil filter, under the front of the car&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Remove drain plug, slightly further behind the oil filter, with a 17mm, rotating clockwise!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oh yeah, make sure you have a drain pan under the car. Let the oil drain for a while.
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Oil&quot; /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add in the drain plug with a little bit of old oil, twist (counter clockwise) until hand tight, then tighten just a bit with your 17mm.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lube the o-ring of the new oil filter with some of the old oil.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add in your oil filter, just hand tight is fine. The oil filter removal tool doesn’t work to tighten anyways.
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Oil&quot; /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add about 3 quarts of oil using your funnel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Replace oil cap in the engine bay&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Drive car off ramps, let sit at idle for about 5 minutes and watch for any leaks
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cap/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Oil&quot; /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If no leaks, check the oil level using the dipstick. If it is between full and low, you’re done. If low, add more oil. If too full, that stinks. Repeat steps 1-11.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Honda S2000 - 25mm Rear Spacers</title><link href="https://rskelton.com/S2000-25mm-Rear-Spacers/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Honda S2000 - 25mm Rear Spacers" /><published>2020-06-09T10:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2020-06-09T10:00:14-04:00</updated><id>https://rskelton.com/S2000-25mm-Rear-Spacers</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rskelton.com/S2000-25mm-Rear-Spacers/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/spacers/both.png&quot; alt=&quot;Spacers&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My 2004 Honda S2000 has a sort of wide body kit at the back, but stock rims, so the tires and rims sit too far within the wheel well. There is a product called spacers, which is just a piece of aluminum that sits between your wheel hub and your rim, poking them slightly further out. I bought some 25mm spacers for my S2000 and installed them. This makes them stick out 25mm more on each side, so 50mm wider on the back tires overall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before buying any spacers, I did a lot of research. There are lug centric spacers, and there are hub-centric spacers. Hub centric spacers have an additional lip that sits within your wheel, and they are much safer. H&amp;amp;R seems to have the best reputation within the S2000 community on spacers, so I bought &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/3hbEJjK&quot;&gt;these H&amp;amp;R 25mm Aluminum spacers&lt;/a&gt; for about $150.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/spacers/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Spacers&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To install, break the lug nuts on the back 2 tires. Jack up the rear of your S2000 and put it on some jack stands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/spacers/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Spacers&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take the back rims completely off. Find out you need new rear tires, like yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/spacers/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Spacers&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, the instructions to say to clean off any rust or grime off your hubs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used some light sandpaper, which didn’t do much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I sprayed some &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2YfqNMU&quot;&gt;PB Blaster&lt;/a&gt; on there, and that rust was gone! PB Blaster is awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/spacers/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Spacers&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Place your spacer over the hub, and tighten on the new spacer nuts in a star pattern.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/spacers/6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Spacers&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had to use a 3/4” socket instead of my 3/4” lug nut tool, since the area around the spacer nuts was pretty small.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tighten those in pretty good, put the rims back on, lower the car. Drive it for 50-100 miles, then take the wheels back off and re-tighten both spacers. They will loosen a little after your first time driving, so this is just to get them back into a permanent place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/spacers/8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Spacers&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/spacers/9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Spacers&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And done! The results are noticeable if you’re looking for them, wider in the back just like I wanted. The wheels look much more natural by not sitting so far within the wheel well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/spacers/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Spacers&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/spacers/before.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Spacers&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After and Before
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/spacers/both.png&quot; alt=&quot;Spacers&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/spacers/10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Spacers&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/spacers/11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Spacers&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/spacers/12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Spacers&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I gotta go get new tires.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Recipe - Keto Canned Tuna Poke Bowl</title><link href="https://rskelton.com/Keto-Canned-Tuna-Poke-Bowl/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Recipe - Keto Canned Tuna Poke Bowl" /><published>2020-05-16T09:01:14-04:00</published><updated>2020-05-16T09:01:14-04:00</updated><id>https://rskelton.com/Keto-Canned-Tuna-Poke-Bowl</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rskelton.com/Keto-Canned-Tuna-Poke-Bowl/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/recipes/poke.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ingredients&quot;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Canned tuna&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Soy sauce&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mayo&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sriracha&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cauliflower Rice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;optional-toppings&quot;&gt;Optional Toppings&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Crushed peanuts&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Green onion&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Matchstick carrots&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Avocado&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sesame seeds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;instructions&quot;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Combine tuna, mayo, Sriracha, soy sauce, and pepper to taste. Should taste like tuna from your local Japanese place!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cook Cauliflower rice and put it in a Bowl&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Top with tuna mixture, and any optional toppings you like&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Recipe - Keto Canned Tuna Ceviche</title><link href="https://rskelton.com/Keto-Canned-Tuna-Ceviche/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Recipe - Keto Canned Tuna Ceviche" /><published>2020-05-16T09:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2020-05-16T09:00:14-04:00</updated><id>https://rskelton.com/Keto-Canned-Tuna-Ceviche</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rskelton.com/Keto-Canned-Tuna-Ceviche/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/recipes/ceviche.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ingredients&quot;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3-4 cans of tuna&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 tomato&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;some cilantro&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 onion, or red onion&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;lime juice&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tabasco, to taste&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Avocado&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;instructions&quot;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Combine all Ingredients&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Salt and pepper to taste&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Top with avocado&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 - Paint New Rims!</title><link href="https://rskelton.com/GX470-Paint-New-Rims/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 - Paint New Rims!" /><published>2020-05-12T10:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2020-05-12T10:00:14-04:00</updated><id>https://rskelton.com/GX470-Paint-New-Rims</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rskelton.com/GX470-Paint-New-Rims/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/20.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been searching for a set of new rims and tires for my GX470 for a while, and finally bought a set of SR5 4Runner take off rims with decent tires for $350. My area isn’t a popular area for Toyotas, so not many rims for Toyotas come up for sale. I was searching for one of the following sets:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;SR5 4Runner takeoffs&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;4Runner Trail Teams&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;TRD Pros&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sequoia takeoffs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically anything that would fit my GX470, that wasn’t the rims it came with. Finally bought this set, and decided to paint them bronze. It’s popular now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, my prep was:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pressure wash rims and center caps&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Remove Lexus logos from center caps&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/35Tl0jr&quot;&gt;320 grit sandpaper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/3csHIBp&quot;&gt;400 grit sandpaper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wash the rims thoroughly&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Clean the tires with tire shine, so if you get any paint on them it will come off easy&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Line the outside of the rims with 3”x5” notecards&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A couple coats of &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/35ZfXhx&quot;&gt;Rust-Oleum Filler Primer&lt;/a&gt; with sanding after each coat. I used 4 cans on my 4 rims and center caps&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2H7U2dj&quot;&gt;Plasti-Dip&lt;/a&gt; the Lexus logos, did maybe 6 coats and used less than half a can.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3 coats of &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2WTdaCi&quot;&gt;Dupli-Color Bronze Wheel Paint&lt;/a&gt;, I used all 6 cans of this.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Super glue Lexus logos back to center caps&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A few coats of &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2YWROXi&quot;&gt;Dupli-Color Wheel Clearcoat&lt;/a&gt;. I used matte because it is all my local auto store had.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mount!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;here-are-the-progress-pictures&quot;&gt;Here are the progress pictures!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bought these rims, $350 with tires
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pressure washed
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cards around rim/tires
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Primer (bottom left rim only)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;
Primer - all 4
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;
Center caps painted with bronze
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;
Lexus logo on center cap
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;
First coat of bronze
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;
Center caps glued back on
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;
More coats of bronze
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;
Spray bronze on the inside so there are no unpainted spots
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;
Last coat of bronze
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;
Clear coat, really lightens the color up
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/16.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;
Before rims
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/17.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;
Half and half
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/18.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Done!
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/19.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rims/20.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rims&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Garage Storage Solutions</title><link href="https://rskelton.com/Garage-Storage-Solutions/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Garage Storage Solutions" /><published>2020-05-03T13:12:14-04:00</published><updated>2020-05-03T13:12:14-04:00</updated><id>https://rskelton.com/Garage-Storage-Solutions</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rskelton.com/Garage-Storage-Solutions/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/garage/11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Garage&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently reorganized and cleaned out my garage so our cars have more space. Here are some of the things I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;new-cabinets&quot;&gt;New cabinets&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, old cabinets from the kitchen remodel. I painted them grey with spray paint, hung them up in a corner, and reused a small plastic organizer shelf for some additional storage. I actually hung these myself, using an old cabinet door as a bottom level and holder. Clamped the two cabinets together to screw them together, hung the doors using the old copper hardware, I think it looks good. I’ll add some copper handles eventually. This let me move a lot of things off my shelves in the corner, which I was able to reuse by moving a lot of stuff off the floor. Goal is to maximize floor space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/garage/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Garage&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/garage/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Garage&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/garage/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Garage&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/garage/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Garage&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/garage/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Garage&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/garage/11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Garage&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;created-some-long-stuff-storage-hanging-in-the-air&quot;&gt;Created some long stuff storage hanging in the air&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made some hangers for wood/baseboards/trim/pipe/etc. Just used a long 2x4, cut into 6” sections and screwed into studs above the door and window. Gets some of that long stuff off the ground. Then I got rid of a ton of drywall and concrete backer board I don’t need.  Before and after!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/garage/6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Garage&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/garage/9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Garage&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;created-pvc-organizers-for-yard-tools&quot;&gt;Created PVC organizers for yard tools&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was made from some PVC I was going to throw away. Cut the ends at 45 degrees so I could run a screw through to the stud. Put yard stuff in them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/garage/7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Garage&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, this took a few days of painting, cleaning, and abusing my Shop Vac. I need a new Ship Vac filter so bad now, but my garage is clean. Also I hung some posters and decorations up that were just sitting on the ground. More floor space!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/garage/8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Garage&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/garage/10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Garage&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Architecture of Money</title><link href="https://rskelton.com/Architecture-of-Money/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Architecture of Money" /><published>2020-04-24T11:20:14-04:00</published><updated>2020-04-24T11:20:14-04:00</updated><id>https://rskelton.com/Architecture-of-Money</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rskelton.com/Architecture-of-Money/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/ccu/arch.png&quot; alt=&quot;Architecture&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like to talk about money, credit cards, banks, investing, etc. I realized that I knew where my money went, and it might be a little complicated, so I wanted to diagram it like a Cloud Architecture diagram. Here it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve got 2 paychecks coming in, one for my job, and one for my wife. Most of that money goes to &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/high-interest-checking-account/&quot;&gt;CCU&lt;/a&gt;, while some goes to Ally for our Emergency Fund, and some goes to Bethpage, where we have our HELOC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of our paychecks go towards investments before it hits the bank, like our 401K’s and HSA at Fidelity. Some goes to investments after it hits the bank, like our Roth IRAs and Brokerage, which are all at Vanguard. I also have accounts open at &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/robinhood/&quot;&gt;Robinhood&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://fundrise.com/r/pdog4&quot;&gt;Fundrise&lt;/a&gt; that I don’t actively contribute to, just collect and reinvest dividends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of our auto-pays go out from CCU, including our mortgage, monthly credit card bills, and any utility bills that don’t let us pay by credit card. Our Bethpage account exists just for us to pay off our HELOC, which is also at Bethpage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s basically it. Money flows in and around, pays for stuff and gets invested. A little more complicated, but we’re seeing results!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>