<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-11-27T12:10:04-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Robert Skelton</title><subtitle>Finance | Tech | Cars | Renovations | Etc</subtitle><entry><title type="html">How to Drive Cool Cars on a Budget [Updated November 2019]</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/drive-cool-cars-on-a-budget-2019/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Drive Cool Cars on a Budget [Updated November 2019]" /><published>2019-11-27T08:05:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-11-27T08:05:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/drive-cool-cars-on-a-budget-2019</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/drive-cool-cars-on-a-budget-2019/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/all.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Both&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of life’s biggest expenses is transportation, especially cars. I love cars, and love getting different cars. I get bored driving the same vehicle for more than a few years. You could imagine this would be expensive, but it doesn’t have to be. I’m 27 and have owned 12 cars, and I’ve not lost much money on them at all. The biggest downside is that you have to pay registration and taxes on every car you buy, but some of that can be tax deductible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The list that follows is all of the cars I’ve owned, how much I paid and sold them for, how many miles I put on them, and about how expensive it was to own each one. I’ve included insurance costs, city/highway MPG, and the cost of oil changes and registration so that you can see how affordable each was to own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first 3 cars I owned in high school, so my parents helped me out by paying for gas, insurance, and registration. Also, 8 of these cars were Rear Wheel Drive, manual transmission cars, and I have owned two silver on black V8 automatic AWD SUVs. 6 of them were American made and had no issues, and 2 were German made and had so many issues. The two Japanese cars have been great so far, and the Italian Fiat we had was great for a long time, then got expensive to maintain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-1993-ford-mustang-lx&quot;&gt;1. 1993 Ford Mustang LX&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $1,700 / 195,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $1,750 / 205,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 25/30, regular gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 2.3L 4-cylinder, 100HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $30 for standard oil change, every 3,000 to 5,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/93mustang.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1993 Mustang&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This car was bought by my parents for me and my brother to learn to drive a manual transmission. I broke the clutch in it, and the A/C compressor went out in it, which cost about $600 to fix both. We owned it for a few years as an extra car, and sold it for more than we paid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-1996-ford-mustang&quot;&gt;2. 1996 Ford Mustang&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $3,600 / 118,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $2,400 / 135,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 23/28, regular gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 3.6L 6-cylinder, 150HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $30 for standard oil change, every 3,000 to 5,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/96mustang.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1996 Mustang&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was the first car I bought myself, the older, silver Mustang in the middle of the picture. I put a $70 Cold Air Intake on it. Other than that, I did no major work on the car, so it had no expenses outside of gas and oil changes. I originally sold the car for $3,200, but the buyer blew a head gasket on the way home. This really surprised me, since after I had 17,000 issue-free miles, they broke a major part in a 5 mile drive home. Since they were family friends, I took it back, and sold it as is a week later for $800 less.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-1999-chevrolet-camaro&quot;&gt;3. 1999 Chevrolet Camaro&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $4,000 / 99,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $3,600 / 115,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 22/27, regular gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 3.8L 6-cylinder, 200HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $30 for standard oil change, every 3,000 to 5,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/camaro.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1999 Camaro&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought the Camaro before heading to college as something more exciting – it had T-Tops! The picture doesn’t portray how enthralled I was. I drove this at the beginning of my college career and had no issues with it. Just a couple hundred dollars upgrading the headlights and front grill, hey, I was 18! When I sold it after a few years, I didn’t lose much money to upgrade to my next car, which was a…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;4-2004-cadillac-cts-v&quot;&gt;4. 2004 Cadillac CTS-V&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $17,800 / 49,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $13,000 / 99,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 16/23, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $120/mo for full coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 5.7L 8-cylinder, 400HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $100 for full synthetic oil change, every 10,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/ctsv.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2004 CTS-V&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought this with the money I had saved from summer jobs and my first semester of Co-oping as a Test Engineer. It came with new tires, I got one set of new tires for free a few years later from my brother (he won them), and I sold it needing new tires. The CTS-V was an amazing car: a luxury sport sedan with a Corvette Z06 engine and a 6-speed manual transmission. I loved it! However, the insurance was really high, and so were the gas costs. This was the longest I had ever owned a car, which was about 4 years. I sold it when I moved down to Florida for my first real Engineering job. I still find myself wanting a car like this again, and they are still selling used years later for the same prices. No more depreciation on these, unfortunately for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;5-2008-chevrolet-corvette&quot;&gt;5. 2008 Chevrolet Corvette&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $27,500 / 36,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $26,500 /49,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 23/30, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $90/mo for full coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 6.2L 8-cylinder, 430HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $100 for full synthetic oil change, every 10,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $3,000&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/c6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2008 Corvette&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought the Corvette after getting my first paycheck as a full time employee after college. A bright blue Corvette with a targa top in perfect Florida weather, why not? A few months later, I was wondering how bad of a financial decision it really was. My dad and brother gave me 0% loans since I couldn’t pay for all of it at once, and I was paying them about $1,000/month to pay it off quickly. It took about 6 months to pay off. Finally selling my CTS-V really helped. I owned the Corvette for a little over a year, and luckily sold it for not much of a loss in order to pay off the down payment on my house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buying a Corvette and a house in the same year might not be the best financial decision, but it worked out for me once I sold the Vette. This was the nicest and fastest car I had owned at this point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The expenses on this were really low, since insurance is super cheap and it got relatively good MPG for a sports car. Everyone wonders how the insurance low, so think about this: Who buys a Corvette, and what do they do with them? Most Corvette owners are 60+ and retired, and they use their Corvette as a weekend car or cruiser, not a daily driver. This means they are garaged the majority of the time, and there are not very many insurance claims on them. This drives the insurance price pretty low, which was great for me! Most people in Corvette Clubs like to brag how few miles they put on their Vette, I was the opposite. I put about 13,000 miles on mine in the year I owned it, and loved every single one of them. It made me want to get back into one once I was more financially stable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;6-1999-porsche-boxster&quot;&gt;6. 1999 Porsche Boxster&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $5,500 / 85,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $5,000  / 89,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 19/25, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $50/mo for legal minimum&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 2.5L 6-cylinder, 200HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $95 for full synthetic oil change, every 7,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $500&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/boxster.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1999 Boxster&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought the Porsche as a replacement to Corvette, which I sold to pay towards the down payment on my house. The difference in selling my Corvette and buying a Porsche was over $21,000! My co-workers wondered why I “upgraded” from a Corvette to a Porsche, and their jaw dropped when they find out I only paid $6,000 after tax and registration for it. The insurance for full coverage on it was about $130/mo, which I thought was insane on a car that’s so cheap. Therefore, I just went for the legal minimum. My thoughts were that if I wreck it, I can just buy another car. I’m also quite confident in my driving abilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I called it my cheap beater Porsche, and that’s not too far off. I converted the non-functional automatic convertible top to a manually-operated top, and I just leave it down all the time. The back window was plastic that has faded to yellow, so it had terrible visibility when the top is up. I spent $50 on new tail light bulbs and a new headlight switch, since those didn’t work when I bought it. Luckily for me, I picked this up for a steal on Craigslist, and bought it the same day it was posted. I loved driving a cheap car that I don’t care about anymore! I kept this about 9 months. I put about $350 into new brakes and rotors. I did them myself, since the dealer quoted $2,700 to do it. When I sold it on eBay, it needed a new water pump, which was about $700 installed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I lost about $1,000 to drive this for close to a year, not bad. I sold it to buy my first automatic car, and first non-sports car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;7-2005-bmw-x5-48&quot;&gt;7. 2005 BMW X5 4.8&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $7,000 / 102,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $7,005 in trade-in / 108,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 14/19, premium gas (ouch)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $67/mo for legal minimum&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 4.8L 8-cylinder, 360HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: Never had to do any&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $700&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/x5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2005 X5&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought this awesome BMW SUV. It was $72,000 new, and I bought it for 10% of that. It was large inside, had a panoramic sunroof, Bluetooth, and heated seats in the front and back. Perfect for Florida! It came with huge 20″ rims that are 315 in the back. I got lots of compliments on the wheels. The car was enjoyable to drive, the A/C was so cold, and it felt like it owned the road. It’s not a sports car, but it’ll scoot. 360HP in this SUV is no slouch. It’s got torque to tow as well. The gas mileage is horrific on this car, and it holds 25 gallons of premium.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never bought new tires on it or did oil changes since I didn’t own it for long, but it had a TON of problems. The inside driver door panel was off for at least half the time I owned it, and I replaced almost every part in there myself. The window barely worked. I ended up using a zip tie to solder a piece of plastic together inside the door. The BMW and Porsche I had might have been lemons, It needed a water pump and coolant flush before I tried selling it private party, then ended up trading it in on this…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;8-2016-chevrolet-corvette&quot;&gt;8. 2016 Chevrolet Corvette&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $40,000 / 44,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $31,000 / 50,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 23/32+, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $110/mo for excellent coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 6.2L 8-cylinder, 455HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $0, included with CPO&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: ~$2,500&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/vette.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Corvette&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Newest car and by far the most expensive car I’ve ever owned. Something about lifestyle creep… I got a 1.49% interest rate 48 month car loan on a USED car. Found this 1-owner, higher mileage C7 Corvette at a dealer. It was the exact combo I wanted, blue exterior and brown/tan interior, 2LT, manual transmission. It was Certified Pre-Owned, so it has free oil changes and services for a few years, plus it was a better price than any 2016 for sale in the country at the time. I haggled for a while, got up to leave a few times, and got about 3k off the dealer price and got more than I paid for my BMW on trade in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 2016 came with a front camera so you don’t hit the front bumper parking, and a flat bottom steering wheel. This is such a nice car, and I’m making some money on the side &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/rent-other-peoples-cars-with-turo/&quot;&gt;renting it with Turo&lt;/a&gt;. I was really tired of how expensive the BMW was and how unreliable it was, so I was happy to pay a premium to get into a reliable American car again. Plus it has cylinder deactivation to run on 4-cylinders when you want to, which helped me get 36 MPG on a road trip to Tampa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since my Vette was CPO, I never paid for oil changes on it. I owned it for almost 2 years before trading it in for a nicer car for my wife. I lost more on this car than any car I’ve ever had.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;9-2007-lexus-gx470&quot;&gt;9. 2007 Lexus GX470&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $10,000 / 145,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: Not yet, and not planning on selling&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 15/19, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $60/mo for excellent coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 4.7L 8-cylinder, 270HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $70-80&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $1,700&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/lexus.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;GX470&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We needed something larger than a Corvette or Fiat to move our dogs around and do more home improvement projects, so I wanted to get something reliable SUV that would last a very long time. I did my research and decided on a Toyota 4Runner, with leather and a V8. So the 4th generation (2003-2009) Toyota 4Runner V8 Limited. Unfortunately, those are rare, and relatively expensive. Then I found out that Lexus made the same car, with more factory options and it’s even nicer than the 4Runner, has a V8, leather, and it sells for less than a V8 Limited 4Runner. That sold me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was originally planning to buy a 2003 model in Pennsylvania for $5,000, but it had rust, was a little rough, and the owner was seeming like he was never going to deliver it. I was paying him to drive it down, but he flaked on me 3 separate times. I had searches set up on every website you can think of, and not many come up for sale. One ended up showing up in Melbourne, FL, where I live, for 10k. It was more than I was wanting to spend, but it was much lower miles, newer, and nicer than I was planning on buying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was this one that I bought. I was going to go look at it, so I scheduled and appointment with this local car dealer for the next day. They called me that day and said the car had already sold, pending financing. Oh well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They called me back another day later and said financing fell through, so I went down that day and bought it, putting almost $7k of the purchase on a Capital One Venture card to get a signing bonus! This car was nearly perfect, super low miles for the model, recent maintenance on the timing belt and water pump, new battery, tires, brakes - it needs nothing. I got this car for below market (the car would’ve sold the next day if I didn’t buy it), and I plan on driving it until it dies. This is a car that needs very little maintenance since it’s a Toyota, it’ll run 3,4,500k miles, and I’m already loving it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you check the &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/category/cars/&quot;&gt;cars category&lt;/a&gt; of my website, I detail many of the mods I’ve been doing on my GX, I really love this car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;9-2013-fiat-500&quot;&gt;9. 2013 Fiat 500&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $20,000 / 19 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $2,000 / ~80,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 28/33, Mid grade gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $80/mo for excellent coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 1.4L 4-cylinder, 135HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $80-100&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $400, car already had taxes paid in Alabama, just had to plate it in Florida&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/fiat.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fiat&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife’s parents bought her this car in college. It was a decent little car for a while, it went almost 70,000 miles with not many issues. The last 10k miles we owned it, it went through 4 window regulators and the car died on her at work one day, ended up being a bushing in the shifter that prevented the car from starting. We decided it was time to upgrade her, and we bought her a…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;9-2018-ford-mustang-convertible&quot;&gt;9. 2018 Ford Mustang Convertible&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $22,000 / 33,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: Not yet, not for a while!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 21/32, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $60/mo for excellent coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 2.3L 4-cylinder, 310HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $50-70&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $1,500&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/mustang.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mustang&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sweet convertible Mustang! It has white paint with a rare red interior, there were only 3 for sale in America with that combo when we bought this. This car is fast for a 4 cylinder, and is just as nice as my Corvette was. It’s the Premium Plus package, so it has lots of digital displays, heated and cooled seats, CarPlay and Android Auto and tons of other great features. This is a super comfortable car that is also fun to drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We bought this CPO from Sarasota Ford over in Sarasota, FL. We drove both the Fiat and Corvette over and traded them both in. It was really sad to see my C7 go, but at the same time, it was way too expensive of a car for me. I got a little upset not having a fun manual sports car though, so I bought myself a…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;9-2004-honda-s2000&quot;&gt;9. 2004 Honda S2000&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $10,000 / 85,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: Not yet&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 18/25, premium gas. Great smiles per gallon!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $50/mo for excellent coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 2.4L 4-cylinder, 237HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: None yet, but I’ll do them myself&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $700&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A great deal on an AP2 S2000, with very low miles. So now we have the Lexus, Mustang, and my S2000. This car doesn’t get driven with the top up, only down. It’s a fun little sports car to drive around town in, but not comfortable at all. It has some aftermarket bumpers and side skirts, and a paint job, and I had all of those things. It was sports car red from the factory, and the previous owner painted it maroon. Maybe eventually I’ll convert it back to stock and get the nice red paint back on it, but for now I just use this to run errands around town, as long as I don’t have to carry too much stuff. This drives just like my old Boxster, which is great, but it’s a Honda, so it is reliable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/s2000/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;S2000&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So those are the cars I’ve owned, and the details on how much they cost to buy and own. Do you have any good stories about cars and how they effected your financial plans? Leave them in the comments!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Honda S2000 LED Swap</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/S2000-LED-Swap/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Honda S2000 LED Swap" /><published>2019-11-12T10:20:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-11-12T10:20:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/S2000-LED-Swap</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/S2000-LED-Swap/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/s2000/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;S2000 LEDs&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently bought my 12th car, a 2004 Honda S2000, so I’ll be doing a few little convenience mods here and there. My first mod is always LEDs, which make the car brighter and more visible, and make it look like a more modern car. Here are the parts I used:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2UQpLoh&quot;&gt;Map Lights: 30mm festoon, thin x2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2S6HvcZ&quot;&gt;Trunk Light: 194 x1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2S6HvcZ&quot;&gt;License Plate Light: 194 x1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2S6HvcZ&quot;&gt;Accent Light on Front Headlights: 194 x2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2qmq3sF&quot;&gt;High Beams: H1 x2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/37n7l4t&quot;&gt;Reverse Light: T20 7440 x2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/s2000/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;S2000 LEDs&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah, the S2000 doesn’t have that many lights compared to my GX. Anyways, they’re all pretty simple to do. The map lights, you pry off only the clear cover, and there are two notches where it indicates where to put in a screwdriver. The trunk requires no tools to remove. The license plate light is one Phillips screw to change. The front marker lights, which might be an AP2 model only thing, not sure, you CAN change those without removing anything, just turn the tire one way and do the lights you can reach, then go turn the tires the other way to do the other side. Reverse bulbs can be changed from inside of the trunk liner. Easy enough!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/s2000/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;S2000 LEDs&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Running Board Removal</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Remove-Running-Boards/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Running Board Removal" /><published>2019-11-12T10:20:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-11-12T10:20:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Remove-Running-Boards</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Remove-Running-Boards/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/steps/17.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Running Boards&quot; /&gt;
After&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/steps/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Running Boards&quot; /&gt;
Before&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I removed the stock running boards on my Lexus GX470, now my SUV doesn’t look as much like a soccer mom vehicle!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the drivers step, I completely removed the whole step, then re-attached the trim that makes the vehicle look finished. If you don’t re-install that trim, you will have some exposed holes on the exterior, and it doesn’t look as good, plus I’ve read that it can let water in your cabin. For the passenger running board, I knew how the step worked, so I actually cut the step off in place! Trimming the bottom part of the step off and not removing it from the car was definitely the best way to go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are basically 3 mounts holding each step on the vehicle, each is held on with 3x 12mm bolts. You can see these mounts in the pictures below, hanging off the frame. Remove those, and reinsert them once the steps are removed so that the hole in the frame doesn’t get gunked up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/steps/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Running Boards&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are also a few 10mm bolts in each the step that attach to those mounts, those were removed too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also had to remove the wiring harness that lights up the courtesy lights, but I kept it to wire in &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2O9Luoo&quot;&gt;these rock lights later&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here, the best strategy is to cut at the very far ends of each step, shown in the next two pictures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/steps/6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Running Boards&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/steps/7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Running Boards&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The final product should look like this. I used tin snips, which worked pretty well. Once the ends are snipped, the whole step should come off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/steps/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Running Boards&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/steps/8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Running Boards&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I then had to cut the front and the back up a little bit, or else it looks weird, as shown in the next two pictures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/steps/10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Running Boards&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/steps/11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Running Boards&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then do the same on the other side!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/steps/12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Running Boards&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/steps/13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Running Boards&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/steps/14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Running Boards&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I reused the existing wiring harness and ordered some &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2O9Luoo&quot;&gt;waterproof rock lights&lt;/a&gt; to install. These mounted directly into the plastic after drilling a few holes. I had to cut the original connector, wire in like for like and crimp then using any electrical connector, then electrical tape them like crazy. I hid the wires up behind the plastic, and cut some more holes to zip tie the wiring harness every few inches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/steps/15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Running Boards&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/steps/16.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Running Boards&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2O9Luoo&quot;&gt;rock lights&lt;/a&gt; are super bright, and have the same functionality as the original courtesy lights, which is to light up when you unlock the vehicle. I love the look of no steps, and only removed them after a multi-month study. I made sure my wife, who is short, could get in and out of the vehicle without the steps. I noticed over a 2 month period that she did not ever use the steps, so they got to go!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">After</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Rear Door Table</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Rear-Door-Table/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Rear Door Table" /><published>2019-11-12T08:20:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-11-12T08:20:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Rear-Door-Table</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Rear-Door-Table/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/19.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I installed a drop down rear table in my GX, it took about 4 hours and $10 of new parts, plus some some scrap and parts I already had. If you bought all new parts and wood, this would cost about $50. The cheapest table you can buy for the GX is the &lt;a href=&quot;https://bluelineeo.com/products/drop-down-table-by-front-runner-1?_pos=1&amp;amp;_sid=d76aacddc&amp;amp;_ss=r&amp;amp;fbclid=IwAR2kTxwcdwTvTWkEN5io6CTTvupPVo2UFykXIjM-KEtGsIX1v0UTjxycjwM&quot;&gt;Front Runner table&lt;/a&gt;, which runs about $130.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, I cut a piece of (nice) scrap plywood down to 40” by 15”. I stained this with a natural stain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I used a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2QmriTh&quot;&gt;30” piano hinge&lt;/a&gt; which I already had to attach it to the bottom of the rear door, using the included screws. This &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2QmriTh&quot;&gt;piano hinge&lt;/a&gt; lets the table swing up and down while still being attached to the door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, I bought a gate latch from Home Depot to secure the table in the up position. I secured this to the top of the door and the other piece to the table itself, making sure it could latch before I screwed anything together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great, now I have a table that can stay in the closed position, but won’t stay level. I fixed that using some old rope, the same rope I used to make the rear door handle. I cut two holes in the outside corners of the table, and kept drilling into the plastic of the door itself. Here, I had to remove the rear door, for like the 10th time since owning the GX, and route the rope behind the plastic rear door cover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I pushed the rope inside, put a very large washer back there, then tied the rope and covered it in electrical tape. While I was back there, I super glued the back of the piano hinge screws and the gate hardware screws as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the rope is secure behind the door, I put the door plastic back on, then routed the other side of the rope through the holes I cut in the wood earlier. I put another large washer on the bottom of the table, then tied the rope into a knot. Now you’ve got a finished, functional table.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I showed it to some friends (Kelley is frosted flakes), and they asked why didn’t I stain it. I used a natural stain, but it was pretty light, so I pulled the wood back off and re-stained using a MUCH darker stain. Looks way better! While the wood was off, I rounded the corners where the rope runs through the holes, so that you don’t walk by it and hit yourself on a sharp corner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the stain was dry, I put the table back on the same way as before. The rear door pocket is still pretty functional! I can still store toilet paper, paper towels, and a few other things. The gate hardware has a spot for a lock, which I just put a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KBZxBr&quot;&gt;carabiner&lt;/a&gt; in, so that it doesn’t unlatch while driving. I also added some clear plastic bumpers onto the rear door plastic so that the wood doesn’t run against plastic while driving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/16.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/17.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/18.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I might cut the ends of the rope down a bit under the table, they’re a bit long, but I’m leaving them for now just in case. I’m excited to use this table on road trips with our dogs!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/20.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Tinting the Fog Lights</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Tint-Fogs/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Tinting the Fog Lights" /><published>2019-10-25T07:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-10-25T07:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Tint-Fogs</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Tint-Fogs/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fog/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fog Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I yellow tinted my fog lights on the GX, it was pretty simple. Here’s how to do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fog/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fog Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take your fog lights off the car. This is a 10mm bolt behind each light, which can be reached easily just by laying under the front bumper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fog/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fog Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take the fogs to your work station. Clean the housing really well. Get out your tint, I used &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/32QXscE&quot;&gt;this yellow tint from Amazon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spray some water from a spray bottle on the lights, then apply the film, sticky side touching the lights. Spray some more water on the outside of the film, then squeegee the water out, using the included tool or a credit card, or similar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finish getting all the water out, then use a hair dryer on VERY HOT to get the edges. Use scissors or a utility knife to cut the ends to look seamless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fog/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fog Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reinstall back on the GX!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fog/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fog Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Ditch Lights Install</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Ditch-Light-Install/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Ditch Lights Install" /><published>2019-10-21T07:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-10-21T07:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Ditch-Light-Install</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Ditch-Light-Install/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/26.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I installed ditch lights in my GX today, it took about 3 hours and $250.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;parts-bought&quot;&gt;Parts Bought&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ragofabrication.com/collections/gx470/products/2002-2009-1st-generation-lexus-gx470-ditch-light-brackets-1&quot;&gt;Rago Fabrication GX470 Ditch Mounts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/31vmj4C&quot;&gt;2x Baja Squadron Sport LED &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2VYJoeI&quot;&gt;1x Add a Circuit Tap&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the time of purchase, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ragofabrication.com/&quot;&gt;Rago Fabrication&lt;/a&gt; was having a sale. I bought the ditch brackets and Baja Squadron Sport pods with wiring harness for $235. You could do this install with any set of LED pods, but you’ll have to make your own wiring harness (with a fuse). The Rago mounts are great, so definitely use those.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alright, here’s how to do it. First, install the brackets from Rago. This was a required first for me, since my brackets got here five days before my lights and wiring harness. I followed &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1F9legl29M4&quot;&gt;this video&lt;/a&gt; to install the brackets, just take 1 bolt out at a time to make the hood not move.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, put the lights on the brackets, follow the instructions there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, take apart all the plastic in your engine, if you still have it. The plastic that is. I hope you still have the engine. I took off the engine cover in order to remove the very back plastic piece that was hiding some wiring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lay your wiring harness in place, you can even hook it up. You can take the red to the positive terminal and black to the negative terminal of your battery to test the harness and lights, just make sure the switch is one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now here comes what I thought was the hardest part - getting part of the wiring harness through the firewall. I decided to use the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2VYJoeI&quot;&gt;Add a Circuit Tap&lt;/a&gt;, so I don’t plug directly in to the battery (which is possible). The part of the harness that connects to the splitter that plugs both lights in, I fed that part through the firewall from the cabin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To do that, I cut a hole in the rubber nipple (where you see the white coat hanger in the pictures below) in the engine compartment on the firewall grommet thing. This is made for wiring expansions anyways. Then, under the drivers seat, push the wiring up through the hole that leads to the engine compartment. I found it MUCH easier to remove the plug (leaving just wiring and connections) and to tape those wires to a wire hanger that had already been pushed through the firewall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alright, got that done? Sweet. Bet it took a minute. Now you can make sure everything works. Plug in the lights to the harnesses, the black to a ground, and the red to power. I pulled back the plastic by the drivers left footwell to use a ground bolt there, you can see in the top left of the picture below. Then I used the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2VYJoeI&quot;&gt;Add a Circuit Tap&lt;/a&gt; to tap the 30A drivers power seat fuse, which is in the small fuse box under the steering wheel. The switch should turn on the lights, and when the lights are on the switch should light up red.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To hook up the included harness to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2VYJoeI&quot;&gt;Add a Circuit Tap&lt;/a&gt;, snip the end off the end of the red wire that was included, expose some of the copper using wire cutters, then push that wire into the end of the tap. Crimp the connection using some elbow grease and pliers. Pull the 30A from the drivers power seat slot and put it in the closer spot to the connector. Add another fuse in the next slot, this is the fuse for your ditch lights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/update.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For your switch in the cabin, I had to remove the wiring for it to sit snug in its newly drilled hole. To do this, unplug all the wires (remember where they are), then run the wires up from the back of the hole. Then plug those wires back into the switch, out of the plastic, then you can put the switch where the hole is. I made my hole a little bit too big, so you can use tape or velcro or caulk or basically anything to make it a little more snug.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What a terrible hole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/16.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/17.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/18.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/19.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, just make everything pretty. I ran the interior wiring behind the plastic footwell. In the engine compartment, I ran the wiring for each light under the plastic piece by the windshield, so very little of the wiring is exposed. This was a little difficult to do, but looks a lot better. I also used zip ties to keep the new electrical running next to the old electrical, and behind that plastic panel I mentioned earlier. Reassemble your engine plastic pieces, close up the interior pieces, you’ve got some bright lights!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/20.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/21.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/22.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/24.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason my install took so long was because I broke the connectors when I was putting the switch back together inside the hole, and had to crimp some new ends. Also I blew a fuse when testing. Then again, it’s electrical in a car. Have you ever done a electrical project in your car and NOT blown a fuse. Me either. The nice thing about the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2VYJoeI&quot;&gt;Add a Circuit Tap&lt;/a&gt; that I linked is that it comes with lots of extra fuses, so I just replaced it with a 5A fuse of the same size.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As far as the products, the Rago mounts fit perfect. You can have the hood opened or closed and the lights never touch your windshield. Some videos I saw complain about the wiring harness being too short, but it was long enough for my GX. The lights seem great so far, SUPER bright.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/23.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/25.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I were to make this nicer, what I would have done is buy a new plate that converts your existing switch panel to have one extra blank from &lt;a href=&quot;https://sbeprecision.com/product/gx470-mirror-switch-plate-with-blanks-plus-2-switch-openings/?fbclid=IwAR2135GD3VnZ60hwcgVjCgGwLRl3IdyQAwuM_xPr2Y2IB22XYZAg6pRJnuU&quot;&gt;SBE Precision Products&lt;/a&gt;, and a new &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ragofabrication.com/collections/led-wiring-and-accessories/products/toyota-factory-switch-square?variant=40556182663&quot;&gt;Toyota OEM looking ditch light switch&lt;/a&gt;. That would have added $70 to my install just for a nicer looking switch, so I didn’t. If you go that route, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6nWmIKTCtkY&quot;&gt;here is a good video&lt;/a&gt; on how to do the wiring - it is a little bit different but your switch is backlit, which is fancy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Blackout All Chrome</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Blackout-All-Chrome/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Blackout All Chrome" /><published>2019-10-16T10:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T10:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Blackout-All-Chrome</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Blackout-All-Chrome/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had already &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/Plasti-Dip-GX470-Grill/&quot;&gt;blacked out the front grill&lt;/a&gt; on my GX with &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2H7U2dj&quot;&gt;Plasti Dip&lt;/a&gt;, and it is holding up really well and looks great, so I figured I would replace the rest of the chrome throughout the vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, I replaced the front 4 windows weatherstripping trim with black trim. This was available on overseas models (Prado), and you can grab the parts on eBay. I wasn’t particularly thrilled with the non-OEM quality of the parts I got from eBay, so I won’t link them. To install them, just remove one Torx screw (I think it was T10) from the inside of your door panel, then remove the old part. The new weatherstripping trim slides in, then screw it in. I had to use a mallet to get it to sit right. Repeat for all 4 doors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The back 2 windows I did not change the weatherstripping trim, as it involves removing the rear windows, and I didn’t want to get into all that. I just Plasti Dipped it, along with the rear emblems. It took less than 1 can of &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2H7U2dj&quot;&gt;Plasti Dip&lt;/a&gt; to do the entire rear of the car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I taped a little of an outline, but it really didn’t help that much. At least it comes off easy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did 8 coats, with 30 minutes in between.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then removed tape and started cleaning with a damp cloth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do not recommend using an exacto knife like I did, I left a few small scratches in the paint. Use some plastic if.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The one time I wish the GX had a V6…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now the only chrome left on the car is the Lexus logo on the front grill and on the rims. And the tow hitch. And the lug nuts. Not blacking any of that out though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Change Heated Seat Bulbs</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Change-Heated-Seat-Bulbs/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Change Heated Seat Bulbs" /><published>2019-10-16T07:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T07:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Change-Heated-Seat-Bulbs</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Change-Heated-Seat-Bulbs/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/hs/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;HS&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the lights that provided a backlight to my heated seats on my GX470 was out, so I wanted to change it. I initially tried pulling the bulb out and replacing it with an LED of similar size, but the LED would not light up in any orientation, and the harness that holds the old bulb in was really difficult to deal with, so I just bought new bulbs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ended up ordered a pair of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.superbrightleds.com/moreinfo/instrument-cluster-gauge/neox-led-bulb-high-power-instrument-panel-led/221/&quot;&gt;NEO3-RHP: 3mm NEO3-xHP Red&lt;/a&gt; from SuperBrightLEDs for $1.79 each. I figured, heated seat, should be red, right?.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/hs/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;HS&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To install, pop the switch out of the dash with a small flathead screwdriver or plastic pry tool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/hs/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;HS&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remove the connector from the wiring. You can use pliers or a clamp to hold it out of the dash, or else it will fall back in and you’ll probably have to use pliers to fish that connector back out. Then remove the cover that says L or R.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/hs/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;HS&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The LED itself is the grey circle on the side of the switch. Use a screwdriver to rotate the old light to the left, the insert your new LED into the same spot, and rotate it right. Plug it back in and turn on the car to see if you have a light. If not, just remove the LED and rotate it to the opposite polarity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/hs/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;HS&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To reassemble, attach the L or R switch cover, plug back into the harness, then push back into your dash. Done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/hs/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;HS&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Radar Detector Hardwire</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Radar-Hardwire/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Radar Detector Hardwire" /><published>2019-10-07T07:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-10-07T07:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Radar-Hardwire</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Radar-Hardwire/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently put my Corvette on the market, so I took the hardwired radar detector out of it. Might as well put it in the GX!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2pSNAke&quot;&gt;RJ11 power cord&lt;/a&gt; that has a simple power and ground, with the goal to get power behind the mirror. It was ridiculously easy, the easiest of any car I’ve ever done. There are 2 wires behind the rearview mirror that are exposed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In spot 1 there is a blue/white cord, and in spot 2 there is a black/white cord.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Put your power from the radar cord (red) into spot 1 with the blue/white cord. Put the ground (black) into spot 2, the black/white cord. The prongs from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2pSNAke&quot;&gt;RJ11 power cord&lt;/a&gt; should fit snug.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I then wrapped a bit of black electrical tape around the power cord and the other wires running into the mirror, to keep everything from moving around too much. Plug in your radar detector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have power when the car is on, and the power drops when the car is turned off. Perfect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wrapped the cord once around my mirror, since it was a little long, then mounted it with the normal suction cup mounts, which aren’t great. If you’re doing any off road driving, you’ll want to take your detector down, or get a &lt;a href=&quot;https://blendmount.com/&quot;&gt;Blendmount&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2pSNAke&quot;&gt;Escort radar detector&lt;/a&gt;, these detectors have great sensitivity, but you can dial it back and customize them how you like them. I actually use an older model 8500 X50 that I bought for my first Corvette.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Custom Webbing Dog Divider</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Custom-Webbing-Dog-Divider/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Custom Webbing Dog Divider" /><published>2019-08-09T07:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-08-09T07:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Custom-Webbing-Dog-Divider</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Custom-Webbing-Dog-Divider/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/26.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a big dog, Bentley, a 75 pound lab mix, who loves being in the front of the GX when I’m driving. Only issue is, he’s a 75 pound dog. So I wanted a webbing divider to keep him in the 3rd row area, but the only one on the market that is made to fit the GX starts at $180! I used &lt;a href=&quot;https://raingler.com/collections/lexus-heavy-duty-cargo-netting/products/lexus-gx-j120-barrier-divider&quot;&gt;this product from Raingler&lt;/a&gt; as my inspiration, and started to plan how to make my own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Raingler divider uses stitching for the joints, and I can sew, but I don’t have a sewing machine. The type of stitches used to sew together an intersection of webbing really requires a sewing machine (or thousands of hour of free time which I don’t have), so I found some other projects that had used grommets to assemble webbing. I decided to go this route, and purchased the following parts on Amazon, which ran me about $60.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Parts Bought&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KpyTwR&quot;&gt;4x Frontmans Loops&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/31vmj4C&quot;&gt;4x D Rings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KBZxBr&quot;&gt;6x Carabiners&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2YUjQiP&quot;&gt;10-12 yards of Webbing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KpSf4S&quot;&gt;Grommet Kit with 100 grommets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tools Needed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hammer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Scissors&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lighter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Drill with a bit that can drill through metal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For mounting the divider, it needs to have something to attach to on the inside of the car. I noticed the Raingler product added some mount points into the body, inside of the panels, so I did that. I pulled back the panels on both sides of the car, right behind the second row seats, and found 2 spots I could drill in to on each side. This gives 2 mount points per side, plus a 3rd mount point per side on the bottom of the middle seats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I put 1 &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KpyTwR&quot;&gt;Frontmans Loop&lt;/a&gt; at each spot, with about a 10” strip of webbing, with a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/31vmj4C&quot;&gt;D ring&lt;/a&gt; on the other end. For making these connection pieces, I made them before putting them in the car. I cut a strip of webbing, then used the grommet punch to make holes. Make sure you burn off the loose strings on the ends of the webbing and the holes. Then, I used the grommet die to put a grommet in, with a Frontmans Loop on one side a D ring on the other. This was my first time using grommets, and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KpSf4S&quot;&gt;kit&lt;/a&gt; I bought was actually pretty easy to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did this for 2 spots on the drivers side and 2 spots on the passenger side, and fed the top connector piece above the panel, and the bottom connector piece between the 2 panels I had to pull off. The most difficult part of this whole project was drilling into the metal body panels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I decided I wanted the webbing to be able to flex with the middle seats being up or down. Turns out, the distance between the mount point on the seats being up or down and the mount point I added was only a 2” difference, so I used the longer measurement. Here’s my chicken scratch measurements, I cut and built my divider using the bottom diagram. 34” along the top mounting points I added, 46” in the middle mount points I added, and 30” for the 2 mount points built in on the middle seats. The vertical strip from the top to middle was 21”, and from middle to bottom was 14”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made the perimeter first, and made sure it fit on the mount points I had added and the back of the middle row seats. All fits! The hardest part was where 3 different strips intersected. I was worried the grommet would be too small to contain all 3 pieces of webbing, but it held great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/16.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/17.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/18.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I added another horizontal strip and started adding a few vertical strips, putting grommets at every intersection along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/19.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/20.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/21.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All done, then just install it! You can see the webbing flexes enough that the middle row can be up or down, however the middle row can not recline much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/21.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/22.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/24.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It took about 3 hours and $60 of parts to build a webbing barrier that is perfect for Bentley, and I have enough leftover parts, webbing, and carabiners that I could make a second one, or any other cool webbing things. I can also add many more vertical and horizontal strips. This was made to keep our lab in the back. We also have a 12 pound Cavalier, and she can fit through the nets, but that’s OK, she doesn’t get in my way when I drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any questions, feel free to comment, or ask me in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/LexusGXOR/?ref=group_header&quot;&gt;GXOR Facebook group&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/dogs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Update, 1 day later: I had to add 2 more vertical strips, since Bentley jumped through them once he saw we had Chick-fil-A in the front seat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/25.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/26.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>