<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-06-17T16:25:26-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Robert Skelton</title><subtitle>Finance | Tech | Cars | Renovations | Etc</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Plasti Dip GX470 Grill</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Plasti-Dip-GX470-Grill/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Plasti Dip GX470 Grill" /><published>2019-05-07T09:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-05-07T09:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Plasti-Dip-GX470-Grill</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Plasti-Dip-GX470-Grill/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/done.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Done&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I plastidipped the grill on my Lexus GX470, and I am very happy with the results. It took about 30 minutes of active work, and about 4 hours of waiting, and this was my first time using &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2H7U2dj&quot;&gt;Plasti Dip&lt;/a&gt;. I used 1 can of black &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2H7U2dj&quot;&gt;Plasti Dip&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the full Chrome grill, before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/before.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The labor is pretty simple - remove about 10 10mm bolts around the grill, up under the hood. I also had to remove 2 bolts on the hood release that were attached. Then just slip the grill off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/back.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also removed the Lexus logo, so that it stayed chrome instead of black. I think the contrast looks better. I’ve seen some other people &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2H7U2dj&quot;&gt;Plasti Dip&lt;/a&gt; the whole grill, and it doesn’t look as good to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/back2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Lexus logo removal involved 2 Phillips screws behind the logo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/remove_logo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make sure you clean your grill really well. You don’t want any bugs or dust on the grill before starting. I applied 8 coats of &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2H7U2dj&quot;&gt;Plasti Dip&lt;/a&gt; on, with 15-30 minutes of drying in between in each coat. It was just like using spray paint. This is after 2 coats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/coat1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this is 6 coats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/coat2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And re-installed the grill! Huge improvement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/done.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Done&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My Georgia Tech OMSCS Experience So Far</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/OMSCS-Experience-So-Far/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Georgia Tech OMSCS Experience So Far" /><published>2019-04-22T09:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-04-22T09:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/OMSCS-Experience-So-Far</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/OMSCS-Experience-So-Far/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/gt/gt.png&quot; alt=&quot;GT&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was accepted to, and enrolled in, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.omscs.gatech.edu/&quot;&gt;Georgia Tech’s OMSCS&lt;/a&gt; (Online Master of Science in Computer Science) in January 2016. This post is meant as a recap as the classes I’ve taken, and my experiences throughout this program. Every class is a 3 hour credit. You need 10 classes, or 30 hours, to earn this degree, which you have to complete within 6 years of admission. There is no thesis requirement, just pass all the classes and you’ve earned the degree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I transferred in 3 hours that I didn’t use from my undergrad at Auburn. I needed 5 engineering elective hours to graduate at Auburn, and I passed 12. I had too much free time then. One class, ELEC5150-Intro to Information Security at Auburn, transferred as credit for CS6035-Intro to Information Security at Georgia Tech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I only take 1 class at a time, since I also work full time and like to do things besides be in front of the computer. I’ve dropped a few classes, and got a D in 1 class, which doesn’t count towards your graduation credits, but, unfortunately, does count towards your GPA. Anyways, here’s the classes I’ve taken, grades I earned, if I recommend the course, and my thoughts on each.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;spring-2016---cs6300---software-development-process&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6300-software-development-process&quot;&gt;Spring 2016 - CS6300 - Software Development Process&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: B&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Would recommend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a great first class to take in OMSCS. It eases you into the concept of working at your own pace, working with groups of people that you never meet in person, and the basics of using Github in a small group. I got a B, but was really close to an A. I wish I had put a little more effort into this class. Dr. Orso is a interesting professor, and you learn a bit of Java and how to build a simple Android app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;summer-2016---cs6310---software-architecture-and-design&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6310-software-architecture-design&quot;&gt;Summer 2016 - CS6310 - Software Architecture and Design&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: B&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a software architecture course. I work in cloud architecture, more along the infrastructure lines, but I didn’t learn much in this class. The lectures are boring, the content is boring… it’s just a whole course on UML.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;fall-2016---cs6250---computer-networks&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6250-computer-networks&quot;&gt;Fall 2016 - CS6250 - Computer Networks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: Dropped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is considered to be one of the easiest classes in OMSCS, but it wasn’t for me. It’s all about writing networking algorithms in Python, and it just didn’t click for me. I dropped this one pretty early.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;spring-2017---cs6475---computational-photography&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cs6475.wordpress.com/&quot;&gt;Spring 2017 - CS6475 - Computational Photography&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: D&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Advice against&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This class with Dr. Irfan Issa has been my worst Georgia Tech class, and second worse classroom experience ever (no one will ever top Dr. Baginski’s Analog Electronics at Auburn). So this class I really struggled in, but I put in a ton of effort, and expected to make a mid C. A bad grade, but at least credit towards graduation. This class is heavy on Python and matrix algebra, both topics I am not strong in. So I go into the final project with a 75, and I just have to get about a 10 (out of 100) to keep my C. One annoying thing about Dr. Issa is that he gives you the assignment file as something like final_project.pdf, and wants the deliverable to have the exact same name (final_project.pdf). You can see how this can cause issues if you’re keeping your projects in the same directory, like a logical person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I uploaded my final project after completion and did an OK job, not A material, but definitely more than a 10 material. When grades came back a few weeks later, I saw that I had a D in the class. I asked the TAs and professor why, and it was because I uploaded the final_project.pdf that was the instructions, not my actual final report. When I selected the file to upload, I was in the wrong directory. I received a 0 on the final project, they would not accept my completed final_report.pdf, and therefore I failed this class. I brought this up to Georgia Tech as a Official Grade Dispute, and it was not re-graded. My D stood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, I would recommend not taking this class unless you have a very strong interest in Computational Photography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;summer-2017---cs6400---database-systems-concepts-and-designs&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6400-database-systems-concepts-and-design&quot;&gt;Summer 2017 - CS6400 - Database Systems, Concepts and Designs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: A&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Would recommend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is another really good class, and it was nice to take a interesting class after my awful previous semester. I had considered dropping the whole program after getting a D in my previous course. In this database course, I learned a bunch, and worked with a really great group on my projects in this course. Dr. Mark is funny and keeps lectures interesting. This class also helped me in my work, as I’ve been working more with databases now than ever before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;fall-2017---none&quot;&gt;Fall 2017 - None&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UgOu1zPtW2I&quot;&gt;Why do school when you can watch football?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;spring-2018---cs6460---educational-technology&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6460-educational-technology&quot;&gt;Spring 2018 - CS6460 - Educational Technology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: A&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This class is taught by Dr. David Joyner, who is highly liked in the OMSCS community. He is a interesting professor, but this wasn’t the most interesting topic for me. This class has a decent amount of busy work, like weekly status reports and required meetings, but it made for the easiest grade in OMSCS so far. I didn’t learn a whole lot in this course, but it is a decent course and good for padding your GPA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;summer-2018---cs7646---machine-learning-for-trading&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://quantsoftware.gatech.edu/Machine_Learning_for_Trading_Course&quot;&gt;Summer 2018 - CS7646 - Machine Learning for Trading&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dropped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I signed up for this thinking it was a really interesting sounding course. The content is interesting, but it gets tough, quick. The first project was easy, then it became super difficult. The course deals with stock trading, AI, and utilizes Python, numpy, pandas, and other Python libraries. I also had a lot of things going on in my personal life, so I couldn’t devote as much time as I needed to this course, so I dropped it. Dr. Balch’s lectures are interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;fall-2018---cs6440---intro-to-health-informatics&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6440-intro-health-informatics&quot;&gt;Fall 2018 - CS6440 - Intro to Health Informatics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: B&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This class was not fun or educational for me. The class is 100% run by a TA, there is no instructor involvement. The lectures are dry, and the content is not interesting for me. You spend most of the course learning about FHIR, a healthcare API, but every time we were had an assignment to do any development with it, the API was not functioning. Luckily, you don’t have to use FHIR for your final project, and I think 0% of my class ended up using it. We were allowed to pick any healthcare related project that was given to us, and it ended up being a simple team project. I came away with a B, but was close to an A. I would not take this class again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;spring-2019---cs7646---machine-learning-for-trading&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://quantsoftware.gatech.edu/Machine_Learning_for_Trading_Course&quot;&gt;Spring 2019 - CS7646 - Machine Learning for Trading&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dropped… again&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got a promotion at work and my work load started going up, I got engaged, ended up doing more home remodeling, more car stuff, and less school. Same as the first time I took this course, the second project was overly difficult. I won’t try to take this one a 3rd time, but the content does still interest me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;summer-2019---none&quot;&gt;Summer 2019 - None&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Honeymoon for a week in Costa Rica, no way I’m doing school then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;fall-2019---cs6238---secure-computing-systems&quot;&gt;Fall 2019 - CS6238 - Secure Computing Systems&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the first time this class has been taught, so it’ll either be super easy or the worst class ever. I’ll let you know in December.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So as of April 2019, I have 18 credits out of 30. I need to pass 4 more classes by Spring 2022 in order to graduate.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">GX470 Android Headunit and Backup Camera Install</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Android-Headunit-Backup-Camera-Install/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="GX470 Android Headunit and Backup Camera Install" /><published>2019-03-07T08:00:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-03-07T08:00:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Android-Headunit-Backup-Camera-Install</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Android-Headunit-Backup-Camera-Install/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/backup.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I installed a new Android headunit in my 2007 Lexus GX470, complete with a reverse activated backup camera. The install took about 5 hours over the course of a few days, and here is how I did it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;parts-needed&quot;&gt;Parts Needed:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aliexpress.com/item/9-inch-car-radio-for-Toyota-Prado-120-2004-2009-Quadcore-Android-6-0-car/32801839608.html?spm=2114.search0104.3.24.5edff7d9xxAsrB&amp;amp;ws_ab_test=searchweb0_0,searchweb201602_1_10065_10068_10130_10890_10547_319_10546_317_10548_10545_10696_453_10084_454_10083_433_10618_10307_537_536_10902_10059_10884_10887_321_322_10103,searchweb201603_6,ppcSwitch_0&amp;amp;algo_expid=c0b5c1d2-1f43-48c9-8027-ff2257719e95-3&amp;amp;algo_pvid=c0b5c1d2-1f43-48c9-8027-ff2257719e95&amp;amp;transAbTest=ae803_5&quot;&gt;9 inch Android Headunit with Canbus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2XJWMnt&quot;&gt;Backup Camera&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2EL3NLR&quot;&gt;Bluetooth OBDII Adapter (optional)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/parts.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So ordering the headunit is a little sketchy. It’s from Aliexpress in China, and will take 2-4 weeks to arrive. This one comes with external GPS, microphone, a WiFi antenna, works with the existing aux input, and has 2 USB female cables to attach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There seems to be only a few aftermarket headunits made for the non-Nav GX470, and the fine folks on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/LexusGXOR&quot;&gt;GXOR&lt;/a&gt; seem to think this is the best option. If you have a navigation equipped GX470, the best option is a Tesla-style massive screen. It costs quite a bit more and makes the air conditioned buttons integrated into the touch screen, which I would hate. Luckily I don’t have that model!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;install&quot;&gt;Install&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, take out any CDs in your current headunit. I forgot to do this. If you want to buy my old headunit, it comes with 6 great CDs!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/remove_air.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, remove the two trim pieces on either side of the shifter, using a flat head screwdriver or a plastic trim puller. I used a screwdriver.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then remove the 2 air conditioner vents. Lift gently from the bottom, where the trim pieces were holding them in. These 2 pieces are supposed to be very expensive to replace, so be very careful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, remove the connector from each side. The drivers side has the hazard light connecter, the passenger side has the passenger air bag light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/left_air.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/right_air.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now you can pop out and unplug the coin/ash tray and the cigarette lighter, located below the air conditioning controls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take the 6 10mm bolts out of the radio harness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You basically have 3 pieces to your center stack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Top - Clock/MPG display&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Middle - Headunit, what we’re replacing&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bottom - A/C controls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/screws.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Start taking screws out of the existing Lexus headunit. There were a lot of screws to remove these 3 parts, and I didn’t document it, but prepare to spend a while on this. Also, you don’t reuse MOST of these screws, I had a ton left over. Once done un-screwing, remove all the connecters and remove the whole thing from the car. I did this, and it made it much easier to install the new head unit into the metal harness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/removed.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note that the 10mm bolt, about where your knee is when driving (and shown just above my knee in the following picture), connects the harnesses that supply power. When testing your install, you’ll need to screw that in all the way. This is something I found out later while debugging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/10mm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have the pieces out of your car, you can install the new headunit into the same spot. To do this, you’ll need to do a small amount of plastic removal on the A/C controls in your Lexus. I used a dremel, as shown below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/dremel1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cut the top tab just a bit on the A/C controls. These tabs protrude too much for the new head unit to clip in and fit flush.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/dremel2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After some cutting, the air conditioning controls will clip in below it. I installed the top piece after I had inserted the rest back into the car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/schematic.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As far as connections go, this was pretty simple. Connect like to like connectors where you can find them. I ran the USB female connectors into the glove box, since I won’t use them often and didn’t want to mount them. I ran the GPS module behind the dash, and stuck it up as high and far back as I could, then used the supplied 3M backing tape. It gets a very good signal, even when not exposed. I chose not to mount the microphone that was included with the headunit, as the included mic on the front of the headunit seemed to do a good enough job for my uses. The WiFi antennae is short and is attached to the back of the headunit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/chrome.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll also want to run your wiring for the reverse camera. For the part behind the headunit, wire the yellow into the backup camera input (9) and tap the reverse cable in. For the run to your back door, you’ll need to do this on the passenger side, because of the way the rear door opens. I ran my wire behind the glove box and under the plastic tray on the seats, all the way to the 3rd row area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/grommet.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is where it gets more complicated. You’ll need to run the wiring through the grommet thing seen above(hardest and most painful part of this whole project), and into the rear door area. There is almost no room inside the grommet to run the cable, so this will take some time. The rear door should paneling should be removed, which is pretty easy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Damage from running the wiring through the grommet into the rear door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/damage.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The wiring for the rear camera is simple. Connect the reverse power wire that you ran from the headunit (red), and the power wire (red) from the camera to the reverse light power wire, which is red with blue stripe. I used the passenger side reverse light since it was closer. Seal that connection with some solder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/camera_wiring.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The yellow video cable from the camera connects to the RCA that you ran from the headunit. The ground (black) from the camera connects to any ground on the rear door, there are a quite few bolts you can use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/installed.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the headunit side, make sure you plug the yellow from the rearview camera into the correct video input. I did not do that the first time, and had to take apart my dash again. You want to use input 9, the rearview input.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/camera.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To mount the rear camera, I drilled 2 very small holes in the black plastic part directly above the license plate. I put the 2 camera screw in there with the camera, then ran the wire through where the drivers side license plate light was at. However, then the light wouldn’t stay in its spot, since it had a wire blocking the seal. I drilled out a very small notch into that opening for the light, just big enough for the wire to run through. I placed the wire in there, seen below, then the light would stay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/wire.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;thoughts&quot;&gt;Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love the headunit. This was my first car audio install other than replacing speakers. The install was relatively easy, the inside of the car looks much nicer, and the audio is much better than flipping through radio stations or CDs. I have a 2007 GX470, which means it came with an aux port, and that is still functional with this headunit. The only downsides so far are that the screen became slightly unglued in the bottom left, probably because of the Florida heat. Maps are a little tricky, since this headunit is not always on an internet connection. So far, I’ve had success using Google Maps with a large portion downloaded locally onto the Android headunit. Still, this was a great $300 spent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;apps-i-recommend&quot;&gt;Apps I recommend&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=org.prowl.torque&quot;&gt;Torque Pro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.autolauncher.motorcar.free&quot;&gt;Car Launcher FREE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.pandora.android&quot;&gt;Pandora&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.music&quot;&gt;Google Play Music&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=org.prowl.torque&quot;&gt;Torque&lt;/a&gt; is an awesome app for reading car diagnostics. I bought Torque Pro in 2011, and it has been used very often to read, diagnose, and clear engine codes, as well as get real time statistics from your car. You can connect to Torque using the OBDII interface in your car, and by using a Wifi or &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2EL3NLR&quot;&gt;Bluetooth OBDII adapter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/torque.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.autolauncher.motorcar.free&quot;&gt;Car Launcher&lt;/a&gt; is a simple launcher application that makes the Android interface a little more car friendly. The buttons are bigger, you can dim the screen with one click, set the few applications you actually use on your home screen. It works well for me. The layouts are also customizable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/launcher.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.pandora.android&quot;&gt;Pandora&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.music&quot;&gt;Google Play Music&lt;/a&gt; can download music and play offline. Some use Spotify or other apps. You can also plug in a USB filled with music into your USB inputs, play music on your phone over Bluetooth, or Wifi tether to your headunit and let the headunit do the audio while online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/bt.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The backup camera is great so far. I think every large car should have one, and this one works especially well with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2SWAmN5&quot;&gt;reverse lights&lt;/a&gt; I have. This camera also has the backup lines built in to the camera feed, so you don’t have to enable them in the Android settings&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/backup.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus the dogs love it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/dogtax.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My Turo Claim Horror Story</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/My-Turo-Claim-Horror-Story/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Turo Claim Horror Story" /><published>2019-02-21T08:00:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-02-21T08:00:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/My-Turo-Claim-Horror-Story</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/My-Turo-Claim-Horror-Story/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/no_window.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;No Window&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;tldr&quot;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dude rents my nice Corvette on Turo, his bi-polar girlfriend vandalizes it, it takes 46 days for Turo to pay to get &lt;em&gt;most&lt;/em&gt; of it fixed, and they wouldn’t fix some of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;background&quot;&gt;Background&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/daniel.martinez.9822?eid=ARA1sLcJCI6aBEHu94oDyZUMBivz-L4RagzNM8K8-3gZ19GkX3xu6JMc-Tz3LdSULecDuvp0h7VbpOz-&amp;amp;timeline_context_item_type=intro_card_relationship&amp;amp;timeline_context_item_source=100004641037329&quot;&gt;Daniel B&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/street.lawyer/&quot;&gt;Martinez Jr&lt;/a&gt;, age 37, a &lt;a href=&quot;https://themartinezlaw.com&quot;&gt;local attorney&lt;/a&gt;, rented my &lt;a href=&quot;https://turo.com/rentals/cars/fl/palm-bay/chevrolet-corvette/381353&quot;&gt;2016 Corvette 2LT&lt;/a&gt; from Jan 3 to Jan 5 on a website called &lt;a href=&quot;https://turo.com/c/roberts974&quot;&gt;Turo&lt;/a&gt;. Turo is a website where you can rent your personal car to other people, and Turo provides insurance. Kinda like AirBNB for cars. He had rented my Corvette for a weekend previously, and only put 10 miles on it. The other time he rented my car, I had to go through his dad in order to pick my car up, since he wouldn’t answer his phone or texts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;timeline&quot;&gt;Timeline&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-3&quot;&gt;Jan 3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12:30 PM - Daniel picks up my Corvette, shown below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/before.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-4&quot;&gt;Jan 4&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;11:55 PM - At nearly midnight, a Palm Bay Police Officer, Matt, arrives at my house asking if I owned a blue Chevrolet. I do. He informs me that Daniel had left my car abandoned at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/place/Cumberland+Farms/@28.0791818,-80.6409332,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x88de0e04064cc945:0xc10058927e69d5c2!8m2!3d28.0791818!4d-80.6387392&quot;&gt;Cumberland Farms gas station on 192 and Dairy Rd in West Melbourne&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matt passes my cell phone number on to a West Melbourne police officer on the scene at the gas station, who calls me. He informs me that my window was broken on my car, and I should come down there and get the car. He said that Daniel’s mother was at the gas station and she had my Corvette key. I get a ride there, and a West Melbourne Police officer is there, who leaves before I get to talk to him, and Daniel’s mother is there. I have just 1 key for the Corvette, and the officer said Daniel’s mother had it. She didn’t. She then drove to her house (where Daniel lives) to get my key.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;damage&quot;&gt;Damage&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/no_window.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;No Window&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The driver window was knocked out and busted on the ground. There was damage on the drivers door and mirror. A scratch on the hatchback. A piece of the front grill missing (this was pre-existing damage, as I later found out). The splitter under the front grill was damaged. A scratch in the leather on the passenger interior. Glass everywhere. The targa top was removed and placed in the hatch, and it was raining, and I had no way to put the top back on since Daniel had my key. Who knows how long it had been raining.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/roof_scrape.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Roof Scrape&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She arrived back about 20 minutes later with a key, and I pop the hatch to put the top back on. The top is in terrible condition, with scratches and deep scrapes all over it. It was like someone used the painted part of the top as an ice sled, or hockey puck. Just really bad shape. I put the top back on to keep the water out of the car, and a trash bag over the lack of drivers window. I waited for the officer to come back to get the police report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/side.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Side&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had talked to the employees at the Cumberland Farms gas station. They said they got the whole thing on video. My car was parked in the front corner spot, right under 2 cameras. Daniel’s girlfriend, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/marina.rogers.739&quot;&gt;Marina&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/marinarogers112/&quot;&gt;Rogers&lt;/a&gt;, age 21, found out that Daniel had cheated on her and was trying to attack Daniel while he was driving, and he didn’t like that. He pulled over and parked my Corvette at a gas station, then got an Uber home. She was mad she couldn’t attack him, so she vandalized my car. The Cumberland Farms employee said she punched the drivers window three times, then grabbed the top of the window and leaned back with all her weight to break the window.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;police-interaction&quot;&gt;Police Interaction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/police.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Police&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Cumberland Farms employee said I couldn’t see or retrieve the video evidence without the police. A West Melbourne police officer, Casey, ID#745, finally showed back up to the scene, and gave me a case number, &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/docs/police_report.pdf&quot;&gt;2019-00000441&lt;/a&gt;. Casey told me I can go through Turo, mine or Daniel’s Insurance, or small claims court in order to get my car fixed. He also said what Daniel’s girlfriend did is not a crime, since it isn’t a crime to vandalize someone else’s car. The damage was considered civil, as opposed to criminal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found out through Casey that Daniel’s girlfriend, Marina Rogers, had been checked into a local mental health institution, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.circlesofcare.org/current1/home-page.html&quot;&gt;Circles of Care&lt;/a&gt;. The cop said she was bi-polar. Daniel’s mom said she was really drunk. Daniel did not inform me of any damage to my car, he never messaged me or called me back, and did not seem remorseful about this event in the slightest. After viewing the &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/docs/police_report.pdf&quot;&gt;police report&lt;/a&gt;, it appears Marina Rogers was drunk and suicidal. The officer recognized this, and enacted the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Florida_Mental_Health_Act&quot;&gt;Baker Act&lt;/a&gt; to bring her to the mental facility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-5&quot;&gt;Jan 5&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12:30 AM Picked up the Corvette at Cumberland Farms, drove it home and vacuumed up glass&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:26 AM - Opened up a damage claim with Turo with photo/video walkthrough after I got home&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10AM - Cleaned up the car some more. Noted that Daniel left a $1,300 deposit slip and some blank checks from Wells Fargo in the car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/mirror.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mirror&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-6&quot;&gt;Jan 6&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-7&quot;&gt;Jan 7&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Got a damage quote from John Bias, owner of &lt;a href=&quot;https://acesautobodyshop.com&quot;&gt;Ace’s Body Shop &lt;/a&gt;- 8k&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Called Daniel at his office, left a message with his secretary. Told her the damage was 8k. She said not to worry and that Daniel would make it right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Messaged Turo Damage Claims with the 8k damage estimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-8&quot;&gt;Jan 8&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Called Daniel on his cell, left a voicemail to call me back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Daniel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-9&quot;&gt;Jan 9&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Got a quote from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gerbercollision.com/locations/palm-bay-fl&quot;&gt;Gerber Collision&lt;/a&gt;, with their associate JP. Quote was 7.3k, + 1.5k to 5k more for new seat and dealer code resets. So even higher than Ace’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sent Turo follow up email with second quote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Called Turo support - got Sylvia. She said to wait for the claims specialist to contact me later today. The Claims Specialist’s name is Donovan Durr, 415-941-0706, donovan.durr@turo.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Submitted a request to West Melbourne PD for the case report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Donovan Durr from Turo support contacted me. He mentioned that the grill already had a piece missing when I had rented it before, according to the pictures. I looked, and he’s right. The grill even had that piece missing when I bought it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daniel finally messaged me that night, saying he’s been busy with a jury and asking what he needed to do to take care of this. I messaged him back saying 8k was the damage cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-10&quot;&gt;Jan 10&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Daniel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I cleaned the interior with soap and water and was able to get the scuffing off of the drivers seat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-11&quot;&gt;Jan 11&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Received email from Donovan at Turo, requesting photos of scratches and damage with a ruler next to it. Photos sent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Received &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/docs/police_report.pdf&quot;&gt;police report&lt;/a&gt; from West Melbourne Police Dept, forwarded to Donovan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Call with Donovan Durr at 3:30PM EST. Said he is reviewing with his supervisor. Follow-up in 1 business day. Nothing else to talk about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Daniel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-12&quot;&gt;Jan 12&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Daniel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From Donovan at Turo:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I reviewed this claim with my supervisor. We’re going to cover the damage to the driver’s side door, the mirror, and the top in that area. We’re going to be denying the damage to the rear passenger quarter panel as we cannot determine if that scratch may have been there based on the pre-trip photos provided for that area and the difficulty of seeing the scratch due to its nature.
For the splitter, we would not be able to cover that as we would need pre-trip photos of the undercarriage unfortunately. Although we don’t have pre-trip photos of the interior, we will reimburse you $200 for the interior as well as cover any water damage that may have occurred to due to the top being left off. Your shop of choice will need to file a supplement request for that portion of the claim.
Finally, I want to do a final review on the scratches on the targa top that go down towards the passenger’s side door. I was advised to move forward with a denial for it as my supervisor wasn’t able to see the damage in the post trip photo we looked at, but as we have a few others on file(and the video from the scene), I want to make sure that we are making the right decision. As I do not work Tuesday through Saturday, I do typically do not work on Mondays, but I will see if I can get her to take a second look at that area. If we decide to move forward with coverage, I will go ahead and get that added to our estimate and we should have this fully resolved by early next week. Thank you for your patience as I know this is frustrating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-13&quot;&gt;Jan 13&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Daniel messaged me on the Turo app, saying he has elected to go through Turo to settle this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joined &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/1825468964354089/&quot;&gt;Turo Owners group&lt;/a&gt; on FB for advice on how to deal with Turo. General advice is to use &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fairclaims.com&quot;&gt;FairClaims&lt;/a&gt; and to not take the first number Turo offers you. Just escalate it when they low ball you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-14&quot;&gt;Jan 14&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Noticed that Turo has delisted my Corvette from their website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-15&quot;&gt;Jan 15&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Created account on ResolveAClaim app, as instructed by Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Snapsheet estimator was Marvin Acosta. Snapsheet is a third party that Turo goes through to get damage estimates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From Donovan:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;My supervisor took a second look at the claim and we will be able to go ahead and cover the scratches on the top as well. So that would be everything covered except for this scratch attached to this message, that portion of the front grill that was already missing and the damage to the splitter. I will go ahead and have an estimate written up at this time. If you have any questions, feel free to let me know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-16&quot;&gt;Jan 16&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Received email from SnapSheet, offering me $1,169.51 to cover the damages. The denied a large part of the damage to my car. They said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We have no pre-trip photos of the undercarriage, the damage to the front grill is pre-existing, and we cannot determine if the scratch on the rear hatch on the passenger’s side is pre-existing based on the pre-trip photos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Based on the circumstances, I regret to inform you this claim is ineligible for coverage because pre-existing damage and areas claimed without pre-trip photos are not covered under our policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-17&quot;&gt;Jan 17&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Accepted $1,169.51 payment from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Donovan said $200 interior damage refund will go directly to my earnings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Left a message for Ace’s on dropping off Vette and working on supplements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-18&quot;&gt;Jan 18&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brought Vette to Ace’s, John took pictures and said that he’d work on supplements with Turo/Snapsheet&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-19&quot;&gt;Jan 19&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-20&quot;&gt;Jan 20&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-21&quot;&gt;Jan 21&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-22&quot;&gt;Jan 22&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-23&quot;&gt;Jan 23&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sent estimate to Gerber Collision from Snapsheet, I never heard back from Gerber&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;John Bias from Ace’s called back - said Snapsheet (Laura was the rep) will approve all supplements. Can bring in Monday, Jan 28.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-24&quot;&gt;Jan 24&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-25&quot;&gt;Jan 25&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-26&quot;&gt;Jan 26&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-27&quot;&gt;Jan 27&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-28&quot;&gt;Jan 28&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brought in Vette to Ace’s Body Shop at 9:15AM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-29&quot;&gt;Jan 29&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Received an email from Snapsheet at 4:30PM about receiving the supplement from Ace’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-30&quot;&gt;Jan 30&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-31&quot;&gt;Jan 31&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-1&quot;&gt;Feb 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-2&quot;&gt;Feb 2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-3&quot;&gt;Feb 3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-4&quot;&gt;Feb 4&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-5&quot;&gt;Feb 5&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-6&quot;&gt;Feb 6&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-7&quot;&gt;Feb 7&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-8&quot;&gt;Feb 8&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Got a call from John at Ace’s Body Shop. Said Corvette is painted, total is about $4700. Still waiting on Snapsheet to send over the supplement approval. John said that Snapsheet is not wanting to put in an OEM window glass, however, there seem to be no aftermarket window glass parts available anyways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;John said he has been working with Michael Ecker, who is an adjuster for Snapsheet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I called Snapsheet support. They said my supplement is approved for the full amount that Ace’s will charge. They said they sent that approval to Turo on February 7, and Turo is the middle man and has to send it to Ace’s Body shop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Called Turo to follow up - waited 27 minutes before requesting a call back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Got a call back from Richard at Turo. He said he is approving it today, sending me and the body shop an email with information today, and that then I can claim the remaining ~$3600 from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Called Ace’s to let them know the full supplement was approved and will be sent over today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-9&quot;&gt;Feb 9&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-10&quot;&gt;Feb 10&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-11&quot;&gt;Feb 11&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heard back from Donovan at Turo Support, the supplement went from Snapsheet to him. He said that Snapsheet incorrectly listed the damage as on the windshield instead of the drivers window, so he is getting them to redo it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-12&quot;&gt;Feb 12&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John from Ace’s called, the car is finished except putting a few trim pieces on. Windows on and tinted, paint looks good. Planned to pick up car on Friday, Feb 15.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heard back from Donovan with a supplement payment of $3,066.96.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That would put the total paid  at $3,066.96 + $1,169.51 + $200 = $4,436.47&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Asked Donovan about getting the additional amount owed, and mentioned using &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fairclaims.com/&quot;&gt;FairClaims&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total Charges from Ace’s = $4,538.47&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-13&quot;&gt;Feb 13&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-14&quot;&gt;Feb 14&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-15&quot;&gt;Feb 15&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Corvette detailed at Ace’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Picked up car from Ace’s, total charge was $4,538.47, which I paid out of pocket. These clear protector on the drivers door over the paint was not installed, so he said for me to come back up next week to get it installed, it is already paid for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;John found a full container of hair gel in the car that Daniel had left in it from the rental.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/gel.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Gel&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-16&quot;&gt;Feb 16&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donovan from Turo said that he has submitted the second supplement payment for authorization to a supervisor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-17&quot;&gt;Feb 17&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-18&quot;&gt;Feb 18&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-19&quot;&gt;Feb 19&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Received $316.23 from Turo on second supplement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total paid from Turo =  $1,169.51 + $200 + $3,066.96 + $316.23 = $4,752.70.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total paid to Ace’s = $4,538.47&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So after all was finished, I got to keep $214.13, but I have a large scratch on my hatch that Turo would not cover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-20&quot;&gt;Feb 20&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://turo.com/rentals/cars/fl/palm-bay/chevrolet-corvette/381353&quot;&gt;Corvette relisted&lt;/a&gt;, required multiple day rentals and higher rate per day, along with a cleaning fee if not returned clean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-21&quot;&gt;Feb 21&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Changed my mind, took the Corvette off Turo because this was a nightmare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, I want to thank &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/Aces-Autobody-1381810925437470/&quot;&gt;Ace’s Body Shop&lt;/a&gt;. They did a great job on my car, and John went above and beyond filling out multiple supplements for Turo and Snapsheet. Seriously, thanks, you guys were great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It took 46 days for Turo to fix damages on my car, and hours of my time dealing with Turo Support, getting quotes from body shops, requesting police reports, and sending in pictures. I was very unsatisfied with both the quality and punctuality of Turo Support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have learned that, if you rent your car on Turo, it should be a car you don’t care about, and to take 50+ pictures before and after every rental. Part of my claim was denied because I only took the 5 required before and after pictures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turo is not on your side, and will do everything possibly to pay you as little as possible. It took me almost 7 weeks to get my damages paid for. I was lucky that I have another car, or else I would have been without a car for a majority of those 7 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;appendix&quot;&gt;Appendix&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.app.goo.gl/EEWHzVyj2soqduuT9&quot;&gt;Pictures/Videos&lt;/a&gt; of the Corvette, timestamps in the details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/daniel.martinez.9822?eid=ARA1sLcJCI6aBEHu94oDyZUMBivz-L4RagzNM8K8-3gZ19GkX3xu6JMc-Tz3LdSULecDuvp0h7VbpOz-&amp;amp;timeline_context_item_type=intro_card_relationship&amp;amp;timeline_context_item_source=100004641037329&quot;&gt;Daniel B&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/street.lawyer&quot;&gt;Martinez Jr&lt;/a&gt; - Rented my Corvette&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Age: 37&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Address: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/place/554+Sedgewood+Cir,+Melbourne,+FL+32904/@28.0543978,-80.6605715,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x88de0dc110aa0175:0x96e0eb8bac68e40e!8m2!3d28.0543978!4d-80.6583775&quot;&gt;554 Sedgewood Circle, Melbourne, FL&lt;/a&gt;. This is a rental house owned by American Homes 4 Rent.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;He lives with his parents, Daniel and Grace Martinez&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Personal email = elsospetto@gmail.com&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cell listed on Turo  321-361-6793&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Law Office Number  321-419-8666&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/marina.rogers.739&quot;&gt;Marina&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/marinarogers112/&quot;&gt;Rogers&lt;/a&gt; - Daniel Martinez’ girlfriend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Age: 21&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Address: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/place/102+Palm+Cir,+Melbourne,+FL+32940/@28.1924181,-80.6625654,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x88de051482b308c7:0x14521373bab1ecfe!8m2!3d28.1924181!4d-80.6603714&quot;&gt;102 Palm Cir Palm Shores, Fl 32940&lt;/a&gt;, owner is Brian Rogers, her father.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They had been dating for 4 months at the time of the vandalism, and are still dating as of the writing of this post.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;FIT student/cheerleader/Publix cashier.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New Lexus Key</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/New-Lexus-Keys/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Lexus Key" /><published>2019-02-07T11:00:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-02-07T11:00:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/New-Lexus-Keys</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/New-Lexus-Keys/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/keys.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Keys&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I fixed the 2 keys for my Lexus. The battery in both keys was dead, so the remote didn’t work. The screws to get the battery out were stripped, so I have to destroy each case to get in. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ajtdesign-llc.com/online-store/Injection-Fob-2008-2014-FJ-Cruiser-BLACK-p109350070&quot;&gt;AJT Designs&lt;/a&gt; makes some cool 3D printed key fob cases. The GX 470 uses the same key fob as the FJ Cruiser, so I ordered 2 of them in different color combos, seen above. I also installed new &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2MU7wuz&quot;&gt;CR1616&lt;/a&gt; batteries, and both keys work perfect now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/parking.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Parking&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also found out this thing is difficult to park, and ordered a new 9” head unit to replace the stock radio.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Cleaning Headlights and Other Improvements on the Lexus</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Cleaning-Headlights-and-other-improvements-on-the-Lexus/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cleaning Headlights and Other Improvements on the Lexus" /><published>2019-01-28T11:00:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-28T11:00:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Cleaning-Headlights-and-other-improvements-on-the-Lexus</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Cleaning-Headlights-and-other-improvements-on-the-Lexus/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/in_process.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve cleaned the headlights on my Lexus, using toothpaste and car wax. Materials included a tube of toothpaste with baking soda, some wax, an old toothbrush, and some rags. Simply spread the toothpaste around the headlights in a circular motion, similar to waxing. Let it sit for a few minutes, then wipe off with some damp rags. Then wax your headlights to apply a sealant on your lights. Toothpaste is not a good sealant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before Pictures
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/before_L.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/before_L_F.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/before_R.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Materials
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/materials.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/toothpaste.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/in.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/in_process.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Removing Toothpaste and Waxing
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/after_L.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/after_R.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/after_L_F.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/after_R_F.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I noticed a huge difference on the fog lights, which were really cloudy. The headlights themselves improved some, but they weren’t that bad to start with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also installed a new &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2MBqzcI&quot;&gt;gas cap&lt;/a&gt;, which got rid of a few engine error codes, and some new &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2RSoajZ&quot;&gt;hood struts&lt;/a&gt;. The hood fell on me while I was changing some bulbs the other week, and I didn’t want that to happen again. The hood struts took about 20 minutes to change, and I needed a 12mm socket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/hood.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/hood2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Parts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2MBqzcI&quot;&gt;Toyota Gas Cap&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2RSoajZ&quot;&gt;BOXI Hood struts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Exterior Lights</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Lexus-GX470-Exterior-Lights/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Exterior Lights" /><published>2019-01-15T11:00:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-15T11:00:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Lexus-GX470-Exterior-Lights</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Lexus-GX470-Exterior-Lights/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/lights4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;All&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wrote about &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/Lexus-GX470-LED-Interior-Lights/&quot;&gt;installing new Interior LEDs&lt;/a&gt; on my Lexus GX470, and here’s a bit about exterior lights. I installed new low beams, high beams, daytime running lamps, fog lights, and reverse lights. The install of all of these lights took about an hour. For the front lights, you just have to remove a few engine covers, and for the reverse lights, you have to remove the rear door cover. The fog lights were the most difficult, as you have to get under the car with a 10mm socket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was very happy with the outcome - for under $110, you get a higher end look out of your vehicle, but also much better visibility. The reverse lights and high beams are incredible. My only complaint was that the fogs were yellower than I’d hoped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a list of lights I used, you need 2 of each bulb:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2SUTGdu&quot;&gt;H11 - Low Beams&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2FyBJgO&quot;&gt;9005 - High Beams&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2sv2Dyq&quot;&gt;H3 - Fog Lights&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2SWAmN5&quot;&gt;7440 - Reverse Lights&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2S6HvcZ&quot;&gt;194 - Daytime Running Lights&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Low Beams Only
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/lights1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Low&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;High Beams - these give amazing visibility when driving!
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/lights2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;High&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daytime Running Lights only
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/lights3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;DRL&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Low Beams and Fogs
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/lights4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;All&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d like to thank the kind members of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/LexusGXOR&quot;&gt;GXOR Facebook group&lt;/a&gt; for their suggestions. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pfranleds.com/gx-470-1/&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; is a handy website for all the light bulbs in a GX470.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Final Bedroom Remodel</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/final-bedroom-remodel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Final Bedroom Remodel" /><published>2019-01-04T11:00:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-04T11:00:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/final-bedroom-remodel</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/final-bedroom-remodel/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/23.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Owen finally moved out and I got the chance to renovate that bedroom. We installed new switches, outlets, floors, ceiling fan, and paint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total renovation cost was under $400! I already had extra light switches, underlayment, and tools to install everything. Here is what else I bought:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lowes.com/pd/Harbor-Breeze-Centreville-42-in-Brushed-Nickel-LED-Indoor-Ceiling-Fan-with-Light-Kit/1000259351&quot;&gt;Ceiling Fan&lt;/a&gt;: $54&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Switch covers: $2&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lowes.com/pd/Style-Selections-Ginger-Hickory-8-05-in-W-x-3-97-ft-L-Smooth-Wood-Plank-Laminate-Flooring/50243461&quot;&gt;Laminate (170 sqft)&lt;/a&gt;: $150&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lowes.com/pd/SimpleSolutions-2-37-in-x-78-74-in-Natural-Oak-Ginger-Hickory-4-n-1-Floor-Moulding/1000094233&quot;&gt;Transition Piece&lt;/a&gt;: $27&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lowes.com/pd/SimpleSolutions-0-75-in-x-94-5-in-Natural-Oak-Ginger-Hickory-Quarter-Round-Floor-Moulding/1000094225&quot;&gt;Quarter round&lt;/a&gt;: $70 - this is enough for 2 more bedrooms as well&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lowes.com/pd/EverTrue-5-25-in-x-12-ft-Interior-Primed-MDF-Baseboard-Moulding/1000444895&quot;&gt;Baseboards&lt;/a&gt;: $77&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Total = $378&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before, it was full of green carpet from 1996, gross walls with gross stuff all over them, an out of date fan, and ugly old baseboards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took off all the switch and outlet covers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Removed the baseboards and painted the window trim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Painted the room. I had already painted around the door frames and installed new 6 panel doors, which I took off for this project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used some bleach to clean up that black grossness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paint, paint, paint. I did 2 coats, and then touched up random spots afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Started ripping out all the carpet. This took 2 weeks worth of trash bins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then took out all the carpet tack strips. The best technique for this that I’ve found is to use a flat head shovel, and have a large trash can nearby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here you can see the new outlets and switches going in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clean the floors before starting to install your laminate. I officially have no more carpet in my house!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dogs help. No they don’t, they get in the way, but they’re fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2RvdhDr&quot;&gt;underlayment&lt;/a&gt; going in. This is the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2RvdhDr&quot;&gt;same underlayment&lt;/a&gt; I had used a few years ago when I did the rest of my house in this laminate. One roll was enough for my entire living room and 3 bedrooms, with plenty still leftover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New 42” ceiling fan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/16.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First laminate piece in!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/17.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Half a room, the easy half.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/18.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alex measuring for the angled cuts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/19.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything but the last row in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/20.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All done except the baseboards! It took me and Alex about 2 hours to put in the entire room, we were booking it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/21.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Baseboards in, it took me a few hours of working by myself one afternoon to finish these.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/22.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also installed laminate matching quarter round, which I had never put in before. The rest of my rooms have white quarter round, or no quarter round. I think that these segmented off rooms, like a bedroom, look great with floor matching quarter round. I’m planning to put it in the other 2 bedrooms, which currently have no quarter round.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/owen/23.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Owen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Drive Cool Cars on a Budget [Updated January 2019]</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/drive-cool-cars-on-a-budget/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Drive Cool Cars on a Budget [Updated January 2019]" /><published>2019-01-03T08:05:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-03T08:05:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/drive-cool-cars-on-a-budget</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/drive-cool-cars-on-a-budget/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/lexus.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Both&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of life’s biggest expenses is transportation, especially cars. I love cars, and love getting different cars. I get bored driving the same vehicle for more than a few years. You could imagine this would be expensive, but it doesn’t have to be. I’m 26 and have owned 9 cars (10 if you count my fiancés Fiat 500, not listed below), and I’ve not lost much money on them at all. The biggest downside is that you have to pay registration and taxes on every car you buy, but some of that can be tax deductible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The list that follows is all of the cars I’ve owned, how much I paid and sold them for, how many miles I put on them, and about how expensive it was to own each one. I’ve included insurance costs, city/highway MPG, and the cost of oil changes and registration so that you can see how affordable each was to own. My first 3 cars I owned in high school, so my helped me out by paying for gas, insurance, and registration. Also, 7 of these cars were Rear Wheel Drive, manual transmission cars, and I have owned two silver on black V8 automatic AWD SUVs. 6 of the 9 were American made and had no issues, and 2 were German made and had so many issues. The one Japanese car has been great so far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-1993-ford-mustang-lx&quot;&gt;1. 1993 Ford Mustang LX&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $1,700 / 195,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $1,750 / 205,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 25/30, regular gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 2.3L 4-cylinder, 100HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $30 for standard oil change, every 3,000 to 5,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/93mustang.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1993 Mustang&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This car was bought by my parents for me and my brother to learn to drive a manual transmission. I broke the clutch in it, and the A/C compressor went out in it, which cost about $600 to fix both. We owned it for a few years as an extra car, and sold it for more than we paid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-1996-ford-mustang&quot;&gt;2. 1996 Ford Mustang&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $3,600 / 118,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $2,400 / 135,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 23/28, regular gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 3.6L 6-cylinder, 150HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $30 for standard oil change, every 3,000 to 5,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/96mustang.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1996 Mustang&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was the first car I bought myself, the older, silver Mustang in the middle of the picture. I put a $70 Cold Air Intake on it. Other than that, I did no major work on the car, so it had no expenses outside of gas and oil changes. I originally sold the car for $3,200, but the buyer blew a head gasket on the way home. This really surprised me, since after I had 17,000 issue-free miles, they broke a major part in a 5 mile drive home. Since they were family friends, I took it back, and sold it as is a week later for $800 less.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-1999-chevrolet-camaro&quot;&gt;3. 1999 Chevrolet Camaro&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $4,000 / 99,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $3,600 / 115,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 22/27, regular gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 3.8L 6-cylinder, 200HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $30 for standard oil change, every 3,000 to 5,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/camaro.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1999 Camaro&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought the Camaro before heading to college as something more exciting – it had T-Tops! The picture doesn’t portray how enthralled I was. I drove this at the beginning of my college career and had no issues with it. Just a couple hundred dollars upgrading the headlights and front grill, hey, I was 18! When I sold it after a few years, I didn’t lose much money to upgrade to my next car, which was a…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;4-2004-cadillac-cts-v&quot;&gt;4. 2004 Cadillac CTS-V&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $17,800 / 49,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $13,000 / 99,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 16/23, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $120/mo for full coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 5.7L 8-cylinder, 400HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $100 for full synthetic oil change, every 10,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/ctsv.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2004 CTS-V&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought this with the money I had saved from summer jobs and my first semester of Co-oping as a Test Engineer. It came with new tires, I got one set of new tires for free a few years later from my brother (he won them), and I sold it needing new tires. The CTS-V was an amazing car: a luxury sport sedan with a Corvette Z06 engine and a 6-speed manual transmission. I loved it! However, the insurance was really high, and so were the gas costs. This was the longest I had ever owned a car, which was about 4 years. I sold it when I moved down to Florida for my first real Engineering job. I still find myself wanting a car like this again, and they are still selling used years later for the same prices. No more depreciation on these, unfortunately for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;5-2008-chevrolet-corvette&quot;&gt;5. 2008 Chevrolet Corvette&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $27,500 / 36,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $26,500 /49,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 23/30, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $90/mo for full coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 6.2L 8-cylinder, 430HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $100 for full synthetic oil change, every 10,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $3,000&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/c6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2008 Corvette&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought the Corvette after getting my first paycheck as a full time employee after college. A bright blue Corvette with a targa top in perfect Florida weather, why not? A few months later, I was wondering how bad of a financial decision it really was. My dad and brother gave me 0% loans since I couldn’t pay for all of it at once, and I was paying them about $1,000/month to pay it off quickly. It took about 6 months to pay off. Finally selling my CTS-V really helped. I owned the Corvette for a little over a year, and luckily sold it for not much of a loss in order to pay off the down payment on my house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buying a Corvette and a house in the same year might not be the best financial decision, but it worked out for me once I sold the Vette. This was the nicest and fastest car I had owned at this point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The expenses on this were really low, since insurance is super cheap and it got relatively good MPG for a sports car. Everyone wonders how the insurance low, so think about this: Who buys a Corvette, and what do they do with them? Most Corvette owners are 60+ and retired, and they use their Corvette as a weekend car or cruiser, not a daily driver. This means they are garaged the majority of the time, and there are not very many insurance claims on them. This drives the insurance price pretty low, which was great for me! Most people in Corvette Clubs like to brag how few miles they put on their Vette, I was the opposite. I put about 13,000 miles on mine in the year I owned it, and loved every single one of them. It made me want to get back into one once I was more financially stable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;6-1999-porsche-boxster&quot;&gt;6. 1999 Porsche Boxster&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bought: $5,500 / 85,000 miles
Sold: $5,000  / 89,000 miles
MPG: 19/25, premium gas
Insurance: $50/mo for legal minimum
Engine: 2.5L 6-cylinder, 200HP
Oil Changes: $95 for full synthetic oil change, every 7,000 miles
Taxes/Registration: $500&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/boxster.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1999 Boxster&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought the Porsche as a replacement to Corvette, which I sold to pay towards the down payment on my house. The difference in selling my Corvette and buying a Porsche was over $21,000! My co-workers wondered why I “upgraded” from a Corvette to a Porsche, and their jaw dropped when they find out I only paid $6,000 after tax and registration for it. The insurance for full coverage on it was about $130/mo, which I thought was insane on a car that’s so cheap. Therefore, I just went for the legal minimum. My thoughts were that if I wreck it, I can just buy another car. I’m also quite confident in my driving abilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I called it my cheap beater Porsche, and that’s not too far off. I converted the non-functional automatic convertible top to a manually-operated top, and I just leave it down all the time. The back window was plastic that has faded to yellow, so it had terrible visibility when the top is up. I spent $50 on new tail light bulbs and a new headlight switch, since those didn’t work when I bought it. Luckily for me, I picked this up for a steal on Craigslist, and bought it the same day it was posted. I loved driving a cheap car that I don’t care about anymore! I kept this about 9 months. I put about $350 into new brakes and rotors. I did them myself, since the dealer quoted $2,700 to do it. When I sold it on eBay, it needed a new water pump, which was about $700 installed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I lost about $1,000 to drive this for close to a year, not bad. I sold it to buy my first automatic car, and first non-sports car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;7-2005-bmw-x5-48&quot;&gt;7. 2005 BMW X5 4.8&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $7,000 / 102,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $7,005 in trade-in / 108,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 14/19, premium gas (ouch)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $67/mo for legal minimum&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 4.8L 8-cylinder, 360HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: None yet&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $700&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/x5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2005 X5&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought this awesome BMW SUV. It was $72,000 new, and I bought it for 10% of that. It was large inside, had a panoramic sunroof, Bluetooth, and heated seats in the front and back. Perfect for Florida! It came with huge 20″ rims that are 315 in the back. I got lots of compliments on the wheels. The car was enjoyable to drive, the A/C was so cold, and it felt like it owned the road. It’s not a sports car, but it’ll scoot. 360HP in this SUV is no slouch. It’s got torque to tow as well. The gas mileage is horrific on this car, and it holds 25 gallons of premium.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never bought new tires on it, but it had a TON of problems. The inside driver door panel was off for at least half the time I owned it, and I replaced almost every part in there myself. The window barely worked. I ended up using a zip tie to solder a piece of plastic together inside the door. The BMW and Porsche I had might have been lemons, It needed some engine work before I tried selling it private party, then ended up trading it in on this…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;8-2016-chevrolet-corvette&quot;&gt;8. 2016 Chevrolet Corvette&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $40,000 / 44,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: Not yet, keeping at least 4 years!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 23/32+, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $110/mo for excellent coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 6.2L 8-cylinder, 455HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: None yet&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: ~$2,500&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/vette.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Corvette&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Newest car and by far the most expensive car I’ve ever owned. Something about lifestyle creep… I got a 1.49% interest rate 48 month car loan on a USED car. Found this 1-owner, higher mileage C7 Corvette at a dealer. It was the exact combo I wanted, blue exterior and brown/tan interior, 2LT, manual transmission. It was Certified Pre-Owned, so it has free oil changes and services for a few years, plus it was a better price than any 2016 for sale in the country at the time. I haggled for a while, got up to leave a few times, and got about 3k off the dealer price and got more than I paid for my BMW on trade in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 2016 came with a front camera so you don’t hit the front bumper parking, and a flat bottom steering wheel. This is such a nice car, and I’m making some money on the side &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/rent-other-peoples-cars-with-turo/&quot;&gt;renting it with Turo&lt;/a&gt;. I was really tired of how expensive the BMW was and how unreliable it was, so I was happy to pay a premium to get into a reliable American car again. Plus it has cylinder deactivation to run on 4-cylinders when you want to, which helped me get 36 MPG on a road trip to Tampa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An update on my Vette for 2019: I’ve put 12,000 miles on it this year, and it’s gotten an oil change and new O2 sensors under warranty. Great, reliable car! I’ve also made almost $1,500 renting it on &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/rent-other-peoples-cars-with-turo/&quot;&gt;Turo!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;9-2007-lexus-gx470&quot;&gt;9. 2007 Lexus GX470&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $10,000 / 145,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: Not yet, and not planning on selling&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 15/19, any gas, I still use premium&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $80/mo for excellent coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 4.7L 8-cylinder, 270HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: None yet, but I’ll do them myself&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $1,700&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/lexus.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;GX470&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We needed something larger than a Corvette or Fiat to move our dogs around and do more home improvement projects, so I wanted to get something reliable SUV that would last a very long time. I did my research and decided on a Toyota 4Runner, with leather and a V8. So the 4th generation (2003-2009) Toyota 4Runner V8 Limited. Unfortunately, those are rare, and relatively expensive. Then I found out that Lexus made the same car, with more factory options and it’s even nicer than the 4Runner, has a V8, leather, and it sells for less than a V8 Limited 4Runner. That sold me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was originally planning to buy a 2003 model in Pennsylvania for $5,000, but it had rust, was a little rough, and the owner was seeming like he was never going to deliver it. I was paying him to drive it down, but he flaked on me 3 separate times. I had searches set up on every website you can think of, and not many come up for sale. One ended up showing up in Melbourne, FL, where I live, for 10k. It was more than I was wanting to spend, but it was much lower miles, newer, and nicer than I was planning on buying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was this one that I bought. I was going to go look at it, so I scheduled and appointment with this local car dealer for the next day. They called me that day and said the car had already sold, pending financing. Oh well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They called me back another day later and said financing fell through, so I went down that day and bought it, putting almost $7k of the purchase on a Capital One Venture card to get a signing bonus! This car was nearly perfect, super low miles for the model, recent maintenance on the timing belt and water pump, new battery, tires, brakes - it needs nothing. I got this car for below market (the car would’ve sold the next day if I didn’t buy it), and I plan on driving it until it dies. This is a car that needs very little maintenance since it’s a Toyota, it’ll run 3,4,500k miles, and I’m already loving it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So those are the cars I’ve owned, and the details on how much they cost to buy and own. Do you have any good stories about cars and how they effected your financial plans? Leave them in the comments!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">2019 Goals</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019-Goals/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2019 Goals" /><published>2019-01-02T07:00:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-02T07:00:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019-Goals</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019-Goals/">&lt;p&gt;Here are my goals for 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;financial&quot;&gt;Financial&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Max out my Roth IRA ($6k)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Max out my fiancés Roth IRA ($6k)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Max out my 401k ($19k)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Keep 5k in an Ally Emergency Fund&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have 35k saved in taxable investment accounts for a down payment on our next house&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reach a Net Worth of 330k&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have a total of 110k invested in retirement accounts&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have a total of 150k invested in everything&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Roll over HSA to Fidelity. I’ll be married in 2019, and we’re getting better health insurance, so I lose access to my HSA. The existing HSA will charge high fees if I’m not contributing to it, so I’m moving it to a no-fee Fidelity HSA.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t buy a car&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;house&quot;&gt;House&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Redo Closet in Owen’s Room&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Finish second bathroom renovation (shower, floors)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Finish master closet&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Paint outside of house&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grow grass in side yard&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Redo gutters by the side yard&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Start composting&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Redo lavender garden, maybe move a fruit tree from the back to here&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add a front garden&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rip out grass around fruit trees and add soil/composting&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pressure wash pool area&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Redo the kitchen. This is an expensive one that I hope to get to this year, it was also on my list for last year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;education&quot;&gt;Education&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pass 2 Georgia Tech classes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get Elizabeth and my college diplomas framed&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Obtain a AWS Professional level Certification&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;other&quot;&gt;Other&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get married&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Weight down to 185&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Beat Final Fantasy 9&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Go to Costa Rica on a Honeymoon&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Recycle plastic bags&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Read Freakonomics&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Read Millionaire Next Door&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Read Phoenix Project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Here are my goals for 2019.</summary></entry></feed>