<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-01-03T10:51:10-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Robert Skelton</title><subtitle>Finance | Tech | Cars | Renovations | Recipes</subtitle><entry><title type="html">How to Drive Cool Cars on a Budget [Updated January 2019]</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/drive-cool-cars-on-a-budget/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Drive Cool Cars on a Budget [Updated January 2019]" /><published>2019-01-03T08:05:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-03T08:05:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/drive-cool-cars-on-a-budget</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/drive-cool-cars-on-a-budget/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/lexus.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Both&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of life’s biggest expenses is transportation, especially cars. I love cars, and love getting different cars. I get bored driving the same vehicle for more than a few years. You could imagine this would be expensive, but it doesn’t have to be. I’m 26 and have owned 9 cars (10 if you count my fiancés Fiat 500, not listed below), and I’ve not lost much money on them at all. The biggest downside is that you have to pay registration and taxes on every car you buy, but some of that can be tax deductible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The list that follows is all of the cars I’ve owned, how much I paid and sold them for, how many miles I put on them, and about how expensive it was to own each one. I’ve included insurance costs, city/highway MPG, and the cost of oil changes and registration so that you can see how affordable each was to own. My first 3 cars I owned in high school, so my helped me out by paying for gas, insurance, and registration. Also, 7 of these cars were Rear Wheel Drive, manual transmission cars, and I have owned two silver on black V8 automatic AWD SUVs. 6 of the 9 were American made and had no issues, and 2 were German made and had so many issues. The one Japanese car has been great so far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-1993-ford-mustang-lx&quot;&gt;1. 1993 Ford Mustang LX&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $1,700 / 195,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $1,750 / 205,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 25/30, regular gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 2.3L 4-cylinder, 100HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $30 for standard oil change, every 3,000 to 5,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/93mustang.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1993 Mustang&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This car was bought by my parents for me and my brother to learn to drive a manual transmission. I broke the clutch in it, and the A/C compressor went out in it, which cost about $600 to fix both. We owned it for a few years as an extra car, and sold it for more than we paid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-1996-ford-mustang&quot;&gt;2. 1996 Ford Mustang&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $3,600 / 118,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $2,400 / 135,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 23/28, regular gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 3.6L 6-cylinder, 150HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $30 for standard oil change, every 3,000 to 5,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/96mustang.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1996 Mustang&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was the first car I bought myself, the older, silver Mustang in the middle of the picture. I put a $70 Cold Air Intake on it. Other than that, I did no major work on the car, so it had no expenses outside of gas and oil changes. I originally sold the car for $3,200, but the buyer blew a head gasket on the way home. This really surprised me, since after I had 17,000 issue-free miles, they broke a major part in a 5 mile drive home. Since they were family friends, I took it back, and sold it as is a week later for $800 less.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-1999-chevrolet-camaro&quot;&gt;3. 1999 Chevrolet Camaro&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $4,000 / 99,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $3,600 / 115,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 22/27, regular gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 3.8L 6-cylinder, 200HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $30 for standard oil change, every 3,000 to 5,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/camaro.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1999 Camaro&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought the Camaro before heading to college as something more exciting – it had T-Tops! The picture doesn’t portray how enthralled I was. I drove this at the beginning of my college career and had no issues with it. Just a couple hundred dollars upgrading the headlights and front grill, hey, I was 18! When I sold it after a few years, I didn’t lose much money to upgrade to my next car, which was a…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;4-2004-cadillac-cts-v&quot;&gt;4. 2004 Cadillac CTS-V&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $17,800 / 49,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $13,000 / 99,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 16/23, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $120/mo for full coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 5.7L 8-cylinder, 400HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $100 for full synthetic oil change, every 10,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: Unsure, parents paid for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/ctsv.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2004 CTS-V&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought this with the money I had saved from summer jobs and my first semester of Co-oping as a Test Engineer. It came with new tires, I got one set of new tires for free a few years later from my brother (he won them), and I sold it needing new tires. The CTS-V was an amazing car: a luxury sport sedan with a Corvette Z06 engine and a 6-speed manual transmission. I loved it! However, the insurance was really high, and so were the gas costs. This was the longest I had ever owned a car, which was about 4 years. I sold it when I moved down to Florida for my first real Engineering job. I still find myself wanting a car like this again, and they are still selling used years later for the same prices. No more depreciation on these, unfortunately for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;5-2008-chevrolet-corvette&quot;&gt;5. 2008 Chevrolet Corvette&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $27,500 / 36,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $26,500 /49,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 23/30, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $90/mo for full coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 6.2L 8-cylinder, 430HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: $100 for full synthetic oil change, every 10,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $3,000&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/c6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2008 Corvette&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought the Corvette after getting my first paycheck as a full time employee after college. A bright blue Corvette with a targa top in perfect Florida weather, why not? A few months later, I was wondering how bad of a financial decision it really was. My dad and brother gave me 0% loans since I couldn’t pay for all of it at once, and I was paying them about $1,000/month to pay it off quickly. It took about 6 months to pay off. Finally selling my CTS-V really helped. I owned the Corvette for a little over a year, and luckily sold it for not much of a loss in order to pay off the down payment on my house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buying a Corvette and a house in the same year might not be the best financial decision, but it worked out for me once I sold the Vette. This was the nicest and fastest car I had owned at this point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The expenses on this were really low, since insurance is super cheap and it got relatively good MPG for a sports car. Everyone wonders how the insurance low, so think about this: Who buys a Corvette, and what do they do with them? Most Corvette owners are 60+ and retired, and they use their Corvette as a weekend car or cruiser, not a daily driver. This means they are garaged the majority of the time, and there are not very many insurance claims on them. This drives the insurance price pretty low, which was great for me! Most people in Corvette Clubs like to brag how few miles they put on their Vette, I was the opposite. I put about 13,000 miles on mine in the year I owned it, and loved every single one of them. It made me want to get back into one once I was more financially stable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;6-1999-porsche-boxster&quot;&gt;6. 1999 Porsche Boxster&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bought: $5,500 / 85,000 miles
Sold: $5,000  / 89,000 miles
MPG: 19/25, premium gas
Insurance: $50/mo for legal minimum
Engine: 2.5L 6-cylinder, 200HP
Oil Changes: $95 for full synthetic oil change, every 7,000 miles
Taxes/Registration: $500&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/boxster.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1999 Boxster&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought the Porsche as a replacement to Corvette, which I sold to pay towards the down payment on my house. The difference in selling my Corvette and buying a Porsche was over $21,000! My co-workers wondered why I “upgraded” from a Corvette to a Porsche, and their jaw dropped when they find out I only paid $6,000 after tax and registration for it. The insurance for full coverage on it was about $130/mo, which I thought was insane on a car that’s so cheap. Therefore, I just went for the legal minimum. My thoughts were that if I wreck it, I can just buy another car. I’m also quite confident in my driving abilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I called it my cheap beater Porsche, and that’s not too far off. I converted the non-functional automatic convertible top to a manually-operated top, and I just leave it down all the time. The back window was plastic that has faded to yellow, so it had terrible visibility when the top is up. I spent $50 on new tail light bulbs and a new headlight switch, since those didn’t work when I bought it. Luckily for me, I picked this up for a steal on Craigslist, and bought it the same day it was posted. I loved driving a cheap car that I don’t care about anymore! I kept this about 9 months. I put about $350 into new brakes and rotors. I did them myself, since the dealer quoted $2,700 to do it. When I sold it on eBay, it needed a new water pump, which was about $700 installed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I lost about $1,000 to drive this for close to a year, not bad. I sold it to buy my first automatic car, and first non-sports car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;7-2005-bmw-x5-48&quot;&gt;7. 2005 BMW X5 4.8&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $7,000 / 102,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: $7,005 in trade-in / 108,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 14/19, premium gas (ouch)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $67/mo for legal minimum&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 4.8L 8-cylinder, 360HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: None yet&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $700&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/x5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2005 X5&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought this awesome BMW SUV. It was $72,000 new, and I bought it for 10% of that. It was large inside, had a panoramic sunroof, Bluetooth, and heated seats in the front and back. Perfect for Florida! It came with huge 20″ rims that are 315 in the back. I got lots of compliments on the wheels. The car was enjoyable to drive, the A/C was so cold, and it felt like it owned the road. It’s not a sports car, but it’ll scoot. 360HP in this SUV is no slouch. It’s got torque to tow as well. The gas mileage is horrific on this car, and it holds 25 gallons of premium.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never bought new tires on it, but it had a TON of problems. The inside driver door panel was off for at least half the time I owned it, and I replaced almost every part in there myself. The window barely worked. I ended up using a zip tie to solder a piece of plastic together inside the door. The BMW and Porsche I had might have been lemons, It needed some engine work before I tried selling it private party, then ended up trading it in on this…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;8-2016-chevrolet-corvette&quot;&gt;8. 2016 Chevrolet Corvette&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $40,000 / 44,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: Not yet, keeping at least 4 years!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 23/32+, premium gas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $110/mo for excellent coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 6.2L 8-cylinder, 455HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: None yet&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: ~$2,500&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/vette.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Corvette&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Newest car and by far the most expensive car I’ve ever owned. Something about lifestyle creep… I got a 1.49% interest rate 48 month car loan on a USED car. Found this 1-owner, higher mileage C7 Corvette at a dealer. It was the exact combo I wanted, blue exterior and brown/tan interior, 2LT, manual transmission. It was Certified Pre-Owned, so it has free oil changes and services for a few years, plus it was a better price than any 2016 for sale in the country at the time. I haggled for a while, got up to leave a few times, and got about 3k off the dealer price and got more than I paid for my BMW on trade in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 2016 came with a front camera so you don’t hit the front bumper parking, and a flat bottom steering wheel. This is such a nice car, and I’m making some money on the side &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/rent-other-peoples-cars-with-turo/&quot;&gt;renting it with Turo&lt;/a&gt;. I was really tired of how expensive the BMW was and how unreliable it was, so I was happy to pay a premium to get into a reliable American car again. Plus it has cylinder deactivation to run on 4-cylinders when you want to, which helped me get 36 MPG on a road trip to Tampa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An update on my Vette for 2019: I’ve put 12,000 miles on it this year, and it’s gotten an oil change and new O2 sensors under warranty. Great, reliable car! I’ve also made almost $1,500 renting it on &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/rent-other-peoples-cars-with-turo/&quot;&gt;Turo!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;9-2007-lexus-gx470&quot;&gt;9. 2007 Lexus GX470&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bought: $10,000 / 145,000 miles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold: Not yet, and not planning on selling&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MPG: 15/19, any gas, I still use premium&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance: $80/mo for excellent coverage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engine: 4.7L 8-cylinder, 270HP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oil Changes: None yet, but I’ll do them myself&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxes/Registration: $1,700&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cars/lexus.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;GX470&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We needed something larger than a Corvette or Fiat to move our dogs around and do more home improvement projects, so I wanted to get something reliable SUV that would last a very long time. I did my research and decided on a Toyota 4Runner, with leather and a V8. So the 4th generation (2003-2009) Toyota 4Runner V8 Limited. Unfortunately, those are rare, and relatively expensive. Then I found out that Lexus made the same car, with more factory options and it’s even nicer than the 4Runner, has a V8, leather, and it sells for less than a V8 Limited 4Runner. That sold me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was originally planning to buy a 2003 model in Pennsylvania for $5,000, but it had rust, was a little rough, and the owner was seeming like he was never going to deliver it. I was paying him to drive it down, but he flaked on me 3 separate times. I had searches set up on every website you can think of, and not many come up for sale. One ended up showing up in Melbourne, FL, where I live, for 10k. It was more than I was wanting to spend, but it was much lower miles, newer, and nicer than I was planning on buying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was this one that I bought. I was going to go look at it, so I scheduled and appointment with this local car dealer for the next day. They called me that day and said the car had already sold, pending financing. Oh well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They called me back another day later and said financing fell through, so I went down that day and bought it, putting almost $7k of the purchase on a Capital One Venture card to get a signing bonus! This car was nearly perfect, super low miles for the model, recent maintenance on the timing belt and water pump, new battery, tires, brakes - it needs nothing. I got this car for below market (the car would’ve sold the next day if I didn’t buy it), and I plan on driving it until it dies. This is a car that needs very little maintenance since it’s a Toyota, it’ll run 3,4,500k miles, and I’m already loving it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So those are the cars I’ve owned, and the details on how much they cost to buy and own. Do you have any good stories about cars and how they effected your financial plans? Leave them in the comments!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">2019 Goals</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019-Goals/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2019 Goals" /><published>2019-01-02T07:00:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-02T07:00:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019-Goals</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019-Goals/">&lt;p&gt;Here are my goals for 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;financial&quot;&gt;Financial&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Max out my Roth IRA ($6k)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Max out my fiancés Roth IRA ($6k)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Max out my 401k ($19k)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Keep 5k in an Ally Emergency Fund&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have 35k saved in taxable investment accounts for a down payment on our next house&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reach a Net Worth of 330k&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have a total of 110k invested in retirement accounts&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have a total of 150k invested in everything&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Roll over HSA to Fidelity. I’ll be married in 2019, and we’re getting better health insurance, so I lose access to my HSA. The existing HSA will charge high fees if I’m not contributing to it, so I’m moving it to a no-fee Fidelity HSA.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t buy a car&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;house&quot;&gt;House&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Redo Closet in Owen’s Room&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Finish second bathroom renovation (shower, floors)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Finish master closet&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Paint outside of house&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grow grass in side yard&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Redo gutters by the side yard&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Start composting&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Redo lavender garden, maybe move a fruit tree from the back to here&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add a front garden&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rip out grass around fruit trees and add soil/composting&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pressure wash pool area&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Redo the kitchen. This is an expensive one that I hope to get to this year, it was also on my list for last year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;education&quot;&gt;Education&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pass 2 Georgia Tech classes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get Elizabeth and my college diplomas framed&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Obtain a AWS Professional level Certification&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;other&quot;&gt;Other&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get married&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Weight down to 185&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Beat Final Fantasy 9&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Go to Costa Rica on a Honeymoon&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Recycle plastic bags&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Read Freakonomics&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Read Millionaire Next Door&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Read Phoenix Project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Here are my goals for 2019.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">2018 Goals Revisited</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018-Goals-Revisited/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2018 Goals Revisited" /><published>2019-01-01T07:00:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-01T07:00:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018-Goals-Revisited</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018-Goals-Revisited/">&lt;p&gt;I keep track of some short term and long term goals using checklists in Google Keep. Here is a recap of my goals for 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;financial&quot;&gt;Financial&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Max out my Roth IRA ($5.5k) - PASS.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Max out my fiancés Roth IRA ($5.5k) - FAIL, we set up an auto-contribution, but ended up about 1k short. We still have until April to finish this goal, which we will.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Max out my 401k ($18.5k) - PASS, or really close.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Max out my HSA ($3.45k) - PASS&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Keep 3k in an Ally Emergency Fund - FAIL, I had more than 3k in there multiple times but I always take it out. I use my emergency fund different than most.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have 30k saved in taxable investment accounts for a down payment on our next house - FAIL, reached 19k.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reach a Net Worth of 260k - FAIL. I hit 259.5k in June! The market fluctuated so much that I ended the year with about 255k.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have a total of 100k invested - PASS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;house&quot;&gt;House&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/pool-enclosure-replacement/&quot;&gt;Fix Pool Cage&lt;/a&gt; - PASS&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Redo Owen’s Room - PASS. One of my roommates finally moved out, so we redid that room. It was pretty disgusting. About $600 in materials and some sweat and it looks amazing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Redo the kitchen - FAIL. This one is going to be expensive and I hope to get it done by the end of 2019. I did buy a much needed new fridge!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Finish master bathroom - PASS. We installed new floors, vanity, tub, toilet, shower, etc. It’s nice.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Finish master closet - FAIL. The layout of the small master closet kinda stinks, so I want to redo the shelving.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/$500-bathroom-remodel/&quot;&gt;Finish 2nd bathroom&lt;/a&gt; - FAIL. We painted the cabinets and walls and put in a new mirror and fixtures, but have yet to do the floors or shower. That is a priority in 2019.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Paint outside of house - FAIL. I got lots of free exterior paint but never got the drive to actually complete this.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Landscaping - FAIL. I put in some fruit trees and a lavender garden, but I need to put in tons more work outside.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;education&quot;&gt;Education&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A in Educational Technology in Spring 2018 at Georgia Tech - PASS&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A in Machine Learning for Trading in Summer 2018 at Georgia Tech - FAIL, I dropped the summer course because of the rigor.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A in Health Informations in Fall 2018 at Georgia Tech - FAIL, I got a B. I’ll take it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get Elizabeth and my college diplomas framed - FAIL. It would take me an hour at Michaels and a few hundred bucks, but I haven’t done it still.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Obtain the AWS SysOps Administrator Certification - PASS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;other&quot;&gt;Other&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Weight down to 200 - PASS, we started on the keto diet and I dropped from 220 to 195.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reach 125 of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.beeradvocate.com/lists/top/&quot;&gt;Top 250 Beers on Beer Advocate&lt;/a&gt; - FAIL, I was at 102 at the start of the year, and they changed their algorithm. I ended up with about 90.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Go to church - FAIL, we went 3 or 4 times.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get engaged - PASS&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/category/cars/&quot;&gt;Get a newer car&lt;/a&gt; - PASS…twice. I bought a 2016 Corvette and a 2007 Lexus GX470.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I keep track of some short term and long term goals using checklists in Google Keep. Here is a recap of my goals for 2018.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 LED Interior Lights</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Lexus-GX470-LED-Interior-Lights/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 LED Interior Lights" /><published>2018-12-13T11:00:14-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-13T11:00:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Lexus-GX470-LED-Interior-Lights</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Lexus-GX470-LED-Interior-Lights/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/both.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Both&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently got another car, my &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/drive-cool-cars-on-a-budget/&quot;&gt;10th car ever&lt;/a&gt;. It’s a 2007 Lexus GX470, basically a nicer 4Runner with leather and a V8. I chose this model specifically since it is a very reliable car, with an example of the same engine and chassis running for over &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.motoringresearch.com/car-news/man-drives-toyota-1-million-miles-9-years-gets-free-toyota/&quot;&gt;1 Million miles&lt;/a&gt;. Mine only has 145k miles. I asked for an overnight test drive, and took it to pick up a delivery of laminate floors from Lowes before I even purchased it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/lowes.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lowes&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first thing I always do to my cars is to replace all the yellow, halogen bulbs with lower power, higher output white LEDs. This makes the car look newer, and visibility is always better. The lights are all relatively easy to replace, you just need a small flat head screwdriver. Note that I did blow a fuse changing the vanity lights, and had to replace a 10A fuse in the fuse box located under the hood. You won’t have to do that if you don’t short the connection, so use something plastic instead of metal to remove those bulbs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a list of lights I used:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2S3FE8J&quot;&gt;Map Lights: BA9S x2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2UQpLoh&quot;&gt;Vanity Lights: 30mm festoon, thin x2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2S6HvcZ&quot;&gt;Courtesy Lights: 194 x4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2S6HvcZ&quot;&gt;Step Rail Lights: 194 x4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2S6HvcZ&quot;&gt;License Plate Lights: 194 x2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2SaufEu&quot;&gt;Overhead Lights in Rear and Middle Seats: 31mm festoon x2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Courtesy Lights
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/courtesy.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Courtesy Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;License Plate Lights
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/license.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;License Plate Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step Rail Lights, before and after
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/step.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Step Rail Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Map Lights, before and after
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/map.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Map Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To replace the license plate lights, I had to take the rear door off. When I bought it, the handle on the inside of that door was broken, so I made a new one. I’ve seen some posts on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/LexusGXOR/&quot;&gt;GXOR&lt;/a&gt;, a great resource for Lexus GX mods, that involve making a new strap from a NATO bracelet or similar. I did similar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/reardooroff.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Door Off&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took a rope that we used to use for our hammock and cut it into 3 pieces. I braided it, tight, then ran it through the back. It’s tied up with tons of electrical tape behind the door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/doorfix.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Door Fix&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/braid.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Braid&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/dooropen.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Door Open&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Front Door Remodel</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/front-door-remodel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Front Door Remodel" /><published>2018-10-17T12:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2018-10-17T12:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/front-door-remodel</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/front-door-remodel/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/frontdoor/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We finally redid our front door for good, final product above. We had taken the door off, sanded and painted it about 6 months ago, using the same color “Swimming” as our laundry room. Problem was, we used the same bucket of paint as the laundry room. Interior paint. You can guess how well that held up outside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below is the door after painting with interior paint. Notice the discoloration and bad spots. And the pups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/frontdoor/0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I bought the house, the door was pink/mauve. This is a picture from when I bought the house, the only picture I have of the front door. We originally redid it with new paint, weatherstripping, and hardware, but then had to repaint for good. That interior paint was not going to last on the door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/frontdoor/before.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We re-did the whole thing - took the door off the hinges, took off the hardware, sanded, sanded, sanded. You can see all of the different layers: wood, pink/mauve from before, primer, and the interior Swimming paint. We took off different levels in different spots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/frontdoor/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/frontdoor/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/frontdoor/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I then applied 4 coats of EXTERIOR Swimming - same color, but better for outdoor use. It’ll hold up much better this time. It looks much lighter with the direct light in the garage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/frontdoor/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/frontdoor/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Keto Cookie Dough Balls</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/keto-cookie-dough-balls/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Keto Cookie Dough Balls" /><published>2018-09-13T11:10:14-04:00</published><updated>2018-09-13T11:10:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/keto-cookie-dough-balls</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/keto-cookie-dough-balls/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/recipes/keto-cookie-dough.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ingredients&quot;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 stick butter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1/2 cup Keto confectioners sugar, I use Swerve&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1/2 tsp salt&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1/2 tsp vanilla extract&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 cups almond flour&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1/2 cup Dark chocolate chips (or more), I use Hershey’s Dark Chocolate Morsels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;instructions&quot;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get your butter to room temperature. I microwave it for 5 seconds on each side.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Put butter in a stand mixer and beat.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;While still beating, add confectioners sugar, salt, and vanilla extract.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;While still beating, add in almond flour, 1/2 cup at a time.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;While still beating, add in dark chocolate chips.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Roll into balls and refrigerate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;considerations&quot;&gt;Considerations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do NOT use Coconut Flour. I tried using 1 for 1 coconut flour instead of almond flour, it was like eating a desert. Not a typo. A desert.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;makes-23-cookie-dough-balls&quot;&gt;Makes ~23 cookie dough balls&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;total-net-carbs-72g&quot;&gt;Total Net Carbs: 72g&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;total-carbs-per-serving-3g&quot;&gt;Total Carbs per Serving: 3g&lt;/h3&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Using Ebates for More Cash Back</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/using-ebates-for-more-cashback/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Using Ebates for More Cash Back" /><published>2018-09-12T12:05:14-04:00</published><updated>2018-09-12T12:05:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/using-ebates-for-more-cashback</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/using-ebates-for-more-cashback/">&lt;p&gt;I started using &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ebates.com/r/ROBERT47769?eeid=28187&quot;&gt;Ebates&lt;/a&gt; in February 2017, when I really started putting lots of money into &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/category/renovations&quot;&gt;renovating&lt;/a&gt; my house. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ebates.com/r/ROBERT47769?eeid=28187&quot;&gt;Ebates&lt;/a&gt; is a website and browser extension (I have it installed as a Chrome extension). When you go to a website, it’ll pop up if you can buy things and get cash back. You simply click “Activate X% Cash Back”, and you earn money in your &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ebates.com/r/ROBERT47769?eeid=28187&quot;&gt;Ebates&lt;/a&gt; account. The amount of cash back per store varies. After you earn $25, they direct deposit your money to your Paypal, or send you a “Big Fat Check”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/ebates/udemy.png&quot; alt=&quot;Ebates&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the last 1.5 years or so of using this browser extension, I’ve earned $226.70. Yeah. The main cash back has come from home improvement websites like Lowe’s and Home Depot, where I order online and pick up in store, or get items delivered if they’re big, like a vanity. Note that Home Depot no longer participates in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ebates.com/r/ROBERT47769?eeid=28187&quot;&gt;Ebates&lt;/a&gt;, but they usually still have lower prices than Lowes in my area.  I have also earned a few bucks back from Udemy, where I buy training in order to get better at &lt;a href=&quot;https://linkedin.com/in/robertjskelton&quot;&gt;my job&lt;/a&gt;. I highly recommend the Acloudguru courses on Udemy if you work in any type of Cloud Architecture role. I even earned some cash back on buying my &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/optimize-everything/&quot;&gt;Chinese Roomba&lt;/a&gt; and on purchasing a refund from TaxAct!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/ebates/ebates.png&quot; alt=&quot;Ebates&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d highly recommend signing up for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ebates.com/r/ROBERT47769?eeid=28187&quot;&gt;Ebates&lt;/a&gt; if you do much online shopping, it’ll save you a bit more money, plus you can keep your Ebates cash along with your credit card cash back!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I started using Ebates in February 2017, when I really started putting lots of money into renovating my house. Ebates is a website and browser extension (I have it installed as a Chrome extension). When you go to a website, it’ll pop up if you can buy things and get cash back. You simply click “Activate X% Cash Back”, and you earn money in your Ebates account. The amount of cash back per store varies. After you earn $25, they direct deposit your money to your Paypal, or send you a “Big Fat Check”.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Vanity Drains Replaced with Pop Up Drains</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/vanity-drains-replaced/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vanity Drains Replaced with Pop Up Drains" /><published>2018-09-10T12:05:14-04:00</published><updated>2018-09-10T12:05:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/vanity-drains-replaced</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/vanity-drains-replaced/">&lt;p&gt;I replaced 2 drains on my master vanity with &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2x1YWCt&quot;&gt;pop up drains&lt;/a&gt;. The vanity I installed does not have the lever to pull up and down the stopper in the drain, so this style is a functional way to have working stoppers. Previously, I had normal drains, and I could not put the stopper down. They were attempted to be pushed down by a few guests, and eventually broke, so I decided to finally replace them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/drains/before.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Drains&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, I took the old drains out and cleaned the sink bottom, where the new drains would be installed. A lesson learned here is to clean the opening more than you think you should. It took me about 5 installs to get both drains working with no leaks, and each time I found more and more gunk to be cleaned. I’d recommend using an old, heavy towel or t-shirt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/drains/drain_removed.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Drains&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/drains/bottom_removed.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Drains&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The install process of the new drain was pretty simple, I would recommend using &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2O3S4M8&quot;&gt;plumbers tape&lt;/a&gt;. I didn’t do this the first few attempts, and it lead to leaking. The new stopper works by pressing down on the top, and it latches closed. To open, just tap again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/drains/after_up.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Drains&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/drains/after_middle.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Drains&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/drains/after_down.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Drains&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/drains/bottom_after.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Drains&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I replaced 2 drains on my master vanity with pop up drains. The vanity I installed does not have the lever to pull up and down the stopper in the drain, so this style is a functional way to have working stoppers. Previously, I had normal drains, and I could not put the stopper down. They were attempted to be pushed down by a few guests, and eventually broke, so I decided to finally replace them!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Matching Your Net Worth with Your Lifetime Earnings</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/matching-your-net-worth-with-your-lifetime-earnings/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Matching Your Net Worth with Your Lifetime Earnings" /><published>2018-08-10T12:05:14-04:00</published><updated>2018-08-10T12:05:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/matching-your-net-worth-with-your-lifetime-earnings</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/matching-your-net-worth-with-your-lifetime-earnings/">&lt;p&gt;A cool metric to track your net worth is against your lifetime earnings, of which you can pull from your social security income. I first heard of this from &lt;a href=&quot;https://retireby40.org/your-lifetime-wealth-ratio/&quot;&gt;Retire By 40&lt;/a&gt;, which he calls your Lifetime Wealth Ratio. Basically, it’s a way to how well you are investing, or if you’re overspending. I decided to run mine and see!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;social-security-earnings&quot;&gt;Social Security Earnings&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can get your social security earnings from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ssa.gov/&quot;&gt;Social Security website&lt;/a&gt;, which I signed up for a few years ago, and my figures are below. Note that I worked at a water treatment plant making $8/hr in the summers of 2008, 2009, and 2010. In 2011, 2012 and 2013 I worked 3-5 months per year at an engineering co-op, earning $15.50-$18/hr. I didn’t work in 2014 (still in college), then started my first professional job in May 2015. I switched jobs for a 35% raise in February 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/ss/ss_income.png&quot; alt=&quot;Social Security&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So 2008 to 2017, I made $209,044. Added in with my latest paycheck (August 2018), I’ve made $48,305 this year. This brings my lifetime total to $257,349.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;current-net-worth&quot;&gt;Current Net Worth&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/ss/pc.png&quot; alt=&quot;Networth&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My current net worth is $254,500 (tracked with &lt;a href=&quot;http://share.personalcapital.com/x/psOnBl&quot;&gt;Personal Capital&lt;/a&gt;), which means I’m $2,805 BEHIND my Social Security reported income. However, I’m at a &lt;strong&gt;98.9% ratio of net worth to lifetime income&lt;/strong&gt;, which is pretty good at age 26.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how&quot;&gt;How?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main reason my ratio is this high is because of my great single real estate purchase. I purchased a 4 bedroom single family home in May 2016 for $170K, which is my primary residence. I’ve had 2-3 roommates for the last few years which almost cover my mortgage, which was a 15 year mortgage with 20% down. The house has also appreciated to about $250K, thanks to a strong market and lots of sweat equity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d also like to acknowledge how my family has helped. My dad gave me $5K to help on the down payment on my house, and loaned me $30K to pay back as I could. I paid it back in less than 6 months after &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/drive-cool-cars-on-a-budget/&quot;&gt;downgrading my car&lt;/a&gt; and putting every penny towards it. I also recently received a $25K life insurance check from my grandfather passing. 100% of that was put into investments and savings. Both of these benefits gave me a head start, and its something I’m very thankful for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I’m doing pretty well at &lt;strong&gt;98.9%&lt;/strong&gt; of my lifetime earnings still attributed to me in assets, investments, or cash. How are you doing?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">A cool metric to track your net worth is against your lifetime earnings, of which you can pull from your social security income. I first heard of this from Retire By 40, which he calls your Lifetime Wealth Ratio. Basically, it’s a way to how well you are investing, or if you’re overspending. I decided to run mine and see!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Simple Guide to Raising Your Credit Score</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/simple-guide-to-raising-your-credit-score/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Simple Guide to Raising Your Credit Score" /><published>2018-07-26T10:15:14-04:00</published><updated>2018-07-26T10:15:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/simple-guide-to-raising-your-credit-score</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/simple-guide-to-raising-your-credit-score/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/credit/all.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;All&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the last year, I’ve helped my fiancé raise her credit score from ~580 to ~720, and my credit score is over 800. Credit scores are a number that lenders take into account when offering you loans, and can make a huge difference when buying a house. A high credit score will get you a lower interest rate, which can add up to tens of thousands of dollars over the life of a mortgage. It takes time to increase your credit score, but it is very simple to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Credit scores take into account many things, but one of the most important and easiest to change is credit utilization, which is how much you’ve spent vs how much you have available. The goal is to decrease the amount you owe, and increase the amount you can borrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Sign up for a credit monitoring service.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recommend &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.creditkarma.com&quot;&gt;CreditKarma&lt;/a&gt; since it is 100% free and updates every two weeks. Lots of credit cards will provide credit scores and monitoring as well, but I still use &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.creditkarma.com&quot;&gt;CreditKarma&lt;/a&gt;. The goal is to see what lines of credit you have open, and things you can do to improve your credit score. When checking my fiancé’s, we found out she was an Authorized User on one of her parents cards with high utilization. We got her parents to remove her from that, which helped decrease the overall utilization of her lines of credit, which helped increase her credit score. You might find something on your credit report you did not know about!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/credit/score.png&quot; alt=&quot;Score&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Start getting Credit Cards&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re just starting out with credit, you’ll want no annual fee, easy to obtain credit cards. The first three credit cards my fiancé got were no annual fee, easy to get, simple rewards, and we applied for them about 3-4 months apart. These 3 cards are considered some of the best beginning cards. When you get your card, setup auto-pay and link them into your &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/personal-capital-review/&quot;&gt;Personal Capital&lt;/a&gt; account, which is also highly recommended.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/credit/big3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Big 3&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.referyourchasecard.com/2/G2SA4SQQGR&quot;&gt;Chase Freedom&lt;/a&gt; - $150 sign on bonus, 1% back on all purchases, 5% on rotating categories. My fiancé got a $1,500 line of credit on this one, her first card.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.citi.com/credit-cards/credit-card-details/citi.action?ID=citi-double-cash-credit-card&quot;&gt;Citi Double Cash&lt;/a&gt; - No sign on, but 2% back on all purchases. My fiancé got a $1,200 line of credit on this one, her second card, so now she had $2,700 of total credit.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://refer.discover.com/s/zmk6g&quot;&gt;Discover IT&lt;/a&gt; - $50 sign on bonus, 1% back on all purchases and 5% on rotating categories, just like the Chase Freedom, HOWEVER! Your first year, Discover matches all your cash back, which effectively makes this a 2% everything, 10% rotating categories card for 1 year. My fiancé got a $5,500 line of credit on this one, her third card, so now she has $8,200 of total credit.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note that her total credit available is increasing substantially, but her spending stays about the same. If she spent $1,000/mo, with her only 1 credit card, she is using $1,000 / $1,500, or ~67% of her total credit. Now that she has 3 cards and more available credit, her new credit utilization is $1,000 / $8,200, or just 12% of her credit. It’s best to keep this number as low as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Other Things&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keep your Cards Open&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should always keep your no-annual fee credit cards open, even if you stop using them, since it will increase the average credit line age. One of my favorite cards, the Sallie Mae Barclaycard, removed the majority of good cash back benefits from the card. I still have the card open, but haven’t spent a penny on it since then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be reasonable when applying for new cards.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t apply for credit cards you don’t think you’ll get approved for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keep Tabs on Your Spending&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Always track your cards, in &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/personal-capital-review/&quot;&gt;Personal Capital&lt;/a&gt; or in Mint. You can see some of my cards and their credit limits below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/credit/pc.png&quot; alt=&quot;Credit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bills in Your Name&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some other things you can do to increase your credit is to have utility bills in your name, so if you’re renting a house, put the utilities in your name. Always set up auto-pay to make sure your bills are paid in full, every month. Months and years of no missed payments will help your credit as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you start getting into the world of Annual Fee cards and churning, this guide might not be for you. :) For further reading see, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/churning&quot;&gt;/r/churning&lt;/a&gt;, this is for those who don’t mind juggling 20+ cards to gain tons of airline miles and points, not for the faint of heart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These simple steps will help get your credit score up and will save you money when applying for loans that matter, such as car and home loans. My 800+ credit score helped me secure a low mortgage rate (3.25%) and a low car loan rate (1.49%). A high credit score will save you money over time, and is simple to get high and keep high.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any other tips? Leave them in the comments!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>