<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-07-10T15:48:35-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Robert Skelton</title><subtitle>Finance | Tech | Cars | Renovations | Etc</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Pros and Cons of Working From Home</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Pros-and-Cons-of-Working-From-Home/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pros and Cons of Working From Home" /><published>2019-07-10T09:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-07-10T09:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Pros-and-Cons-of-Working-From-Home</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Pros-and-Cons-of-Working-From-Home/">&lt;p&gt;I’ve been working from home full time for over 2.5 years, and it is a major benefit of my current position. Remote work offers some great benefits, but also some notable cons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;pros&quot;&gt;Pros&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.  No commute!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This saves so much time! You don’t even need a car when you have no commute, so &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/drive-cool-cars-on-a-budget/&quot;&gt;I have 2&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.  Work with dog(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife and I have 2 dogs, and I get to be at home with them all day. This means no hiring dog sitters, and our pups aren’t always bored.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/wfh/dogs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Dogs&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Make Your Office How You Like It&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought multiple computer monitors, a nice speaker system, decorated my walls, and I can light candles every day! In a shared office environment, you just get what they provide, unless you want to drag it to and from work every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/wfh/office.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Office&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Listen to music without headphones&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Music through speakers is better, and I don’t get tired of having headphones on or in my ears like I did when shared an office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Your Time is More Flexible&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can cook lunch most days and have it ready when my wife comes home from work. If I get frustrated, I can go outside, clean, or go do a load of laundry. I have the privacy to make phone calls without having to find a huddle room or empty office. I can walk out of the office, get quotes from contractors, and can run errands easier than being in a shared office. There seems to much less of a stigma of taking time off from work when you are remote, as opposed to in person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. No Dress Code&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wear gym shorts and t-shirts to work every day. This can also be a con, since I usually look like a slob. It’s also a bit backwards, since I do most of my dressing up on the weekends, when most people dress down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7. More focused working time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can get more high quality work in less hours than in a shared office since I no longer have people tapping on my shoulder for help, or co-workers stopping by to chat. There is no “office water cooler” when you work from home, which means less distractions while working. This can be a huge advantage when writing code, which is a task that requires lots of concentration, at least for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8. Work where you want&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I usually work at my office desk, where I have 3 monitors, speakers, mouse, keyboard, etc. A nice working setup. But occasionally, I’ll want to do training or take meetings and get out of that office. I can go sit in a recliner for a meeting in the living room, or sit by the pool to do some technical training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/wfh/pool.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Pool&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;cons&quot;&gt;Cons&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Cabin Fever&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t notice being cooped up inside as a negative for the first 2 years, but in the last half a year I have been getting stir crazy. I seem to leave my house once a week, and barely get outside off of my property. It has been a recent goal of mine to start getting out of the house more often. I’ve started a trivia group on Thursdays to socialize more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Hard to Shut Off Work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have work email on my phone. If I see an email at 9PM, and it is something that just takes a second to do, I’ll go over to my office and do it. Downside, I then spend another 30 minutes doing other stuff, and I never seem to truly disconnect from work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. The A/C bill&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still have to pay my own power bill, and I live in Florida. That means that if I’m not running the A/C, it will get HOT inside. I keep it at 77-78F most days, but that still adds up. It used to keep the house at 80F during work hours, before I started working here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Less Reliable Internet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corporate offices often have business internet connections, which are more reliable and quicker. I have a 150MB home internet connection, which is fast, but tends to be less reliable. I also had to supply my own internet connection hardware, like the modem and router. These are expenses I would have had normally, but when you’re home 24/7, you care more about a great internet connection than normal. Therefore, I bought a nicer, expensive router recently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Less Connected to Co-Workers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a shared office, you can walk up to your coworkers to get advice or help, and you see them in person at meeting often. In a remote work environment, I occasionally see my team members on Skype video, but it’s usually just audio. We communicate mostly via chat platforms at work, which is a bit more difficult to get things done than if you are sitting next to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Conflicting off days&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife has Tuesdays and Sundays off. I work on Tuesdays. This means that I’m at home trying to work, and she’s at home not working on Tuesdays.   I also used to have a roommate that would have every other Friday off, and I worked those Fridays. He would sit around and play video games all day, which was annoying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Snacks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This could be a pro for some, but I’m always 20 steps from my kitchen, stocked with snacks and food. And I have terrible self control with food, so I am always snacking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, the last 2.5 years working from home have been a wonderful way to work (if you have to work), and I would take remote work over an in person shared office every day. I have learned a few lessons on how to manage working from home though, like setting boundaries on when to start and stop working, how to focus more and be more productive, and to talk to your team members more, even if it is just about their personal lives. Working from home is a great move in the IT and Software disciplines, and I’d recommend employees and managers alike to give it a shot.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I’ve been working from home full time for over 2.5 years, and it is a major benefit of my current position. Remote work offers some great benefits, but also some notable cons.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Honeymoon in Costa Rica</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Honeymoon-In-Costa-Rica/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Honeymoon in Costa Rica" /><published>2019-06-18T09:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-06-18T09:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Honeymoon-In-Costa-Rica</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Honeymoon-In-Costa-Rica/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/map.png&quot; alt=&quot;Map&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife, Elizabeth, and I got married on May 26, 2019, and left for our honeymoon to Costa Rica the next day. We drove from Melbourne, FL to Ft Lauderdale, FL to fly on JetBlue. A direct flight from FLL to SJO, it was about $500 for both of us, and bags were included with my JetBlue credit card. We spent 7 days and 6 nights in Costa Rica, and visited 5 provinces: San Jose, Alajuela, Guanacaste, Heredia, and Puntarenas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/tacobell1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;TacoBell&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;rental-car&quot;&gt;Rental Car&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We rented a Toyota Land Cruise Prado (the Toyota version of my Lexus GX470) from National Rental Car in San Jose, but not at the airport. The pickup location was Hotel Marriott Costa Rica, which was about 10 minutes away from the SJO airport. We found a free shuttle from National at the rental car kiosk in the airport. If you pick up outside of the airport, you avoid a large airport pickup tax. We also used promo code “MEMPHIS” for 10% off, prepaid with a Visa Signature credit card for another 10% off, and declined the LDW insurance. Car rentals require both SLC and LDW insurance. However, you can decline the LDW if you have a credit card that covers it, and you print out and bring the credit card agreement. My Capital One Venture is a Visa Signature, so we paid with that. The Prado was awesome, and we only paid about $340 to drive it for a week. We put 850 miles on it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/prado1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Prado&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/prado2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Prado&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;day-1---san-jose&quot;&gt;Day 1 - San Jose&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Landed in San Jose, got our rental car, checked in to Apartotel La Sabana. It was so rainy, so we did nothing but get room service and stay in. This place was $76/night, and was nothing fancy. The pool looked great (but it was rainy) and there was a sauna, but the room was cramped and not great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/view2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;View&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;day-2---san-jose-to-la-paz-to-heliconias&quot;&gt;Day 2 - San Jose to La Paz to Heliconias&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Woke up and got a great Costa Rican breakfast at Apartotel La Sabana. That made the room worth it. We drove about 1.5 hours to the La Paz waterfall gardens, which was incredible. La Paz entrance was $125 for 2 people. We saw lots of birds, sloths, jungle cats, and beautiful waterfalls, and also had an awesome buffet. This might be our most recommended attraction we visited in Costa Rica.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a lot of hours here, we drove another 2 hours (stopping at McDonalds along the way) to the Heliconias Nature Lodge, and checked in to their Deluxe Treehouse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mcd1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;McDonalds&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mcd2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;McDonalds&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We ordered room service, and enjoyed the awesome room! This room at Heliconias was $270/night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lodge1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lodge&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;day-3---la-fortuna&quot;&gt;Day 3 - La Fortuna&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Woke up and had another great Costa Rican breakfast at the Heliconias Nature Lodge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lodge2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lodge&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drove in to La Fortuna and did some white water rafting with the Desafio Adventure Company down the Balsa River. Afterwards, they provided a lunch buffet at their restaurant. This trip was $150 for 2 people, which we though was a great value. The guides and the food were great!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lodge3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lodge&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lodge4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lodge&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We drove back to the Nature Lodge, relaxed a bit, then drove back in to La Fortuna to visit the EcoTermales Hot Springs. It was $80 for 2 people. We loved the hot springs, but were disappointed with the food. We paid $20 each for a below average buffet. Other than the food, the hot springs were awesome. Great drinks, not too crowded, lots of hot water. Then we drove back to the Nature Lodge and went to sleep early.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/hs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ecotermales&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;day-4---la-fortuna-to-secrets&quot;&gt;Day 4 - La Fortuna to Secrets&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Woke up super early and went on a 6AM Bird Watching Tour, which cost $135 for 2 people and included some fruit. We saw lots of local birds (and dogs) and our guide was very knowledgable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/bird1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bird&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/bird2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bird&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This close up picture of a bird is a Motmot, taken on a Galaxy S8 through a monocular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/bird3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bird&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, we had another Costa Rican breakfast at Heliconias Nature Lodge. The staff here was super friendly. We checked out of this hotel and drove to the La Fortuna Waterfall. It was a ton of stairs to get there, but it was beautiful. It poured here, but luckily not until we were about ready to leave. The waterfall entrance was $36 for 2 people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lafortuna1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;La Fortuna&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lafortuna2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;La Fortuna&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lafortuna3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;La Fortuna&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lafortuna4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;La Fortuna&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then we drove to the Mistico Arenal Hanging Bridges Park. This place was actually closed for bad weather when we got there, so we got some food at their restaurant, and they opened about 30 minutes later. There are lots of hanging suspension bridges, great views of the Arenal volcano, and wildlife. It involved lots of hiking. We were already pretty exhausted from all the walking and hiking we had done the last few days, so we didn’t even see the whole park. We did see coati though, which we had never seen before! Mistico was $80 for 2 people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mistico1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mistico&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mistico2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mistico&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mistico3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mistico&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mistico4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mistico&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mistico5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mistico&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mistico6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mistico&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mistico7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mistico&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, we drove to the Secrets Papagayo resort, about a 3 hour drive. Google Maps sent us down this insane mud road that was about 60 degrees uphill. Our car could handle it, but I could not. We turned around and took a detour, which added about 30 minutes. We got to our resort pretty late at night, and checked in to our room. They had prepped it for our honeymoon, with a sign and a bottle of champage!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/secrets1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Secrets1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;day-5---secrets&quot;&gt;Day 5 - Secrets&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This all inclusive resort was full of other couples on their honeymoons, and that was about it. Everyone had a honeymoon on their door! It was $430/night for 2 people, and of course included all of our food and drinks. So that’s what we did. We ate and drank and sat by the pool. We ordered room service, like 5 times. Then we went to their spa that night, my first time at a spa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/secrets2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Secrets1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/secrets3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Secrets1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/secrets4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Secrets1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/secrets5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Secrets1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;day-6---drive-back-to-san-jose&quot;&gt;Day 6 - Drive back to San Jose&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We just drove from Secrets back to San Jose this day. We stopped at another Taco Bell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/tacobell2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;TacoBell&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We stayed at the AC Hotel, which my Dad bought for us as a gift using points. Well, he is some sort of fancy membership level at Marriott, so they upgraded us to their penthouse suite and gave us free breakfast! It was probably one of the coolest hotel rooms we’ve every stayed in. It had a bedroom, living room, kitchen, 1.5 baths, and the biggest master bathroom I’ve ever been in. We walked around the area that the hotel was in, which is a new upscale shopping area. They also had a Lexus dealer with a LFA in stock. We ate dinner at PF Chang’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/sanjose1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Jose&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/sanjose2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Jose&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/sanjose3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Jose&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/sanjose4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Jose&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;day-7---return-home&quot;&gt;Day 7 - Return home&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The breakfast buffet at the AC Hotel was great. We checked out of the hotel late, dropped off the car at National, then got a ride on their shuttle to the airport. We ate at Smashburger, which was crazy expensive. Like $20 for a burger. We also tried a few local beers in the airport. Landed in FLL later, then drove back to Melbourne to get a few hours sleep before work the next day!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/sanjose5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Jose&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/beer.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Beer&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;other-things-to-know-about-costa-rica&quot;&gt;Other things to know about Costa Rica&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a credit card with no foreign transaction fees, we used my Capital One Venture Card for everything. The drive from Papagayo (west coast) to San Jose has toll roads you have to pay with cash. You can pay with USD and get change back in colones, the local currency. When driving, there are many 1 lane bridges. There is a sign on one side that shows which side has to yield, and the side without a yield sign gets to go without yielding. The roads are all very windy. Our rental took diesel, and all of the gas stations were not self serve. They had an attendant who would fill you up. People who work in the hospitality and tourism industry in Costa Rica are very nice and, in general, have very good English. We did not know much Spanish, but only had to bring out Google Translate once. Download Google Maps and Google Translate for offline usage fore you go if you have limited international data, like we did. We used 0MB of data the whole week, since each hotel had Wifi.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Keto Recipe Collection</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Keto-Recipe-Collection/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Keto Recipe Collection" /><published>2019-06-17T09:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-06-17T09:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Keto-Recipe-Collection</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Keto-Recipe-Collection/">&lt;p&gt;My wife and I have been doing a Keto diet for about 9 months. We have both lost over 30 pounds doing this diet. Since this involves cooking using lots of low carb recipes, I have bookmarked a large collection of recipes we like, here they are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;breakfast&quot;&gt;Breakfast&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ruled.me/jalapeno-popper-egg-cups/&quot;&gt;Jalapeño Popper Egg Cups&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;snacks&quot;&gt;Snacks&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.isavea2z.com/no-carb-cheese-wrap-folios-copycat-recipe/&quot;&gt;Cheese Wraps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wholesomeyum.com/recipes/8-ingredient-spinach-artichoke-dip-low-carb-gluten-free/&quot;&gt;Spinach Artichoke Dip&lt;/a&gt;- We dip &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KVZHVX&quot;&gt;Whisps&lt;/a&gt; into this.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ruled.me/bbq-bacon-wrapped-smokies/&quot;&gt;Bacon Wrapped Lil Smokies&lt;/a&gt; - If you omit the BBQ sauce, it has less carbs and is still great.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wholesomeyum.com/recipes/keto-low-carb-sushi-rolls-recipe-healthy/&quot;&gt;Sushi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;chicken&quot;&gt;Chicken&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://laughingspatula.com/pesto-mozzarella-and-tomato-stuffed-chicken-breasts/#wprm-recipe-container-5260&quot;&gt;Pesto Mozzarella and Tomato Stuffed Chicken Breast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.delish.com/cooking/recipe-ideas/recipes/a51442/chicken-zucchini-alfredo-recipe/&quot;&gt;Chicken Zucchini Alfredo&lt;/a&gt; - If you have a mandolin, you can cut up zucchini to make pasta that’s amazing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/b7uso3/keto_chicken_parm/&quot;&gt;Chicken Parmesan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/aktsqw/the_best_keto_butter_chicken_over_cauliflower/&quot;&gt;Indian Style Butter Chicken over Cauliflower Rice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/bnxnwj/spicy_thai_peanut_chicken/&quot;&gt;Thai Peanut Chicken&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.savorylotus.com/pesto-chicken-avocado-salad/&quot;&gt;Pesto Chicken Avocado Salad&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/a4g6iw/creamy_tuscan_chicken_with_roasted_asparagus/&quot;&gt;Tuscan Chicken&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/9ag2pw/bacon_avocado_and_chicken_sandwich/?st=JLB65CHQ&amp;amp;sh=24d06f0a&quot;&gt;Bacon, Avocado, Chicken Sandwich&lt;/a&gt; - Using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/GifRecipes/comments/9scjzq/lowcarb_keto_bagels_fathead_dough/e8nph5x/&quot;&gt;fathead buns&lt;/a&gt; recipe in the link below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;beef&quot;&gt;Beef&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.delish.com/cooking/recipe-ideas/recipes/a52731/cheese-taco-shells-recipe/&quot;&gt;Cheese Taco Shells&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lowcarbmaven.com/low-carb-taco-seasoning-keto-gluten-free/&quot;&gt;Taco Seasoning&lt;/a&gt; - Brown some beef with this and put it into those cheese taco shells, you’ve got Taco night.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/9h93rf/guacamole_bacon_burger_on_cheesebuns/&quot;&gt;Guac Bacon Burger&lt;/a&gt; - Also using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/GifRecipes/comments/9scjzq/lowcarb_keto_bagels_fathead_dough/e8nph5x/&quot;&gt;fathead buns&lt;/a&gt; recipe below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;crab&quot;&gt;Crab&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.savorytooth.com/crab-stuffed-mushrooms/&quot;&gt;Crab Stuffed Mushroom&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://lowcarbyum.com/keto-crab-cakes/&quot;&gt;Crab Cakes&lt;/a&gt; - This is our most made meal. We use Alaskan faux crab (krab), and I just brown it in a pan, no making cakes. But the combination of ingredients here is great.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;fish&quot;&gt;Fish&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dietdoctor.com/recipes/keto-thai-fish-curry-coconut&quot;&gt;Coconut Curry Thai Fish&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.allrecipes.com/recipe/228056/parmesan-crusted-tilapia-fillets/&quot;&gt;Parmesan Crusted Tilapia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;shrimp&quot;&gt;Shrimp&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://keto-daily.com/keto-sheet-pan-shrimp-recipe/?fbclid=IwAR0zDUl6Q5PvkRquoFq99Xwzjjanm02ZhBHrzbuPznWzzozyDNafztqTc1M&quot;&gt;Sheet Pan Cajun Shrimp&lt;/a&gt; - I usually add some Andouille sausage to this.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/c1mr1y/crispy_shrimp_0g_carbs/&quot;&gt;Crispy Shrimp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;other&quot;&gt;Other&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/GifRecipes/comments/9scjzq/lowcarb_keto_bagels_fathead_dough/e8nph5x/&quot;&gt;Fathead Buns&lt;/a&gt; - I make these all the time, and they taste great for a week! I usually make these into balls to make buns, instead of bagels.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://culinarylion.com/recipes/zucchini-fried-ravioli/&quot;&gt;Zucchini Fried Ravioli&lt;/a&gt; - This is our absolute favorite recipe, period. But it’s really annoying and time consuming to make, so I don’t make it often.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/409b7q/homemade_innoutinspired_animal_style_salad/&quot;&gt;In N Out Style Salad&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wholesomeyum.com/recipes/baked-healthy-buffalo-cauliflower-bites-wings-recipe/&quot;&gt;Buffalo Cauliflower Bites&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/99p88p/lasagna_stuffed_portobello_mushroom_with_bacon/&quot;&gt;Lasagna Stuffed Mushrooms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;desserts&quot;&gt;Desserts&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drdavinahseats.com/recipes/keto-mudslide&quot;&gt;Milkshake&lt;/a&gt; - My favorite keto dessert.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mooreorlesscooking.com/2015/06/17/lo-carb-pudding-dessert/&quot;&gt;Pudding&lt;/a&gt; - We make this weekly.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/9ur8un/keto_pecan_pie/&quot;&gt;Pecan Pie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/keto-cookie-dough-balls/&quot;&gt;Cookie Dough Balls&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://prettypies.com/recipe/low-carb-chocolate-pizza/&quot;&gt;Chocolate Pizza&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/bj4dtu/snickerdoodle_crepes/&quot;&gt;Snickerdoodle Crepes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/bxgfgh/peanut_butter_and_chocolate_mug_cake_no_flour/&quot;&gt;Peanut Butter and Chocolate Mug Cake&lt;/a&gt; - We use low sugar peanut butter instead of PB2.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lowcarbspark.com/keto-lava-cake/&quot;&gt;Chocolate Lava Mug Cake&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hip2keto.com/recipes/3-minute-keto-cinnamon-roll-mug-cake/&quot;&gt;Cinnamon Roll Mug Cake&lt;/a&gt; - Noticing a trend with the mug cakes?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wholesomeyum.com/recipes/low-carb-keto-cream-cheese-frosting-recipe/&quot;&gt;Cream Cheese Frosting&lt;/a&gt; - Use this frosting recipe on the cinnamon roll above.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://peaceloveandlowcarb.com/keto-pumpkin-spice-chocolate-chip-cookies/&quot;&gt;Pumpkin Spice Chocolate Chip Cookies&lt;/a&gt; - October and November only.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">My wife and I have been doing a Keto diet for about 9 months. We have both lost over 30 pounds doing this diet. Since this involves cooking using lots of low carb recipes, I have bookmarked a large collection of recipes we like, here they are.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Plasti Dip GX470 Grill</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Plasti-Dip-GX470-Grill/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Plasti Dip GX470 Grill" /><published>2019-05-07T09:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-05-07T09:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Plasti-Dip-GX470-Grill</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Plasti-Dip-GX470-Grill/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/done.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Done&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I plastidipped the grill on my Lexus GX470, and I am very happy with the results. It took about 30 minutes of active work, and about 4 hours of waiting, and this was my first time using &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2H7U2dj&quot;&gt;Plasti Dip&lt;/a&gt;. I used 1 can of black &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2H7U2dj&quot;&gt;Plasti Dip&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the full Chrome grill, before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/before.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The labor is pretty simple - remove about 10 10mm bolts around the grill, up under the hood. I also had to remove 2 bolts on the hood release that were attached. Then just slip the grill off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/back.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also removed the Lexus logo, so that it stayed chrome instead of black. I think the contrast looks better. I’ve seen some other people &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2H7U2dj&quot;&gt;Plasti Dip&lt;/a&gt; the whole grill, and it doesn’t look as good to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/back2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Lexus logo removal involved 2 Phillips screws behind the logo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/remove_logo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make sure you clean your grill really well. You don’t want any bugs or dust on the grill before starting. I applied 8 coats of &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2H7U2dj&quot;&gt;Plasti Dip&lt;/a&gt; on, with 15-30 minutes of drying in between in each coat. It was just like using spray paint. This is after 2 coats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/coat1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this is 6 coats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/coat2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And re-installed the grill! Huge improvement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/done.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Done&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My Georgia Tech OMSCS Experience So Far</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/OMSCS-Experience-So-Far/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Georgia Tech OMSCS Experience So Far" /><published>2019-04-22T09:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-04-22T09:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/OMSCS-Experience-So-Far</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/OMSCS-Experience-So-Far/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/gt/gt.png&quot; alt=&quot;GT&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was accepted to, and enrolled in, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.omscs.gatech.edu/&quot;&gt;Georgia Tech’s OMSCS&lt;/a&gt; (Online Master of Science in Computer Science) in January 2016. This post is meant as a recap as the classes I’ve taken, and my experiences throughout this program. Every class is a 3 hour credit. You need 10 classes, or 30 hours, to earn this degree, which you have to complete within 6 years of admission. There is no thesis requirement, just pass all the classes and you’ve earned the degree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I transferred in 3 hours that I didn’t use from my undergrad at Auburn. I needed 5 engineering elective hours to graduate at Auburn, and I passed 12. I had too much free time then. One class, ELEC5150-Intro to Information Security at Auburn, transferred as credit for CS6035-Intro to Information Security at Georgia Tech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I only take 1 class at a time, since I also work full time and like to do things besides be in front of the computer. I’ve dropped a few classes, and got a D in 1 class, which doesn’t count towards your graduation credits, but, unfortunately, does count towards your GPA. Anyways, here’s the classes I’ve taken, grades I earned, if I recommend the course, and my thoughts on each.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;spring-2016---cs6300---software-development-process&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6300-software-development-process&quot;&gt;Spring 2016 - CS6300 - Software Development Process&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: B&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Would recommend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a great first class to take in OMSCS. It eases you into the concept of working at your own pace, working with groups of people that you never meet in person, and the basics of using Github in a small group. I got a B, but was really close to an A. I wish I had put a little more effort into this class. Dr. Orso is a interesting professor, and you learn a bit of Java and how to build a simple Android app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;summer-2016---cs6310---software-architecture-and-design&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6310-software-architecture-design&quot;&gt;Summer 2016 - CS6310 - Software Architecture and Design&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: B&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a software architecture course. I work in cloud architecture, more along the infrastructure lines, but I didn’t learn much in this class. The lectures are boring, the content is boring… it’s just a whole course on UML.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;fall-2016---cs6250---computer-networks&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6250-computer-networks&quot;&gt;Fall 2016 - CS6250 - Computer Networks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: Dropped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is considered to be one of the easiest classes in OMSCS, but it wasn’t for me. It’s all about writing networking algorithms in Python, and it just didn’t click for me. I dropped this one pretty early.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;spring-2017---cs6475---computational-photography&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cs6475.wordpress.com/&quot;&gt;Spring 2017 - CS6475 - Computational Photography&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: D&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Advice against&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This class with Dr. Irfan Issa has been my worst Georgia Tech class, and second worse classroom experience ever (no one will ever top Dr. Baginski’s Analog Electronics at Auburn). So this class I really struggled in, but I put in a ton of effort, and expected to make a mid C. A bad grade, but at least credit towards graduation. This class is heavy on Python and matrix algebra, both topics I am not strong in. So I go into the final project with a 75, and I just have to get about a 10 (out of 100) to keep my C. One annoying thing about Dr. Issa is that he gives you the assignment file as something like final_project.pdf, and wants the deliverable to have the exact same name (final_project.pdf). You can see how this can cause issues if you’re keeping your projects in the same directory, like a logical person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I uploaded my final project after completion and did an OK job, not A material, but definitely more than a 10 material. When grades came back a few weeks later, I saw that I had a D in the class. I asked the TAs and professor why, and it was because I uploaded the final_project.pdf that was the instructions, not my actual final report. When I selected the file to upload, I was in the wrong directory. I received a 0 on the final project, they would not accept my completed final_report.pdf, and therefore I failed this class. I brought this up to Georgia Tech as a Official Grade Dispute, and it was not re-graded. My D stood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, I would recommend not taking this class unless you have a very strong interest in Computational Photography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;summer-2017---cs6400---database-systems-concepts-and-designs&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6400-database-systems-concepts-and-design&quot;&gt;Summer 2017 - CS6400 - Database Systems, Concepts and Designs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: A&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Would recommend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is another really good class, and it was nice to take a interesting class after my awful previous semester. I had considered dropping the whole program after getting a D in my previous course. In this database course, I learned a bunch, and worked with a really great group on my projects in this course. Dr. Mark is funny and keeps lectures interesting. This class also helped me in my work, as I’ve been working more with databases now than ever before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;fall-2017---none&quot;&gt;Fall 2017 - None&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UgOu1zPtW2I&quot;&gt;Why do school when you can watch football?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;spring-2018---cs6460---educational-technology&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6460-educational-technology&quot;&gt;Spring 2018 - CS6460 - Educational Technology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: A&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This class is taught by Dr. David Joyner, who is highly liked in the OMSCS community. He is a interesting professor, but this wasn’t the most interesting topic for me. This class has a decent amount of busy work, like weekly status reports and required meetings, but it made for the easiest grade in OMSCS so far. I didn’t learn a whole lot in this course, but it is a decent course and good for padding your GPA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;summer-2018---cs7646---machine-learning-for-trading&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://quantsoftware.gatech.edu/Machine_Learning_for_Trading_Course&quot;&gt;Summer 2018 - CS7646 - Machine Learning for Trading&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dropped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I signed up for this thinking it was a really interesting sounding course. The content is interesting, but it gets tough, quick. The first project was easy, then it became super difficult. The course deals with stock trading, AI, and utilizes Python, numpy, pandas, and other Python libraries. I also had a lot of things going on in my personal life, so I couldn’t devote as much time as I needed to this course, so I dropped it. Dr. Balch’s lectures are interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;fall-2018---cs6440---intro-to-health-informatics&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6440-intro-health-informatics&quot;&gt;Fall 2018 - CS6440 - Intro to Health Informatics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: B&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This class was not fun or educational for me. The class is 100% run by a TA, there is no instructor involvement. The lectures are dry, and the content is not interesting for me. You spend most of the course learning about FHIR, a healthcare API, but every time we were had an assignment to do any development with it, the API was not functioning. Luckily, you don’t have to use FHIR for your final project, and I think 0% of my class ended up using it. We were allowed to pick any healthcare related project that was given to us, and it ended up being a simple team project. I came away with a B, but was close to an A. I would not take this class again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;spring-2019---cs7646---machine-learning-for-trading&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://quantsoftware.gatech.edu/Machine_Learning_for_Trading_Course&quot;&gt;Spring 2019 - CS7646 - Machine Learning for Trading&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dropped… again&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got a promotion at work and my work load started going up, I got engaged, ended up doing more home remodeling, more car stuff, and less school. Same as the first time I took this course, the second project was overly difficult. I won’t try to take this one a 3rd time, but the content does still interest me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;summer-2019---none&quot;&gt;Summer 2019 - None&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Honeymoon for a week in Costa Rica, no way I’m doing school then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;fall-2019---cs6238---secure-computing-systems&quot;&gt;Fall 2019 - CS6238 - Secure Computing Systems&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the first time this class has been taught, so it’ll either be super easy or the worst class ever. I’ll let you know in December.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So as of April 2019, I have 18 credits out of 30. I need to pass 4 more classes by Spring 2022 in order to graduate.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">GX470 Android Headunit and Backup Camera Install</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Android-Headunit-Backup-Camera-Install/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="GX470 Android Headunit and Backup Camera Install" /><published>2019-03-07T08:00:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-03-07T08:00:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Android-Headunit-Backup-Camera-Install</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Android-Headunit-Backup-Camera-Install/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/backup.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I installed a new Android headunit in my 2007 Lexus GX470, complete with a reverse activated backup camera. The install took about 5 hours over the course of a few days, and here is how I did it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;parts-needed&quot;&gt;Parts Needed:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aliexpress.com/item/9-inch-car-radio-for-Toyota-Prado-120-2004-2009-Quadcore-Android-6-0-car/32801839608.html?spm=2114.search0104.3.24.5edff7d9xxAsrB&amp;amp;ws_ab_test=searchweb0_0,searchweb201602_1_10065_10068_10130_10890_10547_319_10546_317_10548_10545_10696_453_10084_454_10083_433_10618_10307_537_536_10902_10059_10884_10887_321_322_10103,searchweb201603_6,ppcSwitch_0&amp;amp;algo_expid=c0b5c1d2-1f43-48c9-8027-ff2257719e95-3&amp;amp;algo_pvid=c0b5c1d2-1f43-48c9-8027-ff2257719e95&amp;amp;transAbTest=ae803_5&quot;&gt;9 inch Android Headunit with Canbus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2XJWMnt&quot;&gt;Backup Camera&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2EL3NLR&quot;&gt;Bluetooth OBDII Adapter (optional)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/parts.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So ordering the headunit is a little sketchy. It’s from Aliexpress in China, and will take 2-4 weeks to arrive. This one comes with external GPS, microphone, a WiFi antenna, works with the existing aux input, and has 2 USB female cables to attach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There seems to be only a few aftermarket headunits made for the non-Nav GX470, and the fine folks on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/LexusGXOR&quot;&gt;GXOR&lt;/a&gt; seem to think this is the best option. If you have a navigation equipped GX470, the best option is a Tesla-style massive screen. It costs quite a bit more and makes the air conditioned buttons integrated into the touch screen, which I would hate. Luckily I don’t have that model!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;install&quot;&gt;Install&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, take out any CDs in your current headunit. I forgot to do this. If you want to buy my old headunit, it comes with 6 great CDs!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/remove_air.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, remove the two trim pieces on either side of the shifter, using a flat head screwdriver or a plastic trim puller. I used a screwdriver.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then remove the 2 air conditioner vents. Lift gently from the bottom, where the trim pieces were holding them in. These 2 pieces are supposed to be very expensive to replace, so be very careful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, remove the connector from each side. The drivers side has the hazard light connecter, the passenger side has the passenger air bag light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/left_air.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/right_air.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now you can pop out and unplug the coin/ash tray and the cigarette lighter, located below the air conditioning controls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take the 6 10mm bolts out of the radio harness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You basically have 3 pieces to your center stack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Top - Clock/MPG display&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Middle - Headunit, what we’re replacing&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bottom - A/C controls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/screws.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Start taking screws out of the existing Lexus headunit. There were a lot of screws to remove these 3 parts, and I didn’t document it, but prepare to spend a while on this. Also, you don’t reuse MOST of these screws, I had a ton left over. Once done un-screwing, remove all the connecters and remove the whole thing from the car. I did this, and it made it much easier to install the new head unit into the metal harness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/removed.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note that the 10mm bolt, about where your knee is when driving (and shown just above my knee in the following picture), connects the harnesses that supply power. When testing your install, you’ll need to screw that in all the way. This is something I found out later while debugging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/10mm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have the pieces out of your car, you can install the new headunit into the same spot. To do this, you’ll need to do a small amount of plastic removal on the A/C controls in your Lexus. I used a dremel, as shown below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/dremel1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cut the top tab just a bit on the A/C controls. These tabs protrude too much for the new head unit to clip in and fit flush.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/dremel2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After some cutting, the air conditioning controls will clip in below it. I installed the top piece after I had inserted the rest back into the car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/schematic.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As far as connections go, this was pretty simple. Connect like to like connectors where you can find them. I ran the USB female connectors into the glove box, since I won’t use them often and didn’t want to mount them. I ran the GPS module behind the dash, and stuck it up as high and far back as I could, then used the supplied 3M backing tape. It gets a very good signal, even when not exposed. I chose not to mount the microphone that was included with the headunit, as the included mic on the front of the headunit seemed to do a good enough job for my uses. The WiFi antennae is short and is attached to the back of the headunit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/chrome.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll also want to run your wiring for the reverse camera. For the part behind the headunit, wire the yellow into the backup camera input (9) and tap the reverse cable in. For the run to your back door, you’ll need to do this on the passenger side, because of the way the rear door opens. I ran my wire behind the glove box and under the plastic tray on the seats, all the way to the 3rd row area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/grommet.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is where it gets more complicated. You’ll need to run the wiring through the grommet thing seen above(hardest and most painful part of this whole project), and into the rear door area. There is almost no room inside the grommet to run the cable, so this will take some time. The rear door should paneling should be removed, which is pretty easy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Damage from running the wiring through the grommet into the rear door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/damage.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The wiring for the rear camera is simple. Connect the reverse power wire that you ran from the headunit (red), and the power wire (red) from the camera to the reverse light power wire, which is red with blue stripe. I used the passenger side reverse light since it was closer. Seal that connection with some solder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/camera_wiring.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The yellow video cable from the camera connects to the RCA that you ran from the headunit. The ground (black) from the camera connects to any ground on the rear door, there are a quite few bolts you can use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/installed.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the headunit side, make sure you plug the yellow from the rearview camera into the correct video input. I did not do that the first time, and had to take apart my dash again. You want to use input 9, the rearview input.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/camera.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To mount the rear camera, I drilled 2 very small holes in the black plastic part directly above the license plate. I put the 2 camera screw in there with the camera, then ran the wire through where the drivers side license plate light was at. However, then the light wouldn’t stay in its spot, since it had a wire blocking the seal. I drilled out a very small notch into that opening for the light, just big enough for the wire to run through. I placed the wire in there, seen below, then the light would stay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/wire.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;thoughts&quot;&gt;Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love the headunit. This was my first car audio install other than replacing speakers. The install was relatively easy, the inside of the car looks much nicer, and the audio is much better than flipping through radio stations or CDs. I have a 2007 GX470, which means it came with an aux port, and that is still functional with this headunit. The only downsides so far are that the screen became slightly unglued in the bottom left, probably because of the Florida heat. Maps are a little tricky, since this headunit is not always on an internet connection. So far, I’ve had success using Google Maps with a large portion downloaded locally onto the Android headunit. Still, this was a great $300 spent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;apps-i-recommend&quot;&gt;Apps I recommend&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=org.prowl.torque&quot;&gt;Torque Pro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.autolauncher.motorcar.free&quot;&gt;Car Launcher FREE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.pandora.android&quot;&gt;Pandora&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.music&quot;&gt;Google Play Music&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=org.prowl.torque&quot;&gt;Torque&lt;/a&gt; is an awesome app for reading car diagnostics. I bought Torque Pro in 2011, and it has been used very often to read, diagnose, and clear engine codes, as well as get real time statistics from your car. You can connect to Torque using the OBDII interface in your car, and by using a Wifi or &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2EL3NLR&quot;&gt;Bluetooth OBDII adapter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/torque.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.autolauncher.motorcar.free&quot;&gt;Car Launcher&lt;/a&gt; is a simple launcher application that makes the Android interface a little more car friendly. The buttons are bigger, you can dim the screen with one click, set the few applications you actually use on your home screen. It works well for me. The layouts are also customizable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/launcher.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.pandora.android&quot;&gt;Pandora&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.music&quot;&gt;Google Play Music&lt;/a&gt; can download music and play offline. Some use Spotify or other apps. You can also plug in a USB filled with music into your USB inputs, play music on your phone over Bluetooth, or Wifi tether to your headunit and let the headunit do the audio while online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/bt.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The backup camera is great so far. I think every large car should have one, and this one works especially well with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2SWAmN5&quot;&gt;reverse lights&lt;/a&gt; I have. This camera also has the backup lines built in to the camera feed, so you don’t have to enable them in the Android settings&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/backup.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus the dogs love it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/headunit/dogtax.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Headunit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My Turo Claim Horror Story</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/My-Turo-Claim-Horror-Story/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Turo Claim Horror Story" /><published>2019-02-21T08:00:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-02-21T08:00:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/My-Turo-Claim-Horror-Story</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/My-Turo-Claim-Horror-Story/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/no_window.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;No Window&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;tldr&quot;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dude rents my nice Corvette on Turo, his bi-polar girlfriend vandalizes it, it takes 46 days for Turo to pay to get &lt;em&gt;most&lt;/em&gt; of it fixed, and they wouldn’t fix some of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;background&quot;&gt;Background&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/daniel.martinez.9822?eid=ARA1sLcJCI6aBEHu94oDyZUMBivz-L4RagzNM8K8-3gZ19GkX3xu6JMc-Tz3LdSULecDuvp0h7VbpOz-&amp;amp;timeline_context_item_type=intro_card_relationship&amp;amp;timeline_context_item_source=100004641037329&quot;&gt;Daniel B&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/street.lawyer/&quot;&gt;Martinez Jr&lt;/a&gt;, age 37, a &lt;a href=&quot;https://themartinezlaw.com&quot;&gt;local attorney&lt;/a&gt;, rented my &lt;a href=&quot;https://turo.com/rentals/cars/fl/palm-bay/chevrolet-corvette/381353&quot;&gt;2016 Corvette 2LT&lt;/a&gt; from Jan 3 to Jan 5 on a website called &lt;a href=&quot;https://turo.com/c/roberts974&quot;&gt;Turo&lt;/a&gt;. Turo is a website where you can rent your personal car to other people, and Turo provides insurance. Kinda like AirBNB for cars. He had rented my Corvette for a weekend previously, and only put 10 miles on it. The other time he rented my car, I had to go through his dad in order to pick my car up, since he wouldn’t answer his phone or texts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;timeline&quot;&gt;Timeline&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-3&quot;&gt;Jan 3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12:30 PM - Daniel picks up my Corvette, shown below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/before.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-4&quot;&gt;Jan 4&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;11:55 PM - At nearly midnight, a Palm Bay Police Officer, Matt, arrives at my house asking if I owned a blue Chevrolet. I do. He informs me that Daniel had left my car abandoned at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/place/Cumberland+Farms/@28.0791818,-80.6409332,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x88de0e04064cc945:0xc10058927e69d5c2!8m2!3d28.0791818!4d-80.6387392&quot;&gt;Cumberland Farms gas station on 192 and Dairy Rd in West Melbourne&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matt passes my cell phone number on to a West Melbourne police officer on the scene at the gas station, who calls me. He informs me that my window was broken on my car, and I should come down there and get the car. He said that Daniel’s mother was at the gas station and she had my Corvette key. I get a ride there, and a West Melbourne Police officer is there, who leaves before I get to talk to him, and Daniel’s mother is there. I have just 1 key for the Corvette, and the officer said Daniel’s mother had it. She didn’t. She then drove to her house (where Daniel lives) to get my key.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;damage&quot;&gt;Damage&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/no_window.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;No Window&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The driver window was knocked out and busted on the ground. There was damage on the drivers door and mirror. A scratch on the hatchback. A piece of the front grill missing (this was pre-existing damage, as I later found out). The splitter under the front grill was damaged. A scratch in the leather on the passenger interior. Glass everywhere. The targa top was removed and placed in the hatch, and it was raining, and I had no way to put the top back on since Daniel had my key. Who knows how long it had been raining.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/roof_scrape.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Roof Scrape&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She arrived back about 20 minutes later with a key, and I pop the hatch to put the top back on. The top is in terrible condition, with scratches and deep scrapes all over it. It was like someone used the painted part of the top as an ice sled, or hockey puck. Just really bad shape. I put the top back on to keep the water out of the car, and a trash bag over the lack of drivers window. I waited for the officer to come back to get the police report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/side.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Side&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had talked to the employees at the Cumberland Farms gas station. They said they got the whole thing on video. My car was parked in the front corner spot, right under 2 cameras. Daniel’s girlfriend, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/marina.rogers.739&quot;&gt;Marina&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/marinarogers112/&quot;&gt;Rogers&lt;/a&gt;, age 21, found out that Daniel had cheated on her and was trying to attack Daniel while he was driving, and he didn’t like that. He pulled over and parked my Corvette at a gas station, then got an Uber home. She was mad she couldn’t attack him, so she vandalized my car. The Cumberland Farms employee said she punched the drivers window three times, then grabbed the top of the window and leaned back with all her weight to break the window.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;police-interaction&quot;&gt;Police Interaction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/police.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Police&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Cumberland Farms employee said I couldn’t see or retrieve the video evidence without the police. A West Melbourne police officer, Casey, ID#745, finally showed back up to the scene, and gave me a case number, &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/docs/police_report.pdf&quot;&gt;2019-00000441&lt;/a&gt;. Casey told me I can go through Turo, mine or Daniel’s Insurance, or small claims court in order to get my car fixed. He also said what Daniel’s girlfriend did is not a crime, since it isn’t a crime to vandalize someone else’s car. The damage was considered civil, as opposed to criminal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found out through Casey that Daniel’s girlfriend, Marina Rogers, had been checked into a local mental health institution, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.circlesofcare.org/current1/home-page.html&quot;&gt;Circles of Care&lt;/a&gt;. The cop said she was bi-polar. Daniel’s mom said she was really drunk. Daniel did not inform me of any damage to my car, he never messaged me or called me back, and did not seem remorseful about this event in the slightest. After viewing the &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/docs/police_report.pdf&quot;&gt;police report&lt;/a&gt;, it appears Marina Rogers was drunk and suicidal. The officer recognized this, and enacted the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Florida_Mental_Health_Act&quot;&gt;Baker Act&lt;/a&gt; to bring her to the mental facility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-5&quot;&gt;Jan 5&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12:30 AM Picked up the Corvette at Cumberland Farms, drove it home and vacuumed up glass&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:26 AM - Opened up a damage claim with Turo with photo/video walkthrough after I got home&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10AM - Cleaned up the car some more. Noted that Daniel left a $1,300 deposit slip and some blank checks from Wells Fargo in the car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/mirror.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mirror&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-6&quot;&gt;Jan 6&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-7&quot;&gt;Jan 7&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Got a damage quote from John Bias, owner of &lt;a href=&quot;https://acesautobodyshop.com&quot;&gt;Ace’s Body Shop &lt;/a&gt;- 8k&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Called Daniel at his office, left a message with his secretary. Told her the damage was 8k. She said not to worry and that Daniel would make it right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Messaged Turo Damage Claims with the 8k damage estimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-8&quot;&gt;Jan 8&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Called Daniel on his cell, left a voicemail to call me back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Daniel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-9&quot;&gt;Jan 9&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Got a quote from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gerbercollision.com/locations/palm-bay-fl&quot;&gt;Gerber Collision&lt;/a&gt;, with their associate JP. Quote was 7.3k, + 1.5k to 5k more for new seat and dealer code resets. So even higher than Ace’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sent Turo follow up email with second quote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Called Turo support - got Sylvia. She said to wait for the claims specialist to contact me later today. The Claims Specialist’s name is Donovan Durr, 415-941-0706, donovan.durr@turo.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Submitted a request to West Melbourne PD for the case report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Donovan Durr from Turo support contacted me. He mentioned that the grill already had a piece missing when I had rented it before, according to the pictures. I looked, and he’s right. The grill even had that piece missing when I bought it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daniel finally messaged me that night, saying he’s been busy with a jury and asking what he needed to do to take care of this. I messaged him back saying 8k was the damage cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-10&quot;&gt;Jan 10&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Daniel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I cleaned the interior with soap and water and was able to get the scuffing off of the drivers seat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-11&quot;&gt;Jan 11&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Received email from Donovan at Turo, requesting photos of scratches and damage with a ruler next to it. Photos sent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Received &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/docs/police_report.pdf&quot;&gt;police report&lt;/a&gt; from West Melbourne Police Dept, forwarded to Donovan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Call with Donovan Durr at 3:30PM EST. Said he is reviewing with his supervisor. Follow-up in 1 business day. Nothing else to talk about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Daniel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-12&quot;&gt;Jan 12&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Daniel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From Donovan at Turo:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I reviewed this claim with my supervisor. We’re going to cover the damage to the driver’s side door, the mirror, and the top in that area. We’re going to be denying the damage to the rear passenger quarter panel as we cannot determine if that scratch may have been there based on the pre-trip photos provided for that area and the difficulty of seeing the scratch due to its nature.
For the splitter, we would not be able to cover that as we would need pre-trip photos of the undercarriage unfortunately. Although we don’t have pre-trip photos of the interior, we will reimburse you $200 for the interior as well as cover any water damage that may have occurred to due to the top being left off. Your shop of choice will need to file a supplement request for that portion of the claim.
Finally, I want to do a final review on the scratches on the targa top that go down towards the passenger’s side door. I was advised to move forward with a denial for it as my supervisor wasn’t able to see the damage in the post trip photo we looked at, but as we have a few others on file(and the video from the scene), I want to make sure that we are making the right decision. As I do not work Tuesday through Saturday, I do typically do not work on Mondays, but I will see if I can get her to take a second look at that area. If we decide to move forward with coverage, I will go ahead and get that added to our estimate and we should have this fully resolved by early next week. Thank you for your patience as I know this is frustrating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-13&quot;&gt;Jan 13&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Daniel messaged me on the Turo app, saying he has elected to go through Turo to settle this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joined &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/1825468964354089/&quot;&gt;Turo Owners group&lt;/a&gt; on FB for advice on how to deal with Turo. General advice is to use &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fairclaims.com&quot;&gt;FairClaims&lt;/a&gt; and to not take the first number Turo offers you. Just escalate it when they low ball you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-14&quot;&gt;Jan 14&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Noticed that Turo has delisted my Corvette from their website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-15&quot;&gt;Jan 15&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Created account on ResolveAClaim app, as instructed by Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Snapsheet estimator was Marvin Acosta. Snapsheet is a third party that Turo goes through to get damage estimates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From Donovan:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;My supervisor took a second look at the claim and we will be able to go ahead and cover the scratches on the top as well. So that would be everything covered except for this scratch attached to this message, that portion of the front grill that was already missing and the damage to the splitter. I will go ahead and have an estimate written up at this time. If you have any questions, feel free to let me know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-16&quot;&gt;Jan 16&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Received email from SnapSheet, offering me $1,169.51 to cover the damages. The denied a large part of the damage to my car. They said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We have no pre-trip photos of the undercarriage, the damage to the front grill is pre-existing, and we cannot determine if the scratch on the rear hatch on the passenger’s side is pre-existing based on the pre-trip photos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Based on the circumstances, I regret to inform you this claim is ineligible for coverage because pre-existing damage and areas claimed without pre-trip photos are not covered under our policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-17&quot;&gt;Jan 17&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Accepted $1,169.51 payment from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Donovan said $200 interior damage refund will go directly to my earnings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Left a message for Ace’s on dropping off Vette and working on supplements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-18&quot;&gt;Jan 18&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brought Vette to Ace’s, John took pictures and said that he’d work on supplements with Turo/Snapsheet&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-19&quot;&gt;Jan 19&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-20&quot;&gt;Jan 20&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-21&quot;&gt;Jan 21&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-22&quot;&gt;Jan 22&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-23&quot;&gt;Jan 23&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sent estimate to Gerber Collision from Snapsheet, I never heard back from Gerber&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;John Bias from Ace’s called back - said Snapsheet (Laura was the rep) will approve all supplements. Can bring in Monday, Jan 28.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-24&quot;&gt;Jan 24&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-25&quot;&gt;Jan 25&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-26&quot;&gt;Jan 26&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-27&quot;&gt;Jan 27&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-28&quot;&gt;Jan 28&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brought in Vette to Ace’s Body Shop at 9:15AM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-29&quot;&gt;Jan 29&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Received an email from Snapsheet at 4:30PM about receiving the supplement from Ace’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-30&quot;&gt;Jan 30&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jan-31&quot;&gt;Jan 31&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-1&quot;&gt;Feb 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-2&quot;&gt;Feb 2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-3&quot;&gt;Feb 3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-4&quot;&gt;Feb 4&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-5&quot;&gt;Feb 5&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-6&quot;&gt;Feb 6&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-7&quot;&gt;Feb 7&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-8&quot;&gt;Feb 8&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Got a call from John at Ace’s Body Shop. Said Corvette is painted, total is about $4700. Still waiting on Snapsheet to send over the supplement approval. John said that Snapsheet is not wanting to put in an OEM window glass, however, there seem to be no aftermarket window glass parts available anyways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;John said he has been working with Michael Ecker, who is an adjuster for Snapsheet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I called Snapsheet support. They said my supplement is approved for the full amount that Ace’s will charge. They said they sent that approval to Turo on February 7, and Turo is the middle man and has to send it to Ace’s Body shop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Called Turo to follow up - waited 27 minutes before requesting a call back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Got a call back from Richard at Turo. He said he is approving it today, sending me and the body shop an email with information today, and that then I can claim the remaining ~$3600 from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Called Ace’s to let them know the full supplement was approved and will be sent over today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-9&quot;&gt;Feb 9&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-10&quot;&gt;Feb 10&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-11&quot;&gt;Feb 11&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heard back from Donovan at Turo Support, the supplement went from Snapsheet to him. He said that Snapsheet incorrectly listed the damage as on the windshield instead of the drivers window, so he is getting them to redo it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-12&quot;&gt;Feb 12&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John from Ace’s called, the car is finished except putting a few trim pieces on. Windows on and tinted, paint looks good. Planned to pick up car on Friday, Feb 15.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heard back from Donovan with a supplement payment of $3,066.96.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That would put the total paid  at $3,066.96 + $1,169.51 + $200 = $4,436.47&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Asked Donovan about getting the additional amount owed, and mentioned using &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fairclaims.com/&quot;&gt;FairClaims&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total Charges from Ace’s = $4,538.47&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-13&quot;&gt;Feb 13&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-14&quot;&gt;Feb 14&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-15&quot;&gt;Feb 15&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Corvette detailed at Ace’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Picked up car from Ace’s, total charge was $4,538.47, which I paid out of pocket. These clear protector on the drivers door over the paint was not installed, so he said for me to come back up next week to get it installed, it is already paid for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;John found a full container of hair gel in the car that Daniel had left in it from the rental.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/turo/gel.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Gel&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-16&quot;&gt;Feb 16&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donovan from Turo said that he has submitted the second supplement payment for authorization to a supervisor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-17&quot;&gt;Feb 17&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-18&quot;&gt;Feb 18&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response from Turo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-19&quot;&gt;Feb 19&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Received $316.23 from Turo on second supplement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total paid from Turo =  $1,169.51 + $200 + $3,066.96 + $316.23 = $4,752.70.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total paid to Ace’s = $4,538.47&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So after all was finished, I got to keep $214.13, but I have a large scratch on my hatch that Turo would not cover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-20&quot;&gt;Feb 20&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://turo.com/rentals/cars/fl/palm-bay/chevrolet-corvette/381353&quot;&gt;Corvette relisted&lt;/a&gt;, required multiple day rentals and higher rate per day, along with a cleaning fee if not returned clean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feb-21&quot;&gt;Feb 21&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Changed my mind, took the Corvette off Turo because this was a nightmare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, I want to thank &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/Aces-Autobody-1381810925437470/&quot;&gt;Ace’s Body Shop&lt;/a&gt;. They did a great job on my car, and John went above and beyond filling out multiple supplements for Turo and Snapsheet. Seriously, thanks, you guys were great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It took 46 days for Turo to fix damages on my car, and hours of my time dealing with Turo Support, getting quotes from body shops, requesting police reports, and sending in pictures. I was very unsatisfied with both the quality and punctuality of Turo Support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have learned that, if you rent your car on Turo, it should be a car you don’t care about, and to take 50+ pictures before and after every rental. Part of my claim was denied because I only took the 5 required before and after pictures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turo is not on your side, and will do everything possibly to pay you as little as possible. It took me almost 7 weeks to get my damages paid for. I was lucky that I have another car, or else I would have been without a car for a majority of those 7 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;appendix&quot;&gt;Appendix&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.app.goo.gl/EEWHzVyj2soqduuT9&quot;&gt;Pictures/Videos&lt;/a&gt; of the Corvette, timestamps in the details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/daniel.martinez.9822?eid=ARA1sLcJCI6aBEHu94oDyZUMBivz-L4RagzNM8K8-3gZ19GkX3xu6JMc-Tz3LdSULecDuvp0h7VbpOz-&amp;amp;timeline_context_item_type=intro_card_relationship&amp;amp;timeline_context_item_source=100004641037329&quot;&gt;Daniel B&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/street.lawyer&quot;&gt;Martinez Jr&lt;/a&gt; - Rented my Corvette&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Age: 37&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Address: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/place/554+Sedgewood+Cir,+Melbourne,+FL+32904/@28.0543978,-80.6605715,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x88de0dc110aa0175:0x96e0eb8bac68e40e!8m2!3d28.0543978!4d-80.6583775&quot;&gt;554 Sedgewood Circle, Melbourne, FL&lt;/a&gt;. This is a rental house owned by American Homes 4 Rent.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;He lives with his parents, Daniel and Grace Martinez&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Personal email = elsospetto@gmail.com&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cell listed on Turo  321-361-6793&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Law Office Number  321-419-8666&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/marina.rogers.739&quot;&gt;Marina&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/marinarogers112/&quot;&gt;Rogers&lt;/a&gt; - Daniel Martinez’ girlfriend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Age: 21&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Address: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/place/102+Palm+Cir,+Melbourne,+FL+32940/@28.1924181,-80.6625654,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x88de051482b308c7:0x14521373bab1ecfe!8m2!3d28.1924181!4d-80.6603714&quot;&gt;102 Palm Cir Palm Shores, Fl 32940&lt;/a&gt;, owner is Brian Rogers, her father.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;They had been dating for 4 months at the time of the vandalism, and are still dating as of the writing of this post.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;FIT student/cheerleader/Publix cashier.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New Lexus Key</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/New-Lexus-Keys/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Lexus Key" /><published>2019-02-07T11:00:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-02-07T11:00:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/New-Lexus-Keys</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/New-Lexus-Keys/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/keys.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Keys&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I fixed the 2 keys for my Lexus. The battery in both keys was dead, so the remote didn’t work. The screws to get the battery out were stripped, so I have to destroy each case to get in. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ajtdesign-llc.com/online-store/Injection-Fob-2008-2014-FJ-Cruiser-BLACK-p109350070&quot;&gt;AJT Designs&lt;/a&gt; makes some cool 3D printed key fob cases. The GX 470 uses the same key fob as the FJ Cruiser, so I ordered 2 of them in different color combos, seen above. I also installed new &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2MU7wuz&quot;&gt;CR1616&lt;/a&gt; batteries, and both keys work perfect now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/parking.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Parking&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also found out this thing is difficult to park, and ordered a new 9” head unit to replace the stock radio.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Cleaning Headlights and Other Improvements on the Lexus</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Cleaning-Headlights-and-other-improvements-on-the-Lexus/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cleaning Headlights and Other Improvements on the Lexus" /><published>2019-01-28T11:00:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-28T11:00:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Cleaning-Headlights-and-other-improvements-on-the-Lexus</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Cleaning-Headlights-and-other-improvements-on-the-Lexus/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/in_process.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve cleaned the headlights on my Lexus, using toothpaste and car wax. Materials included a tube of toothpaste with baking soda, some wax, an old toothbrush, and some rags. Simply spread the toothpaste around the headlights in a circular motion, similar to waxing. Let it sit for a few minutes, then wipe off with some damp rags. Then wax your headlights to apply a sealant on your lights. Toothpaste is not a good sealant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before Pictures
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/before_L.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/before_L_F.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/before_R.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Materials
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/materials.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/toothpaste.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/in.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/in_process.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Removing Toothpaste and Waxing
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/after_L.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/after_R.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/after_L_F.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/after_R_F.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I noticed a huge difference on the fog lights, which were really cloudy. The headlights themselves improved some, but they weren’t that bad to start with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also installed a new &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2MBqzcI&quot;&gt;gas cap&lt;/a&gt;, which got rid of a few engine error codes, and some new &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2RSoajZ&quot;&gt;hood struts&lt;/a&gt;. The hood fell on me while I was changing some bulbs the other week, and I didn’t want that to happen again. The hood struts took about 20 minutes to change, and I needed a 12mm socket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/hood.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus2/hood2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Clean Headlights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Parts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2MBqzcI&quot;&gt;Toyota Gas Cap&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2RSoajZ&quot;&gt;BOXI Hood struts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Exterior Lights</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Lexus-GX470-Exterior-Lights/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Exterior Lights" /><published>2019-01-15T11:00:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-15T11:00:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Lexus-GX470-Exterior-Lights</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Lexus-GX470-Exterior-Lights/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/lights4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;All&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wrote about &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/Lexus-GX470-LED-Interior-Lights/&quot;&gt;installing new Interior LEDs&lt;/a&gt; on my Lexus GX470, and here’s a bit about exterior lights. I installed new low beams, high beams, daytime running lamps, fog lights, and reverse lights. The install of all of these lights took about an hour. For the front lights, you just have to remove a few engine covers, and for the reverse lights, you have to remove the rear door cover. The fog lights were the most difficult, as you have to get under the car with a 10mm socket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was very happy with the outcome - for under $110, you get a higher end look out of your vehicle, but also much better visibility. The reverse lights and high beams are incredible. My only complaint was that the fogs were yellower than I’d hoped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a list of lights I used, you need 2 of each bulb:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2SUTGdu&quot;&gt;H11 - Low Beams&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2FyBJgO&quot;&gt;9005 - High Beams&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2sv2Dyq&quot;&gt;H3 - Fog Lights&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2SWAmN5&quot;&gt;7440 - Reverse Lights&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2S6HvcZ&quot;&gt;194 - Daytime Running Lights&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Low Beams Only
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/lights1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Low&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;High Beams - these give amazing visibility when driving!
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/lights2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;High&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daytime Running Lights only
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/lights3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;DRL&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Low Beams and Fogs
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/lexus/lights4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;All&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d like to thank the kind members of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/LexusGXOR&quot;&gt;GXOR Facebook group&lt;/a&gt; for their suggestions. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pfranleds.com/gx-470-1/&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; is a handy website for all the light bulbs in a GX470.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>