<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-11-12T09:51:34-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Robert Skelton</title><subtitle>Finance | Tech | Cars | Renovations | Etc</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Rear Door Table</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Rear-Door-Table/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Rear Door Table" /><published>2019-11-12T08:20:14-05:00</published><updated>2019-11-12T08:20:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Rear-Door-Table</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Rear-Door-Table/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/19.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I installed a drop down rear table in my GX, it took about 4 hours and $10 of new parts, plus some some scrap and parts I already had. If you bought all new parts and wood, this would cost about $50. The cheapest table you can buy for the GX is the &lt;a href=&quot;https://bluelineeo.com/products/drop-down-table-by-front-runner-1?_pos=1&amp;amp;_sid=d76aacddc&amp;amp;_ss=r&amp;amp;fbclid=IwAR2kTxwcdwTvTWkEN5io6CTTvupPVo2UFykXIjM-KEtGsIX1v0UTjxycjwM&quot;&gt;Front Runner table&lt;/a&gt;, which runs about $130.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, I cut a piece of (nice) scrap plywood down to 40” by 15”. I stained this with a natural stain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I used a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2QmriTh&quot;&gt;30” piano hinge&lt;/a&gt; which I already had to attach it to the bottom of the rear door, using the included screws. This &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2QmriTh&quot;&gt;piano hinge&lt;/a&gt; lets the table swing up and down while still being attached to the door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, I bought a gate latch from Home Depot to secure the table in the up position. I secured this to the top of the door and the other piece to the table itself, making sure it could latch before I screwed anything together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great, now I have a table that can stay in the closed position, but won’t stay level. I fixed that using some old rope, the same rope I used to make the rear door handle. I cut two holes in the outside corners of the table, and kept drilling into the plastic of the door itself. Here, I had to remove the rear door, for like the 10th time since owning the GX, and route the rope behind the plastic rear door cover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I pushed the rope inside, put a very large washer back there, then tied the rope and covered it in electrical tape. While I was back there, I super glued the back of the piano hinge screws and the gate hardware screws as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the rope is secure behind the door, I put the door plastic back on, then routed the other side of the rope through the holes I cut in the wood earlier. I put another large washer on the bottom of the table, then tied the rope into a knot. Now you’ve got a finished, functional table.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I showed it to some friends (Kelley is frosted flakes), and they asked why didn’t I stain it. I used a natural stain, but it was pretty light, so I pulled the wood back off and re-stained using a MUCH darker stain. Looks way better! While the wood was off, I rounded the corners where the rope runs through the holes, so that you don’t walk by it and hit yourself on a sharp corner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the stain was dry, I put the table back on the same way as before. The rear door pocket is still pretty functional! I can still store toilet paper, paper towels, and a few other things. The gate hardware has a spot for a lock, which I just put a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KBZxBr&quot;&gt;carabiner&lt;/a&gt; in, so that it doesn’t unlatch while driving. I also added some clear plastic bumpers onto the rear door plastic so that the wood doesn’t run against plastic while driving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/16.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/17.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/18.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I might cut the ends of the rope down a bit under the table, they’re a bit long, but I’m leaving them for now just in case. I’m excited to use this table on road trips with our dogs!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/table/20.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rear Table&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Tinting the Fog Lights</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Tint-Fogs/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Tinting the Fog Lights" /><published>2019-10-25T07:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-10-25T07:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Tint-Fogs</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Tint-Fogs/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fog/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fog Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I yellow tinted my fog lights on the GX, it was pretty simple. Here’s how to do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fog/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fog Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take your fog lights off the car. This is a 10mm bolt behind each light, which can be reached easily just by laying under the front bumper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fog/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fog Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take the fogs to your work station. Clean the housing really well. Get out your tint, I used &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/32QXscE&quot;&gt;this yellow tint from Amazon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spray some water from a spray bottle on the lights, then apply the film, sticky side touching the lights. Spray some more water on the outside of the film, then squeegee the water out, using the included tool or a credit card, or similar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finish getting all the water out, then use a hair dryer on VERY HOT to get the edges. Use scissors or a utility knife to cut the ends to look seamless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fog/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fog Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reinstall back on the GX!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fog/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fog Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Ditch Lights Install</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Ditch-Light-Install/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Ditch Lights Install" /><published>2019-10-21T07:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-10-21T07:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Ditch-Light-Install</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Ditch-Light-Install/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/26.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I installed ditch lights in my GX today, it took about 3 hours and $250.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;parts-bought&quot;&gt;Parts Bought&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ragofabrication.com/collections/gx470/products/2002-2009-1st-generation-lexus-gx470-ditch-light-brackets-1&quot;&gt;Rago Fabrication GX470 Ditch Mounts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/31vmj4C&quot;&gt;2x Baja Squadron Sport LED &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2VYJoeI&quot;&gt;1x Add a Circuit Tap&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the time of purchase, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ragofabrication.com/&quot;&gt;Rago Fabrication&lt;/a&gt; was having a sale. I bought the ditch brackets and Baja Squadron Sport pods with wiring harness for $235. You could do this install with any set of LED pods, but you’ll have to make your own wiring harness (with a fuse). The Rago mounts are great, so definitely use those.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alright, here’s how to do it. First, install the brackets from Rago. This was a required first for me, since my brackets got here five days before my lights and wiring harness. I followed &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1F9legl29M4&quot;&gt;this video&lt;/a&gt; to install the brackets, just take 1 bolt out at a time to make the hood not move.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, put the lights on the brackets, follow the instructions there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, take apart all the plastic in your engine, if you still have it. The plastic that is. I hope you still have the engine. I took off the engine cover in order to remove the very back plastic piece that was hiding some wiring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lay your wiring harness in place, you can even hook it up. You can take the red to the positive terminal and black to the negative terminal of your battery to test the harness and lights, just make sure the switch is one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now here comes what I thought was the hardest part - getting part of the wiring harness through the firewall. I decided to use the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2VYJoeI&quot;&gt;Add a Circuit Tap&lt;/a&gt;, so I don’t plug directly in to the battery (which is possible). The part of the harness that connects to the splitter that plugs both lights in, I fed that part through the firewall from the cabin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To do that, I cut a hole in the rubber nipple (where you see the white coat hanger in the pictures below) in the engine compartment on the firewall grommet thing. This is made for wiring expansions anyways. Then, under the drivers seat, push the wiring up through the hole that leads to the engine compartment. I found it MUCH easier to remove the plug (leaving just wiring and connections) and to tape those wires to a wire hanger that had already been pushed through the firewall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alright, got that done? Sweet. Bet it took a minute. Now you can make sure everything works. Plug in the lights to the harnesses, the black to a ground, and the red to power. I pulled back the plastic by the drivers left footwell to use a ground bolt there, you can see in the top left of the picture below. Then I used the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2VYJoeI&quot;&gt;Add a Circuit Tap&lt;/a&gt; to tap the 30A drivers power seat fuse, which is in the small fuse box under the steering wheel. The switch should turn on the lights, and when the lights are on the switch should light up red.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To hook up the included harness to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2VYJoeI&quot;&gt;Add a Circuit Tap&lt;/a&gt;, snip the end off the end of the red wire that was included, expose some of the copper using wire cutters, then push that wire into the end of the tap. Crimp the connection using some elbow grease and pliers. Pull the 30A from the drivers power seat slot and put it in the closer spot to the connector. Add another fuse in the next slot, this is the fuse for your ditch lights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/update.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For your switch in the cabin, I had to remove the wiring for it to sit snug in its newly drilled hole. To do this, unplug all the wires (remember where they are), then run the wires up from the back of the hole. Then plug those wires back into the switch, out of the plastic, then you can put the switch where the hole is. I made my hole a little bit too big, so you can use tape or velcro or caulk or basically anything to make it a little more snug.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What a terrible hole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/16.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/17.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/18.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/19.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, just make everything pretty. I ran the interior wiring behind the plastic footwell. In the engine compartment, I ran the wiring for each light under the plastic piece by the windshield, so very little of the wiring is exposed. This was a little difficult to do, but looks a lot better. I also used zip ties to keep the new electrical running next to the old electrical, and behind that plastic panel I mentioned earlier. Reassemble your engine plastic pieces, close up the interior pieces, you’ve got some bright lights!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/20.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/21.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/22.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/24.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason my install took so long was because I broke the connectors when I was putting the switch back together inside the hole, and had to crimp some new ends. Also I blew a fuse when testing. Then again, it’s electrical in a car. Have you ever done a electrical project in your car and NOT blown a fuse. Me either. The nice thing about the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2VYJoeI&quot;&gt;Add a Circuit Tap&lt;/a&gt; that I linked is that it comes with lots of extra fuses, so I just replaced it with a 5A fuse of the same size.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As far as the products, the Rago mounts fit perfect. You can have the hood opened or closed and the lights never touch your windshield. Some videos I saw complain about the wiring harness being too short, but it was long enough for my GX. The lights seem great so far, SUPER bright.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/23.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dl/25.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ditch Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I were to make this nicer, what I would have done is buy a new plate that converts your existing switch panel to have one extra blank from &lt;a href=&quot;https://sbeprecision.com/product/gx470-mirror-switch-plate-with-blanks-plus-2-switch-openings/?fbclid=IwAR2135GD3VnZ60hwcgVjCgGwLRl3IdyQAwuM_xPr2Y2IB22XYZAg6pRJnuU&quot;&gt;SBE Precision Products&lt;/a&gt;, and a new &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ragofabrication.com/collections/led-wiring-and-accessories/products/toyota-factory-switch-square?variant=40556182663&quot;&gt;Toyota OEM looking ditch light switch&lt;/a&gt;. That would have added $70 to my install just for a nicer looking switch, so I didn’t. If you go that route, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6nWmIKTCtkY&quot;&gt;here is a good video&lt;/a&gt; on how to do the wiring - it is a little bit different but your switch is backlit, which is fancy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Blackout All Chrome</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Blackout-All-Chrome/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Blackout All Chrome" /><published>2019-10-16T10:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T10:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Blackout-All-Chrome</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Blackout-All-Chrome/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had already &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/Plasti-Dip-GX470-Grill/&quot;&gt;blacked out the front grill&lt;/a&gt; on my GX with &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2H7U2dj&quot;&gt;Plasti Dip&lt;/a&gt;, and it is holding up really well and looks great, so I figured I would replace the rest of the chrome throughout the vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, I replaced the front 4 windows weatherstripping trim with black trim. This was available on overseas models (Prado), and you can grab the parts on eBay. I wasn’t particularly thrilled with the non-OEM quality of the parts I got from eBay, so I won’t link them. To install them, just remove one Torx screw (I think it was T10) from the inside of your door panel, then remove the old part. The new weatherstripping trim slides in, then screw it in. I had to use a mallet to get it to sit right. Repeat for all 4 doors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The back 2 windows I did not change the weatherstripping trim, as it involves removing the rear windows, and I didn’t want to get into all that. I just Plasti Dipped it, along with the rear emblems. It took less than 1 can of &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2H7U2dj&quot;&gt;Plasti Dip&lt;/a&gt; to do the entire rear of the car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I taped a little of an outline, but it really didn’t help that much. At least it comes off easy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did 8 coats, with 30 minutes in between.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then removed tape and started cleaning with a damp cloth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do not recommend using an exacto knife like I did, I left a few small scratches in the paint. Use some plastic if.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The one time I wish the GX had a V6…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now the only chrome left on the car is the Lexus logo on the front grill and on the rims. And the tow hitch. And the lug nuts. Not blacking any of that out though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blackout/10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Change Heated Seat Bulbs</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Change-Heated-Seat-Bulbs/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Change Heated Seat Bulbs" /><published>2019-10-16T07:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T07:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Change-Heated-Seat-Bulbs</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Change-Heated-Seat-Bulbs/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/hs/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;HS&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the lights that provided a backlight to my heated seats on my GX470 was out, so I wanted to change it. I initially tried pulling the bulb out and replacing it with an LED of similar size, but the LED would not light up in any orientation, and the harness that holds the old bulb in was really difficult to deal with, so I just bought new bulbs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ended up ordered a pair of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.superbrightleds.com/moreinfo/instrument-cluster-gauge/neox-led-bulb-high-power-instrument-panel-led/221/&quot;&gt;NEO3-RHP: 3mm NEO3-xHP Red&lt;/a&gt; from SuperBrightLEDs for $1.79 each. I figured, heated seat, should be red, right?.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/hs/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;HS&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To install, pop the switch out of the dash with a small flathead screwdriver or plastic pry tool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/hs/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;HS&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remove the connector from the wiring. You can use pliers or a clamp to hold it out of the dash, or else it will fall back in and you’ll probably have to use pliers to fish that connector back out. Then remove the cover that says L or R.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/hs/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;HS&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The LED itself is the grey circle on the side of the switch. Use a screwdriver to rotate the old light to the left, the insert your new LED into the same spot, and rotate it right. Plug it back in and turn on the car to see if you have a light. If not, just remove the LED and rotate it to the opposite polarity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/hs/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;HS&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To reassemble, attach the L or R switch cover, plug back into the harness, then push back into your dash. Done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/hs/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;HS&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Radar Detector Hardwire</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Radar-Hardwire/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Radar Detector Hardwire" /><published>2019-10-07T07:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-10-07T07:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Radar-Hardwire</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Radar-Hardwire/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently put my Corvette on the market, so I took the hardwired radar detector out of it. Might as well put it in the GX!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2pSNAke&quot;&gt;RJ11 power cord&lt;/a&gt; that has a simple power and ground, with the goal to get power behind the mirror. It was ridiculously easy, the easiest of any car I’ve ever done. There are 2 wires behind the rearview mirror that are exposed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In spot 1 there is a blue/white cord, and in spot 2 there is a black/white cord.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Put your power from the radar cord (red) into spot 1 with the blue/white cord. Put the ground (black) into spot 2, the black/white cord. The prongs from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2pSNAke&quot;&gt;RJ11 power cord&lt;/a&gt; should fit snug.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I then wrapped a bit of black electrical tape around the power cord and the other wires running into the mirror, to keep everything from moving around too much. Plug in your radar detector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have power when the car is on, and the power drops when the car is turned off. Perfect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wrapped the cord once around my mirror, since it was a little long, then mounted it with the normal suction cup mounts, which aren’t great. If you’re doing any off road driving, you’ll want to take your detector down, or get a &lt;a href=&quot;https://blendmount.com/&quot;&gt;Blendmount&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2pSNAke&quot;&gt;Escort radar detector&lt;/a&gt;, these detectors have great sensitivity, but you can dial it back and customize them how you like them. I actually use an older model 8500 X50 that I bought for my first Corvette.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Custom Webbing Dog Divider</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Custom-Webbing-Dog-Divider/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Custom Webbing Dog Divider" /><published>2019-08-09T07:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-08-09T07:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Custom-Webbing-Dog-Divider</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Custom-Webbing-Dog-Divider/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/26.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a big dog, Bentley, a 75 pound lab mix, who loves being in the front of the GX when I’m driving. Only issue is, he’s a 75 pound dog. So I wanted a webbing divider to keep him in the 3rd row area, but the only one on the market that is made to fit the GX starts at $180! I used &lt;a href=&quot;https://raingler.com/collections/lexus-heavy-duty-cargo-netting/products/lexus-gx-j120-barrier-divider&quot;&gt;this product from Raingler&lt;/a&gt; as my inspiration, and started to plan how to make my own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Raingler divider uses stitching for the joints, and I can sew, but I don’t have a sewing machine. The type of stitches used to sew together an intersection of webbing really requires a sewing machine (or thousands of hour of free time which I don’t have), so I found some other projects that had used grommets to assemble webbing. I decided to go this route, and purchased the following parts on Amazon, which ran me about $60.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Parts Bought&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KpyTwR&quot;&gt;4x Frontmans Loops&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/31vmj4C&quot;&gt;4x D Rings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KBZxBr&quot;&gt;6x Carabiners&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2YUjQiP&quot;&gt;10-12 yards of Webbing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KpSf4S&quot;&gt;Grommet Kit with 100 grommets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tools Needed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hammer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Scissors&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lighter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Drill with a bit that can drill through metal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For mounting the divider, it needs to have something to attach to on the inside of the car. I noticed the Raingler product added some mount points into the body, inside of the panels, so I did that. I pulled back the panels on both sides of the car, right behind the second row seats, and found 2 spots I could drill in to on each side. This gives 2 mount points per side, plus a 3rd mount point per side on the bottom of the middle seats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I put 1 &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KpyTwR&quot;&gt;Frontmans Loop&lt;/a&gt; at each spot, with about a 10” strip of webbing, with a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/31vmj4C&quot;&gt;D ring&lt;/a&gt; on the other end. For making these connection pieces, I made them before putting them in the car. I cut a strip of webbing, then used the grommet punch to make holes. Make sure you burn off the loose strings on the ends of the webbing and the holes. Then, I used the grommet die to put a grommet in, with a Frontmans Loop on one side a D ring on the other. This was my first time using grommets, and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KpSf4S&quot;&gt;kit&lt;/a&gt; I bought was actually pretty easy to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did this for 2 spots on the drivers side and 2 spots on the passenger side, and fed the top connector piece above the panel, and the bottom connector piece between the 2 panels I had to pull off. The most difficult part of this whole project was drilling into the metal body panels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I decided I wanted the webbing to be able to flex with the middle seats being up or down. Turns out, the distance between the mount point on the seats being up or down and the mount point I added was only a 2” difference, so I used the longer measurement. Here’s my chicken scratch measurements, I cut and built my divider using the bottom diagram. 34” along the top mounting points I added, 46” in the middle mount points I added, and 30” for the 2 mount points built in on the middle seats. The vertical strip from the top to middle was 21”, and from middle to bottom was 14”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made the perimeter first, and made sure it fit on the mount points I had added and the back of the middle row seats. All fits! The hardest part was where 3 different strips intersected. I was worried the grommet would be too small to contain all 3 pieces of webbing, but it held great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/16.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/17.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/18.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I added another horizontal strip and started adding a few vertical strips, putting grommets at every intersection along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/19.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/20.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/21.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All done, then just install it! You can see the webbing flexes enough that the middle row can be up or down, however the middle row can not recline much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/21.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/22.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/24.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It took about 3 hours and $60 of parts to build a webbing barrier that is perfect for Bentley, and I have enough leftover parts, webbing, and carabiners that I could make a second one, or any other cool webbing things. I can also add many more vertical and horizontal strips. This was made to keep our lab in the back. We also have a 12 pound Cavalier, and she can fit through the nets, but that’s OK, she doesn’t get in my way when I drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any questions, feel free to comment, or ask me in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/LexusGXOR/?ref=group_header&quot;&gt;GXOR Facebook group&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/dogs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Update, 1 day later: I had to add 2 more vertical strips, since Bentley jumped through them once he saw we had Chick-fil-A in the front seat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/25.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/26.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Format an Audio USB for a C7 Corvette from a Mac</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Format-Audio-USB-for-C7-Corvette-From-Mac/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Format an Audio USB for a C7 Corvette from a Mac" /><published>2019-07-29T12:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-07-29T12:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Format-Audio-USB-for-C7-Corvette-From-Mac</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Format-Audio-USB-for-C7-Corvette-From-Mac/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/vette/plug.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.  Insert a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2OpmYmB&quot;&gt;USB drive&lt;/a&gt; into your Mac&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.  Open disk utility.&lt;/strong&gt; This is under Applications &amp;gt; Utilities &amp;gt; Disk Utility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/vette/1.png&quot; alt=&quot;1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.  Eject the partition.&lt;/strong&gt;
This is listed below the USB Drive name itself, and has an eject button to the right. Labeled “2” in the picture above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4.  Format the USB&lt;/strong&gt;
Click on the USB Name, then Erase. Select Format MS-DOS and Scheme “Master Boot Record”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Format the partition&lt;/strong&gt;
Click on the partition below it that was just created, then Erase. Select format MS-DOS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/vette/2.png&quot; alt=&quot;2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Add Audio Files&lt;/strong&gt;
Find your USB drive and drag and drop audio files onto it. Most people seem to recommend playlists, since those will play non stop in your Vette.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7. Put in in your Vette&lt;/strong&gt;
Plug your USB drive into the USB slot either behind the dash, or under the center console. Either one works for audio, in a 2016 at least.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How To Save Money on Large Purchases</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/How-To-Save-Money-On-Large-Purchases/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How To Save Money on Large Purchases" /><published>2019-07-18T12:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-07-18T12:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/How-To-Save-Money-On-Large-Purchases</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/How-To-Save-Money-On-Large-Purchases/">&lt;p&gt;If you do any amount of online shopping, using some of the following tips can save you some money!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;rakuten&quot;&gt;Rakuten&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rakuten.com/r/ROBERT47769?eeid=43662&amp;amp;utm_source=extension&amp;amp;utm_medium=raf_link&quot;&gt;Rakuten&lt;/a&gt;, formerly called Ebates. This is a browser extension that helps you to earn cash back on purchases at certain retailers. It will also suggest other retailers if you can get the same item at a cheaper price. I have &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/using-rakuten-for-more-cashback&quot;&gt;wrote about Rakuten before&lt;/a&gt;, and I’ve earned about $350 in cash back since 2016. I recently needed to buy a new range and microwave, and the ones I decided on were about $1300 at Home Depot. My Rakuten extension popped up and said I could buy the same models at ABT.com for about $1100, and they give 6% back at Rakuten, which is $66 back!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/ebates/rakuten.png&quot; alt=&quot;Rakuten&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;credit-card-cash-back&quot;&gt;Credit Card Cash Back&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one is obvious, but you can pay with credit cards to earn some more cash back. Some cards have rotating categories, so will give higher percentage cash back at certain retailers, but only during certain quarters. The Chase Freedom and Discover IT cards are examples of these cards. A great example here is that for Q3 2019, which is the current quarter as I write this article, Discover is 5% back on Paypal purchases. As I was checking out at ABT.com for my new appliances (mentioned above), they had the option to check out with Paypal, so I did with my Discover IT card. At 5% of $1100, that is $55 cash back, on top of the $66 I got from Rakuten. So using Rakuten and the right credit card got me from $1300 to $1100 - $66 - $55 = under $1000! Nice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;honey&quot;&gt;Honey&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://joinhoney.com/ref/dsskgi&quot;&gt;Honey&lt;/a&gt; is very similar to Rakuten, but I don’t think it does as good of a job at giving cash back. It gives cash back in the form of “Honey Gold”, which you can buy gift cards with. The nice feature of Honey is that it will automatically try coupon codes! Lots of  ecommerce sites have discount codes or coupon codes, that are sometimes not public. Honey has a list of these, and will try to use all of them. I like to get the discount code from Honey, then use Rakuten for their cash back. You can not earn both cash back through Rakuten AND Honey Gold. If you click on one after the other, one will pop up saying that you can’t earn for both cash back portals, so pick and choose which one works best for your given transaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/ebates/honey1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Honey&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/ebates/honey2.png&quot; alt=&quot;Honey&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;slickdeals&quot;&gt;Slickdeals&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://slickdeals.net/&quot;&gt;Slickdeals&lt;/a&gt; is the classic website for finding things that are on sale. You can set up email alerts for items you are interested in. I did this with some $60 Sennheiser headphones that I knew went on sale pretty often. I set up the emails, and bought them a few months later for $28. This site is mostly focused on technology products, but there are tons of other products on here. I’ve bought some clothes and dry food products that I’ve seen on Slickdeals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;home-depot-and-lowes-10-off-codes&quot;&gt;Home Depot and Lowe’s 10% Off Codes&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re making a large purchase at Home Depot or Lowe’s, it can behoove you buy online and use a coupon code. You can generate them, somehow (search the Slickdeals forums if you are interested), or you can buy them for a few bucks. When you’re spending $1,000 on flooring, it’s worth it to spend $5 to get a 10% coupon, which will save you $95. I’ve bought &lt;a href=&quot;https://lowescoupon.info/&quot;&gt;Lowe’s coupons here&lt;/a&gt; and found free ones &lt;a href=&quot;https://renovopower.com/lowes.html&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, though I am not affiliated with either website. You can also fill out a &lt;a href=&quot;https://moversguide.usps.com/mgo/disclaimer?referral=MG80&quot;&gt;USPS Change of Address form&lt;/a&gt;, and they send you a welcome kit. This usually includes a 10% off coupon to both Home Depot and Lowe’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;bumped&quot;&gt;Bumped&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bumped.com/?ref=8ad7cc96&quot;&gt;Bumped&lt;/a&gt; is an app that you give access to your credit card transactions, and you can earn stocks based on what retailers you shop at. You get a choice of 1 retailer per category, and they are called “Loyalties”. For example, Home Improvement is a category. I chose Home Depot over Lowe’s, since I shop at Home Depot much more. When Bumped notices a transaction on any of my linked credits cards from Home Depot, it’ll give me a small percentage of that purchase as a stock, 1% at Home Depot. There are tons of categories. I don’t ever count on this, but I set it up a few months ago and I’ve earned about $30 in stocks from just doing normal shopping. This is a new application, so the app is still a bit buggy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/ebates/bumped.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bumped&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;camelcamelcamel&quot;&gt;CamelCamelCamel&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is one I don’t use that often, since I don’t a ton of Amazon shopping, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://camelcamelcamel.com/&quot;&gt;CamelCamelCamel&lt;/a&gt; is a Amazon price history. You can install it as a browser extension, and see the price of an item over time. Honey does a lot of the same things.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">If you do any amount of online shopping, using some of the following tips can save you some money!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Recipe - Keto Chocolate Milkshake</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Keto-Chocolate-Milkshake/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Recipe - Keto Chocolate Milkshake" /><published>2019-07-12T09:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-07-12T09:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Keto-Chocolate-Milkshake</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Keto-Chocolate-Milkshake/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/recipes/milkshake.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ingredients&quot;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 Cups Ice&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3 Tbsp &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2l2Cern&quot;&gt;Swerve&lt;/a&gt;, or similar Keto confectioners sugar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3/4 Cup Heavy Whipping Cream&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1.5 Cups Almond Milk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 scoops &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2l2Cern&quot;&gt;Protein Powder&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;instructions&quot;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Put everything in blender&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Blend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>