<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-07-12T11:44:43-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Robert Skelton</title><subtitle>Finance | Tech | Cars | Renovations | Recipes</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Pepper Steak</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/pepper-steak/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pepper Steak" /><published>2018-07-12T11:10:14-04:00</published><updated>2018-07-12T11:10:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/pepper-steak</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/pepper-steak/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/recipes/peppersteak.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ingredients&quot;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1.5+ lbs Beef Round Steak&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2+ cups brown rice&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1+ Red Bell Pepper, chopped&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 onion, chopped&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Soy Sauce&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;White wine vinegar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Corn starch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;instructions&quot;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cook rice&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Combine 1 tbsp soy sauce, 1 tbsp white wine vinegar, 1 tsp cornstarch, tons of pepper as the marinade&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cut the steak into strips, marinate&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Place cooked rice into containers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cook steak, place into same containers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Combine 3 tbsp soy sauce, 1 tbsp water, 2 tsp cornstarch and crushed red pepper as the sauce for the veggies&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cook onion and red bell pepper, add sauce&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Place veggies into same containers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;considerations&quot;&gt;Considerations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add green onions&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add sesame seeds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;makes-6-servings&quot;&gt;Makes ~6 servings&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;total-price-13&quot;&gt;Total Price: ~$13&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;price-per-serving-217&quot;&gt;Price per serving: $2.17&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;elizabeths-rating-&quot;&gt;Elizabeth’s Rating: ?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;roberts-rating-8&quot;&gt;Robert’s Rating: 8&lt;/h4&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shrimp and Sausage Cajun Bowl</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/shrimp-and-sausage-cajun-bowl/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shrimp and Sausage Cajun Bowl" /><published>2018-07-12T10:10:14-04:00</published><updated>2018-07-12T10:10:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/shrimp-and-sausage-cajun-bowl</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/shrimp-and-sausage-cajun-bowl/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/recipes/shrimp-sausage-bowl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ingredients&quot;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2+ cups of brown or white rice&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shrimp, seasoned with some cajun seasoning&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1+ Zucchini, quartered and peppered&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1+ Bell Pepper, any color&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 Andouille Sausage, cut up&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2+ avocados, sliced into small pieces&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 can of corn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;instructions&quot;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cook rice&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cook corn in microwave&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cook shrimp&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cook zucchini and bell pepper&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cook sausage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Combine rice, shrimp, corn, zucchini and peppers, sausage, avocados into containers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;considerations&quot;&gt;Considerations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add cilantro&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add cheese&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add hot sauce&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add lime juice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;makes-7-servings&quot;&gt;Makes ~7 servings&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;total-price-15&quot;&gt;Total Price: ~$15&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;price-per-serving-214&quot;&gt;Price per serving: $2.14&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;elizabeths-rating-9&quot;&gt;Elizabeth’s Rating: 9&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;roberts-rating-10&quot;&gt;Robert’s Rating: 10&lt;/h4&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Cost of a Dog, Itemized</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cost-of-a-dog-itemized/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cost of a Dog, Itemized" /><published>2018-06-25T14:10:14-04:00</published><updated>2018-06-25T14:10:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cost-of-a-dog-itemized</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cost-of-a-dog-itemized/">&lt;p&gt;My fiancé, Elizabeth, and I adopted a black lab mix puppy from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.leecountyhumane.org/&quot;&gt;Lee County Humane Society&lt;/a&gt; in Auburn, AL in April 2017. His name is Bentley, and he’s a wonderful dog! He weighs about 65 pounds, and stays with me while I work from home. I wanted to know exactly how much he was costing us, so here’s the expenses for our dog broken down. This post is also an excuse to publish tons of dog pictures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dog/pup.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bentley&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Purchase/Adoption&lt;/strong&gt; - If you buy a dog from a breeder, costs can be in the multi-hundreds to the multi-thousands of dollars. We adopted our pup at the Humane Society, and the adoption fee was $120. He was already neutered, had his first few rounds of shots, and was already healthy enough to be taken home at 8 weeks. I’m not going to include this one time cost in my yearly dog expenses, but it’s something to consider with a dog.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dog/cake.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bentley&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Training&lt;/strong&gt; - We did a Beginning Puppy Training at PetCo, it was a little over $100. This class was really more about us (the humans) learning how to train our dog. Now that we have taken it, I think we’d do a good job at training any other dogs we adopt without paying for a class. This was also a one time expense, so I won’t count it towards yearly expenses. I highly recommend taking a class like this with your first dog so that you can learn how to train them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dog/lake.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bentley&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2trGgLe&quot;&gt;Food&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - We buy a bag of dog food about every 5 weeks, about 10 bags per year. We buy &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2trGgLe&quot;&gt;Hills Science Diet for Sensitive Stomachs&lt;/a&gt;, highly recommended by every vet Elizabeth has ever worked for. Each bag costs about $50. We also give him lots of veggies, peanut butter, and table scraps, but they aren’t just for him. He gets all of the broccoli stalks and lots of baby carrots, those costs are more associated with us humans though, so counting those here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dog/barkbox.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bentley&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.barkbox.com/r/VLSI3YAX94&quot;&gt;BarkBox&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; -  We use BarkBox to get new toys and treats, but mostly to keep up out of the Pet Store. We’re pretty bad about impulse buying all kinds of treats and bones when we’re in there. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.barkbox.com/r/VLSI3YAX94&quot;&gt;BarkBox&lt;/a&gt; costs $20/month, and has been very worth it for us so far. It usually has 2 toys, 2 bags of treats, and a bone, which would cost well over $20 at PetCo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dog/tango.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bentley&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2MprawH&quot;&gt;Probiotic Powder&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Bentley farts a lot. We give him 1 probiotic powder pack at breakfast to reduce that as much as possible, this is about $1 per day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dog/pool.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bentley&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Medicine&lt;/strong&gt; - Here’s where we have gotten lucky so far. My fiancé, Elizabeth, works for a veterinarian’s office. So far, we have received all of Bentley’s medicine for free! This saves us about $200 per year, so if your fiancé doesn’t work for a vet, don’t forget to consider for this cost.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dog/halloween.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bentley&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vet Visits&lt;/strong&gt; - Required shots, yearly checkups, etc. Bentley has had issues with his stomach, so we’ve had a few costly vet visits already. It does help that Elizabeth gets all vet services for half price because of her job, so we’ve spent about $400 per year so far on this. It’d be more than double if we didn’t have that benefit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dog/luau.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bentley&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;www.rover.com/refer/robers32904/&quot;&gt;Dog Sitting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - I stay at home with Bentley most days, and if I’m out of town then my fiancé or our roommates usually feed him, take him outside to use the bathroom, etc. The exception is long holidays when everyone goes out of town, like Thanksgiving or Christmas. We paid our neighbor $100 last year to watch Bentley for a few days over Christmas, and Elizabeth stayed in town on Thanksgiving. This year we’ll probably both be gone both holidays, so maybe $200 for dog sitting those two holidays. We’ve used &lt;a href=&quot;www.rover.com/refer/robers32904/&quot;&gt;Rover&lt;/a&gt; to watch other dogs before, and will likely look to utilize it again over the holidays.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dog/lightsaber.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bentley&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other&lt;/strong&gt; - I say we have the BarkBox to keep up out of the pet store, but we still go too much. I’d say on average, we spend $20/month on more toys, leashes, collars, &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2K9EhWo&quot;&gt;harnesses&lt;/a&gt;, dog bowls, treats, bones, a cage, dog bed, etc. We bought most of this stuff when we first got Bentley, but we still buy him new collars, more bones, and harnesses and leashes if the old ones get worn out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dog/hd.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bentley&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total = Food + BarkBox + Probiotic Powder + Medicine + Vet Visits + Dog Sitting + Etc&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total = (10 bags * $50) + (12 months * $20/month) + (365 days * $1/day) + $0 + ($400/yr) + ($200/year)+ (12 months * $20/month)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total per Year = ($500) + ($240) + ($365) + ($0) + ($400) + ($200) + ($240)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total = $1,945&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/dog/handsome.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bentley&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There you go, about $2,000 per year for our full size Labrador, or $5.50 per day. So worth it. This does not factor in some large upfront costs, like adoption fees, puppy training, or some things you’ll need for your first dog, like harnesses, leashes, crates, dog beds, which will likely add up to over $500. Getting a dog is a big financial decision, but can be even more expensive if you have to take your dog to day care or don’t have access to benefits of a vet office.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">My fiancé, Elizabeth, and I adopted a black lab mix puppy from the Lee County Humane Society in Auburn, AL in April 2017. His name is Bentley, and he’s a wonderful dog! He weighs about 65 pounds, and stays with me while I work from home. I wanted to know exactly how much he was costing us, so here’s the expenses for our dog broken down. This post is also an excuse to publish tons of dog pictures.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Citrus Paint Colors</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/citrus-paint-colors/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Citrus Paint Colors" /><published>2018-06-25T08:05:14-04:00</published><updated>2018-06-25T08:05:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/citrus-paint-colors</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/citrus-paint-colors/">&lt;p&gt;This is a post for my own knowledge, to keep track of what colors I’ve painted what rooms in my house on Citrus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Guest Bathroom - Fresh Arboretum PPG Eggshell, PPG83-310. 50 GY 74/273.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Living room, hallways - Dorian Gray, SW7017 eggshell.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Master Bedroom, Accent Wall - SW Naval Infinity, SW6244 Eggshell Ultra Deep.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Master Suite, everything else - SW Laid-back Beige, HGSW3127.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;“Drum Room”, multi-purpose room attached to the kitchen - HC141 Cemented Deal, Sherwin Williams. This is the only paint I’ve bought an actual paint store, as opposed to Lowe’s or Home Depot. Sherwin Williams had paint 40% off.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Office - Behr Pro Fresh Croissant, Eggshell, PR334.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Laundry Room - SW Swimming Eggshell, SW6764.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Alex’s Room - Behr Pro PR333, Exotic Blossom Eggshell.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Primer - Kilz Pro-X Interior Primer, P10. I do 2 coats of this when converting brown wood to white.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Trim - Behr Marquee Interior Gloss Enamel,  Semi-Brilliant, green can. I finish baseboards and other wood trim in a coat or two of this.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Exterior trim - Brevard Recycles Harmony, Exterior Latex. This was free paint from Ace Hardware.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This is a post for my own knowledge, to keep track of what colors I’ve painted what rooms in my house on Citrus.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Optimize Everything</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/optimize-everything/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Optimize Everything" /><published>2018-05-25T08:05:14-04:00</published><updated>2018-05-25T08:05:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/optimize-everything</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/optimize-everything/">&lt;p&gt;I’m a big believer in optimization and automation. One thing I like to optimize is my time. Here are 3 examples of how I do that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-lawn-and-pool-care&quot;&gt;1. Lawn and Pool Care&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I pay someone to mow my lawn, but not to do my pool. When I bought my house in May 2016, I mowed my own lawn with a terrible, 12” cut electric mower. It took forever. I paid the local pool store to do the cleaning and chemicals in my pool, which cost $100/mo.  After a few months, I decided to swap those services. Now I pay someone $65/mo to mow my lawn, and I learned how to do my own pool. I spend about $100/yr on pool chemicals, and I genuinely enjoy getting in the pool and using the vacuum. So by switching these 2 services, I saved $35/mo, which is $420/yr, minus the chemicals for the pool saves me $320/yr!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/optimize/pool.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Pool&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-bought-a-knockoff-roomba&quot;&gt;2. Bought a knockoff Roomba&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since we have a dog who sheds a bit, plus 4 people in a house, the floor can get messy, quick. I decided to buy a Roomba, but I wanted the nicest, best one on the market, which was the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KVWe6N&quot;&gt;Roomba 980&lt;/a&gt;. This sells for $8-900, but you can find them on sale and stack coupons to get them down to about $600. That’s more than I wanted to spend. I did a ton of research, and found the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2s6N4NG&quot;&gt;Xiaomi Mi Robot&lt;/a&gt;, which I bought off some sketchy Chinese website for $280, with 2 month shipping. The Xiaomi Mi Robot is comparable to the Roomba 980, has an app, can be scheduled, controlled remotely, and is very smart in its cleaning patterns. When we finally got the vacuum, we named him Roscoe (yeah, we named our vacuum), gave him a label-maker name tag, and set him up on a schedule. Roscoe cleans the house every weekday at 2PM, and does a great job. This has saved countless hours of vacuuming so far, and all I do is empty the dust bin every 3 or 4 days. The house has never looked better!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/optimize/roscoe.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Pool&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-walmart-grocery&quot;&gt;3. Walmart Grocery&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We used to shop at the Walmart Community Market, which is like a smaller Walmart with only groceries and household items. It was closer than the real Walmart, and you don’t have to deal with large crowds at the Walmart Community Market. Recently, the real Walmart near us started using &lt;a href=&quot;http://r.wmt.co/hKEvX&quot;&gt;Walmart Grocery&lt;/a&gt;, where you can order groceries online, set a time to pick them up, then when you arrive, a Walmart employee will bring them out to your car. There is no additional cost for this service. You park in dedicated parking spots on the side of the store, and never have to go inside. We started doing this at the beginning of 2018, and it’s amazing. I haven’t been in a grocery store in months, and I don’t impulse buy either! This also saves time and money. Use &lt;a href=&quot;http://r.wmt.co/hKEvX&quot;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt; for $10 off your Walmart Grocery order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There you have it, 3 simple ways I’ve optimized my time and money in 2018. If you have any other good optimization tips, leave them in comments!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I’m a big believer in optimization and automation. One thing I like to optimize is my time. Here are 3 examples of how I do that.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Calculating My Savings Rate</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/calculating-my-savings-rate/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Calculating My Savings Rate" /><published>2018-05-22T08:10:14-04:00</published><updated>2018-05-22T08:10:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/calculating-my-savings-rate</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/calculating-my-savings-rate/">&lt;p&gt;Savings rate is always talked about in the Financial Independence / Early Retirement (FI/RE) space. It’s been written about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mrmoneymustache.com/2012/01/13/the-shockingly-simple-math-behind-early-retirement/&quot;&gt;time&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://20somethingfinance.com/personal-savings-rate/&quot;&gt;time&lt;/a&gt; again, and everyone has a different thought on it.
I had never sat down and calculated mine, so here goes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My money is moving to multiple different investment accounts. I have my Fidelity 401k through work, a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.madfientist.com/ultimate-retirement-account/&quot;&gt;Optum HSA (Health Savings Account)&lt;/a&gt; through work, a Vanguard Roth IRA that is contributed to post-tax, I buy individual stocks through &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/robinhood/&quot;&gt;Robinhood&lt;/a&gt;, and a Vanguard taxable brokerage account that I put money in to save for a down payment on my next house. My income from work is $82,400 pre-tax, and is used for Savings Rate Calculations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note that these calculations do not include stock dividends, rent that my roommates provide to go towards my mortgage, or equity in my mortgage. This is my interpretation of a Savings Rate calculation.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;my-savings-rate-calculation&quot;&gt;My Savings Rate Calculation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fidelity 401k&lt;/strong&gt; - I contribute 22% of my pay (as close to $18,500 as possible) and my employer contributes 7% = 29% * $82,400 = $23,896&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optum HSA&lt;/strong&gt; - I contribute the maximum allowed = $3,450/yr&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vanguard Roth IRA&lt;/strong&gt; - I contribute the maximum allowed, as I have extra money throughout the year = $5,500/yr&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vanguard Taxable Brokerage&lt;/strong&gt; - I add $50 week = $50 * 52 = $2,600/yr&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/robinhood/&quot;&gt;Robinhood Individual Stocks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - I stopped with automatic contributions here, I still add about $100/mo = $100 * 12 = $1,200/yr
Total Invested Per Year = $36,646
Divided by Salary = $36,646 / $82,400 = 44.5%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There you have it, almost a 45% savings rate. Considering the &lt;a href=&quot;https://fred.stlouisfed.org/series/PSAVERT&quot;&gt;average savings rate&lt;/a&gt; in America was 3.1% at the time of writing, I think I’m saving pretty well. It is difficult when checking the pay stub from work, seeing your income, but then seeing almost half of your income directed to other accounts you can’t spend. I’m glad I got into the habit of not taking my entire paycheck to a bank account!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Savings rate is always talked about in the Financial Independence / Early Retirement (FI/RE) space. It’s been written about time and time again, and everyone has a different thought on it. I had never sat down and calculated mine, so here goes.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hallway Bookshelves</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hallway-bookshelves/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hallway Bookshelves" /><published>2018-05-22T08:05:14-04:00</published><updated>2018-05-22T08:05:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hallway-bookshelves</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hallway-bookshelves/">&lt;p&gt;I made some simple hallway bookshelves. They cost $43 and a few hours of my time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bookshelves/pre.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bookshelves&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Materials included brackets and a piece of 3/4” MDF, cut down to 2 pieces of 9” x 24”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bookshelves/paint.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bookshelves&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These were then sanded, given 2 coats of primer, then a final coat of Behr white paint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bookshelves/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bookshelves&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make sure to use a level on your brackets, both vertically and horizontally. I used a large textbook to guess how far apart the shelves should be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bookshelves/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bookshelves&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lumber was $13, the 4 brackets were $30, and I already owned the paint and brushes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bookshelves/attached.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bookshelves&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s the final product with some books! Total of $43 and about 2 hours of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bookshelves/done.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bookshelves&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I made some simple hallway bookshelves. They cost $43 and a few hours of my time.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fiat 500 Steering Column Fix</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/fiat-500-steering-column-fix/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fiat 500 Steering Column Fix" /><published>2018-05-21T10:05:14-04:00</published><updated>2018-05-21T10:05:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/fiat-500-steering-column-fix</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/fiat-500-steering-column-fix/">&lt;p&gt;My fiancé has a 2013 Fiat 500, which has been a great little car. Great gas mileage, easy to drive, hardly any issues in almost 60,000 miles! The window regulator broke on the passenger side, which was fixed at the dealer for $300, just out of warranty. The steering wheel column cover also broke, and the dealer wanted $600 to fix that, so I decided to see what I could do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fiat/removed.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fiat&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The steering column cover is 2 pieces of plastic that sit around the steering column, and has openings for the ignition, wiper stalk, and turn signal stalk. The bottom plastic piece is attached to the column by 2 short screws (shown above), which sit on small plastic spacer sections of the lower piece. These plastic pieces are fragile, and broke about a year ago. This means the 2 pieces of plastic are just flapping around while driving, not secured to anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fiat/halfoff.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fiat&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took the entire assembly off, found 2 longer screws and washers that would secure the plastic bottom piece to the steering column. I attached both and tightened them up, but found that it made the ignition hard to use, and the turn signal stalk was obstructed. It was secured too tight. I ended up removed 1 of the screw and washer sets, so that just 1 remains, and it is as secure as it was when new, but it won’t break this time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fiat/complete.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fiat&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">My fiancé has a 2013 Fiat 500, which has been a great little car. Great gas mileage, easy to drive, hardly any issues in almost 60,000 miles! The window regulator broke on the passenger side, which was fixed at the dealer for $300, just out of warranty. The steering wheel column cover also broke, and the dealer wanted $600 to fix that, so I decided to see what I could do.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pool Enclosure Replacement</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/pool-enclosure-replacement/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pool Enclosure Replacement" /><published>2018-05-16T10:05:14-04:00</published><updated>2018-05-16T10:05:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/pool-enclosure-replacement</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/pool-enclosure-replacement/">&lt;p&gt;I had a pool enclosure on my house, it was likely built along with the pool in the 80s or 90s. These enclosures are common to have over Florida pools to keep leaves and bugs out. Some people call them screen, cages, bird cages, enclosures, etc. I had a few screen panels blown out in 2016 during Hurricane Matthew, and the guy who replaced them said I’d be lucky if my enclosure lasted 5 more years. It lasted 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My old pool enclosure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/before_irma.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Irma destoryed that enclosure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/irma.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hurricane Irma destroyed my original enclosure in September 2017. I got 4 quotes to replace the enclosure, along with a few screen on my front porch. I finally got an insurance check for about $9,000 in January 2018, and then got 4 quotes. The quotes were:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;$14,242 with a 6 month lead time. 100% down.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;$11,940 with a 4 month lead time. 10% down, 90% due at completion.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;$9,985 with a 4 month lead time. 60% down, 40% due at completion.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;$10,685 with a 3 month lead time. 0% down, 100% due at completion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went with the 4th company, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.palmbayaluminum.com&quot;&gt;Palm Bay Aluminum&lt;/a&gt;, even though they weren’t the cheapest. The cheapest required 60% of the cost up front, but Palm Bay Aluminum asked for 0% down and 100% at completion. Leaving my money invested for those 4 months earned me about $200 interest anyways, so the price difference was about $500 after factoring that in. Not having to carry the risk of some aluminum company having lots of my money before even starting a project was worth it for me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My screen was started on April 17 and took about 4 days to finish the install. The front screens were completed shortly after, and the permit signed off and inspected on May 4, 2018. Until the screen was started, I had this chicken wire fence around the pool, to keep the dogs in and because it is a law to have some sort of fence around your pool. It looked terrible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/before.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Palm Bay Aluminum started by removing the old gutter and prepping the existing metal roof area for attachments. They ended up adding a 3” beam of aluminum for better structural integrity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/prep.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s all the aluminum and parts they needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/materials.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the new “super gutter” installed. The old gutter only went the length of the roof on the house, and didn’t have a gutter attached to the metal roof area above the Florida room (where you can see the step). The new super gutter runs the entire length, which is stronger, better for water flow, and looks way better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/gutter.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I thought was interesting is that the assemblers build the entire roof in the front yard in pieces, then walk it to the back and and raise it, then place a wall under it. The roof is screened before being raised into place. It makes a ton of sense! The new roof is a Mansard style, which is stronger than the box gable style that the old screen was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/front_yard_assembly.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/front_yard_assembly_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/raising.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/up.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got them to install a dog door for Bentley, and it is super sturdy. It’s a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2L54qCF&quot;&gt;Magnador&lt;/a&gt;, which is framed in with aluminum. It has magnets on the bottom and flap in order to keep the flap at its lowest position. It also has locks so that you can lock the dog in or out, or if you don’t have a dog you can lock it to ensure no other creatures figure out the door. I got the biggest size possible, since Bentley is a pretty big dog at 65 pounds. The additional cost to install and frame the dog door in was $125, on top of the previously stated prices above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/side.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/far_side.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/bentley.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/dog_door.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoying one of my favorite beers the first day with a screen!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/huna.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is how they joined the super gutter into the existing downspout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/gutter_attached.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the screen was up, Alex and I (but mostly Alex) got to work installing lighting. There were awesome string lights in a zig-zag pattern on the old enclosure which were hooked up to an on/off switch, we wanted that same functionality, but better. Alex hooked up a system with pulleys that required attaching hooks at the top most point and a lower point on each side, so we needed to get up there. He made a ladder thing that went across the pool so you could reach the top with a 10 ft ladder. Check it out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/ladder.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/alex.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bentley also found a new way to sit, with his tail just hanging into the water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/bentley_sitting.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As far as the electrical, each beam of the roof has its own outlet, which is run through black conduit. So there are 5 outlets for the 5 strands of lights, and the strands can be pulled in and out easily as they are on wire. The lights are just in a staggered pattern now, no zig-zags like before. I think I’ll replace the light strands with Christmas lights in December!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/electrical_in_progress.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/electrical_in_progress_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/electrical.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The grey switch is the on/off switch for the lights, and it turns on all 5 sets of lights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/lights_off.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Notice the enclosure opposite mine is a box gable roof, like my old one was. It looks like a triangle at the end. The new style is different, more squared. The result is a higher maximum roof height!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/lights_on.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m very pleased with the new enclosure, the lights, the dog door, and Alex and Palm Bay Aluminum’s work!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pool/night.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I had a pool enclosure on my house, it was likely built along with the pool in the 80s or 90s. These enclosures are common to have over Florida pools to keep leaves and bugs out. Some people call them screen, cages, bird cages, enclosures, etc. I had a few screen panels blown out in 2016 during Hurricane Matthew, and the guy who replaced them said I’d be lucky if my enclosure lasted 5 more years. It lasted 1.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">$500 Weekend Bathroom Remodel</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/$500-bathroom-remodel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="$500 Weekend Bathroom Remodel" /><published>2018-04-30T01:05:14-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-30T01:05:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/$500-bathroom-remodel</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/$500-bathroom-remodel/">&lt;p&gt;I completed a quick bathroom remodel the weekend on the guest bathroom with the help of my fiancés mom, (Cindy) and one of my roommates (Alex). I kept the existing vanity and shower, but gave everything a nice touchup. The changes included new paint on the walls and vanity cabinets, new towel and toilet paper holders, new mirror, new vanity light, new baseboards, and a new curved shower rod curtain. Both the shower rod curtain and vanity light are the same model as in the master bathroom we remodeled recently. I kept the existing over the toilet wall mounted storage, since it’s in good shape. Here are the before pictures:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/before1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/before2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/before3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/before4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The vanity top was pretty nice, but the cabinets were yellow (WHY) and the hardware was bad. I took the vanity doors and hardware off, and painted everything with 2 coats of primer (Kilz) and 2 coats of a white finish coat (Behr). I bought new hinges and handles to finish it off, along with lots of caulk and wood fill to mask the previous imperfections in the cabinets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/cabinets1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cabinets&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/cabinets2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cabinets&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/cabinets3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cabinets&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/cabinets4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cabinets&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before painting, I took off the old school toothbrush holder, toilet paper holder and towel holder. They were plastered in, so I did as good a job as I can with re-drywalling and patching. We bought 1 gallon of a green paint, and didn’t even use half of it.  Cindy was a huge help with the painting. Notice the blue outlines on the mirror - that’s the size of the new medicine cabinet mirror.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/process1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Process&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/process2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Process&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/process3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Process&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/process4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Process&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were also 2 hooks on the ceiling, maybe for hanging plants? They were above the old vanity light. I took the hooks down and plastered and painted over them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/process5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Process&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/process6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Process&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/process7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Process&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since we painted before installing the new vanity light, it was dark in the bathroom. There are no windows! We used a work lamp to paint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/process8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Process&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/process9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Process&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/process10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Process&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/process11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Process&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/process12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Process&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/process13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Process&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/process14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Process&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This bathroom doesn’t have pull out drawers in the vanity, they’re blanks, so there isn’t much storage. I decided to buy the biggest medicine cabinet I could find, which was 48” x 30”. It’s almost as big as the old mirror was. This gives more storage and a more modern look. A new vanity light helped as well. I installed a dual curved shower curtain holder, so you can hang towels on the outside and people can still shower. The toilet paper holder has a storage spot on top for baby wipes. Alex was helpful in installing all the new wall hanging hardware.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/shower.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Done&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The old shower tile doesn’t match great with the new bathroom, but it’ll get retiled…eventually… This is nice for now. There’s enough storage for my roommates to keep their stuff off of the vanity so that guests can have a nicer bathroom, and the room seems so much bigger now that it’s actually nice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/final1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Done&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/final2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Done&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/final3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Done&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the costs, I bought most of the smaller items off Amazon, the Mirrored Medicine Cabinet was bought in person from Home Depot, and the Vanity Light was bought online from Lowe’s with a coupon. I already had the primer and white paint, tools, paintbrushes, drywall, etc. Here’s the breakdown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;final-expenses&quot;&gt;Final Expenses:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.homedepot.com/p/Glacier-Bay-48-in-x-30-in-Frameless-Surface-Mount-Bathroom-Medicine-Cabinet-in-White-T48-BM/100557237&quot;&gt;Mirrored Medicine Cabinet&lt;/a&gt; $150&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lowes.com/pd/allen-roth-Merington-5-Light-37-5-in-Brushed-Nickel-Vanity-Light-Bar/50432422&quot;&gt;Vanity Light&lt;/a&gt; $100&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Paint $38&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Caulk $6&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cabinet Hardware $50&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2Fv57Rp&quot;&gt;Towel Bar&lt;/a&gt; $19&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2JDW7fk&quot;&gt;Hand Towel Holder&lt;/a&gt; $17&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2JAuqEf&quot;&gt;Toilet Paper Holder&lt;/a&gt; $12&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2Fu8055&quot;&gt;Double Shower Curtain Rod&lt;/a&gt; $35&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;total-428&quot;&gt;Total: $428!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was under $500, sweet! As a bonus, here’s a picture of a 48” x 30” mirrored medicine cabinet in the back of the Corvette. The guy at Home Depot who helped me load it in was skeptical, but this car is as practical as any truck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bathroom/itfits.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bonus&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I completed a quick bathroom remodel the weekend on the guest bathroom with the help of my fiancés mom, (Cindy) and one of my roommates (Alex). I kept the existing vanity and shower, but gave everything a nice touchup. The changes included new paint on the walls and vanity cabinets, new towel and toilet paper holders, new mirror, new vanity light, new baseboards, and a new curved shower rod curtain. Both the shower rod curtain and vanity light are the same model as in the master bathroom we remodeled recently. I kept the existing over the toilet wall mounted storage, since it’s in good shape. Here are the before pictures:</summary></entry></feed>