<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-10-07T10:14:39-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Robert Skelton</title><subtitle>Finance | Tech | Cars | Renovations | Etc</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Radar Detector Hardwire</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Radar-Hardwire/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Radar Detector Hardwire" /><published>2019-10-07T07:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-10-07T07:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Radar-Hardwire</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Radar-Hardwire/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently put my Corvette on the market, so I took the hardwired radar detector out of it. Might as well put it in the GX!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2pSNAke&quot;&gt;RJ11 power cord&lt;/a&gt; that has a simple power and ground, with the goal to get power behind the mirror. It was ridiculously easy, the easiest of any car I’ve ever done. There are 2 wires behind the rearview mirror that are exposed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In spot 1 there is a blue/white cord, and in spot 2 there is a black/white cord.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Put your power from the radar cord (red) into spot 1 with the blue/white cord. Put the ground (black) into spot 2, the black/white cord. I then wrapped a bit of black electrical tape around the power cord and the other wires running into the mirror, to keep everything from moving around too much. Plug in your radar detector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have power when the car is on, and the power drops when the car is turned off. Perfect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/radar/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Radar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wrapped the cord once around my mirror, since it was a little long, then mounted it with the normal suction cup mounts, which aren’t great. If you’re doing any off road driving, you’ll want to take your detector down, or get a &lt;a href=&quot;https://blendmount.com/&quot;&gt;Blendmount&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2pSNAke&quot;&gt;Escort radar detector&lt;/a&gt;, these detectors have great sensitivity, but you can dial it back and customize them how you like them. I actually use an older model 8500 X50 that I bought for my first Corvette.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lexus GX470 Custom Webbing Dog Divider</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Custom-Webbing-Dog-Divider/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lexus GX470 Custom Webbing Dog Divider" /><published>2019-08-09T07:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-08-09T07:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/GX470-Custom-Webbing-Dog-Divider</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/GX470-Custom-Webbing-Dog-Divider/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/26.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a big dog, Bentley, a 75 pound lab mix, who loves being in the front of the GX when I’m driving. Only issue is, he’s a 75 pound dog. So I wanted a webbing divider to keep him in the 3rd row area, but the only one on the market that is made to fit the GX starts at $180! I used &lt;a href=&quot;https://raingler.com/collections/lexus-heavy-duty-cargo-netting/products/lexus-gx-j120-barrier-divider&quot;&gt;this product from Raingler&lt;/a&gt; as my inspiration, and started to plan how to make my own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Raingler divider uses stitching for the joints, and I can sew, but I don’t have a sewing machine. The type of stitches used to sew together an intersection of webbing really requires a sewing machine (or thousands of hour of free time which I don’t have), so I found some other projects that had used grommets to assemble webbing. I decided to go this route, and purchased the following parts on Amazon, which ran me about $60.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Parts Bought&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KpyTwR&quot;&gt;4x Frontmans Loops&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/31vmj4C&quot;&gt;4x D Rings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KBZxBr&quot;&gt;6x Carabiners&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2YUjQiP&quot;&gt;10-12 yards of Webbing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KpSf4S&quot;&gt;Grommet Kit with 100 grommets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tools Needed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hammer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Scissors&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lighter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Drill with a bit that can drill through metal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For mounting the divider, it needs to have something to attach to on the inside of the car. I noticed the Raingler product added some mount points into the body, inside of the panels, so I did that. I pulled back the panels on both sides of the car, right behind the second row seats, and found 2 spots I could drill in to on each side. This gives 2 mount points per side, plus a 3rd mount point per side on the bottom of the middle seats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I put 1 &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KpyTwR&quot;&gt;Frontmans Loop&lt;/a&gt; at each spot, with about a 10” strip of webbing, with a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/31vmj4C&quot;&gt;D ring&lt;/a&gt; on the other end. For making these connection pieces, I made them before putting them in the car. I cut a strip of webbing, then used the grommet punch to make holes. Make sure you burn off the loose strings on the ends of the webbing and the holes. Then, I used the grommet die to put a grommet in, with a Frontmans Loop on one side a D ring on the other. This was my first time using grommets, and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KpSf4S&quot;&gt;kit&lt;/a&gt; I bought was actually pretty easy to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did this for 2 spots on the drivers side and 2 spots on the passenger side, and fed the top connector piece above the panel, and the bottom connector piece between the 2 panels I had to pull off. The most difficult part of this whole project was drilling into the metal body panels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I decided I wanted the webbing to be able to flex with the middle seats being up or down. Turns out, the distance between the mount point on the seats being up or down and the mount point I added was only a 2” difference, so I used the longer measurement. Here’s my chicken scratch measurements, I cut and built my divider using the bottom diagram. 34” along the top mounting points I added, 46” in the middle mount points I added, and 30” for the 2 mount points built in on the middle seats. The vertical strip from the top to middle was 21”, and from middle to bottom was 14”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made the perimeter first, and made sure it fit on the mount points I had added and the back of the middle row seats. All fits! The hardest part was where 3 different strips intersected. I was worried the grommet would be too small to contain all 3 pieces of webbing, but it held great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/16.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/17.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/18.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I added another horizontal strip and started adding a few vertical strips, putting grommets at every intersection along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/19.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/20.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/21.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All done, then just install it! You can see the webbing flexes enough that the middle row can be up or down, however the middle row can not recline much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/21.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/22.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/24.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It took about 3 hours and $60 of parts to build a webbing barrier that is perfect for Bentley, and I have enough leftover parts, webbing, and carabiners that I could make a second one, or any other cool webbing things. I can also add many more vertical and horizontal strips. This was made to keep our lab in the back. We also have a 12 pound Cavalier, and she can fit through the nets, but that’s OK, she doesn’t get in my way when I drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any questions, feel free to comment, or ask me in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/LexusGXOR/?ref=group_header&quot;&gt;GXOR Facebook group&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/dogs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Update, 1 day later: I had to add 2 more vertical strips, since Bentley jumped through them once he saw we had Chick-fil-A in the front seat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/25.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/divider/26.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Divider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Format an Audio USB for a C7 Corvette from a Mac</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Format-Audio-USB-for-C7-Corvette-From-Mac/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Format an Audio USB for a C7 Corvette from a Mac" /><published>2019-07-29T12:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-07-29T12:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Format-Audio-USB-for-C7-Corvette-From-Mac</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Format-Audio-USB-for-C7-Corvette-From-Mac/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/vette/plug.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.  Insert a &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2OpmYmB&quot;&gt;USB drive&lt;/a&gt; into your Mac&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.  Open disk utility.&lt;/strong&gt; This is under Applications &amp;gt; Utilities &amp;gt; Disk Utility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/vette/1.png&quot; alt=&quot;1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.  Eject the partition.&lt;/strong&gt;
This is listed below the USB Drive name itself, and has an eject button to the right. Labeled “2” in the picture above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4.  Format the USB&lt;/strong&gt;
Click on the USB Name, then Erase. Select Format MS-DOS and Scheme “Master Boot Record”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Format the partition&lt;/strong&gt;
Click on the partition below it that was just created, then Erase. Select format MS-DOS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/vette/2.png&quot; alt=&quot;2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Add Audio Files&lt;/strong&gt;
Find your USB drive and drag and drop audio files onto it. Most people seem to recommend playlists, since those will play non stop in your Vette.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7. Put in in your Vette&lt;/strong&gt;
Plug your USB drive into the USB slot either behind the dash, or under the center console. Either one works for audio, in a 2016 at least.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How To Save Money on Large Purchases</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/How-To-Save-Money-On-Large-Purchases/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How To Save Money on Large Purchases" /><published>2019-07-18T12:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-07-18T12:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/How-To-Save-Money-On-Large-Purchases</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/How-To-Save-Money-On-Large-Purchases/">&lt;p&gt;If you do any amount of online shopping, using some of the following tips can save you some money!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;rakuten&quot;&gt;Rakuten&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rakuten.com/r/ROBERT47769?eeid=43662&amp;amp;utm_source=extension&amp;amp;utm_medium=raf_link&quot;&gt;Rakuten&lt;/a&gt;, formerly called Ebates. This is a browser extension that helps you to earn cash back on purchases at certain retailers. It will also suggest other retailers if you can get the same item at a cheaper price. I have &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/using-rakuten-for-more-cashback&quot;&gt;wrote about Rakuten before&lt;/a&gt;, and I’ve earned about $350 in cash back since 2016. I recently needed to buy a new range and microwave, and the ones I decided on were about $1300 at Home Depot. My Rakuten extension popped up and said I could buy the same models at ABT.com for about $1100, and they give 6% back at Rakuten, which is $66 back!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/ebates/rakuten.png&quot; alt=&quot;Rakuten&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;credit-card-cash-back&quot;&gt;Credit Card Cash Back&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one is obvious, but you can pay with credit cards to earn some more cash back. Some cards have rotating categories, so will give higher percentage cash back at certain retailers, but only during certain quarters. The Chase Freedom and Discover IT cards are examples of these cards. A great example here is that for Q3 2019, which is the current quarter as I write this article, Discover is 5% back on Paypal purchases. As I was checking out at ABT.com for my new appliances (mentioned above), they had the option to check out with Paypal, so I did with my Discover IT card. At 5% of $1100, that is $55 cash back, on top of the $66 I got from Rakuten. So using Rakuten and the right credit card got me from $1300 to $1100 - $66 - $55 = under $1000! Nice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;honey&quot;&gt;Honey&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://joinhoney.com/ref/dsskgi&quot;&gt;Honey&lt;/a&gt; is very similar to Rakuten, but I don’t think it does as good of a job at giving cash back. It gives cash back in the form of “Honey Gold”, which you can buy gift cards with. The nice feature of Honey is that it will automatically try coupon codes! Lots of  ecommerce sites have discount codes or coupon codes, that are sometimes not public. Honey has a list of these, and will try to use all of them. I like to get the discount code from Honey, then use Rakuten for their cash back. You can not earn both cash back through Rakuten AND Honey Gold. If you click on one after the other, one will pop up saying that you can’t earn for both cash back portals, so pick and choose which one works best for your given transaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/ebates/honey1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Honey&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/ebates/honey2.png&quot; alt=&quot;Honey&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;slickdeals&quot;&gt;Slickdeals&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://slickdeals.net/&quot;&gt;Slickdeals&lt;/a&gt; is the classic website for finding things that are on sale. You can set up email alerts for items you are interested in. I did this with some $60 Sennheiser headphones that I knew went on sale pretty often. I set up the emails, and bought them a few months later for $28. This site is mostly focused on technology products, but there are tons of other products on here. I’ve bought some clothes and dry food products that I’ve seen on Slickdeals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;home-depot-and-lowes-10-off-codes&quot;&gt;Home Depot and Lowe’s 10% Off Codes&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re making a large purchase at Home Depot or Lowe’s, it can behoove you buy online and use a coupon code. You can generate them, somehow (search the Slickdeals forums if you are interested), or you can buy them for a few bucks. When you’re spending $1,000 on flooring, it’s worth it to spend $5 to get a 10% coupon, which will save you $95. I’ve bought &lt;a href=&quot;https://lowescoupon.info/&quot;&gt;Lowe’s coupons here&lt;/a&gt; and found free ones &lt;a href=&quot;https://renovopower.com/lowes.html&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, though I am not affiliated with either website. You can also fill out a &lt;a href=&quot;https://moversguide.usps.com/mgo/disclaimer?referral=MG80&quot;&gt;USPS Change of Address form&lt;/a&gt;, and they send you a welcome kit. This usually includes a 10% off coupon to both Home Depot and Lowe’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;bumped&quot;&gt;Bumped&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bumped.com/?ref=8ad7cc96&quot;&gt;Bumped&lt;/a&gt; is an app that you give access to your credit card transactions, and you can earn stocks based on what retailers you shop at. You get a choice of 1 retailer per category, and they are called “Loyalties”. For example, Home Improvement is a category. I chose Home Depot over Lowe’s, since I shop at Home Depot much more. When Bumped notices a transaction on any of my linked credits cards from Home Depot, it’ll give me a small percentage of that purchase as a stock, 1% at Home Depot. There are tons of categories. I don’t ever count on this, but I set it up a few months ago and I’ve earned about $30 in stocks from just doing normal shopping. This is a new application, so the app is still a bit buggy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/ebates/bumped.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bumped&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;camelcamelcamel&quot;&gt;CamelCamelCamel&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is one I don’t use that often, since I don’t a ton of Amazon shopping, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://camelcamelcamel.com/&quot;&gt;CamelCamelCamel&lt;/a&gt; is a Amazon price history. You can install it as a browser extension, and see the price of an item over time. Honey does a lot of the same things.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">If you do any amount of online shopping, using some of the following tips can save you some money!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Recipe - Keto Chocolate Milkshake</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Keto-Chocolate-Milkshake/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Recipe - Keto Chocolate Milkshake" /><published>2019-07-12T09:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-07-12T09:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Keto-Chocolate-Milkshake</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Keto-Chocolate-Milkshake/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/recipes/milkshake.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ingredients&quot;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 Cups Ice&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3 Tbsp &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2l2Cern&quot;&gt;Swerve&lt;/a&gt;, or similar Keto confectioners sugar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3/4 Cup Heavy Whipping Cream&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1.5 Cups Almond Milk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 scoops &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2l2Cern&quot;&gt;Protein Powder&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;instructions&quot;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Put everything in blender&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Blend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pros and Cons of Working From Home</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Pros-and-Cons-of-Working-From-Home/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pros and Cons of Working From Home" /><published>2019-07-10T09:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-07-10T09:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Pros-and-Cons-of-Working-From-Home</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Pros-and-Cons-of-Working-From-Home/">&lt;p&gt;I’ve been working from home full time for over 2.5 years, and it is a major benefit of my current position. Remote work offers some great benefits, but also some notable cons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;pros&quot;&gt;Pros&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.  No commute!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This saves so much time! You don’t even need a car when you have no commute, so &lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/drive-cool-cars-on-a-budget/&quot;&gt;I have 2&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.  Work with dog(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife and I have 2 dogs, and I get to be at home with them all day. This means no hiring dog sitters, and our pups aren’t always bored.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/wfh/dogs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Dogs&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Make Your Office How You Like It&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought multiple computer monitors, a nice speaker system, decorated my walls, and I can light candles every day! In a shared office environment, you just get what they provide, unless you want to drag it to and from work every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/wfh/office.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Office&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Listen to music without headphones&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Music through speakers is better, and I don’t get tired of having headphones on or in my ears like I did when shared an office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Your Time is More Flexible&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can cook lunch most days and have it ready when my wife comes home from work. If I get frustrated, I can go outside, clean, or go do a load of laundry. I have the privacy to make phone calls without having to find a huddle room or empty office. I can walk out of the office, get quotes from contractors, and can run errands easier than being in a shared office. There seems to much less of a stigma of taking time off from work when you are remote, as opposed to in person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. No Dress Code&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wear gym shorts and t-shirts to work every day. This can also be a con, since I usually look like a slob. It’s also a bit backwards, since I do most of my dressing up on the weekends, when most people dress down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7. More focused working time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can get more high quality work in less hours than in a shared office since I no longer have people tapping on my shoulder for help, or co-workers stopping by to chat. There is no “office water cooler” when you work from home, which means less distractions while working. This can be a huge advantage when writing code, which is a task that requires lots of concentration, at least for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8. Work where you want&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I usually work at my office desk, where I have 3 monitors, speakers, mouse, keyboard, etc. A nice working setup. But occasionally, I’ll want to do training or take meetings and get out of that office. I can go sit in a recliner for a meeting in the living room, or sit by the pool to do some technical training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/wfh/pool.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Pool&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;cons&quot;&gt;Cons&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Cabin Fever&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t notice being cooped up inside as a negative for the first 2 years, but in the last half a year I have been getting stir crazy. I seem to leave my house once a week, and barely get outside off of my property. It has been a recent goal of mine to start getting out of the house more often. I’ve started a trivia group on Thursdays to socialize more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Hard to Shut Off Work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have work email on my phone. If I see an email at 9PM, and it is something that just takes a second to do, I’ll go over to my office and do it. Downside, I then spend another 30 minutes doing other stuff, and I never seem to truly disconnect from work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. The A/C bill&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still have to pay my own power bill, and I live in Florida. That means that if I’m not running the A/C, it will get HOT inside. I keep it at 77-78F most days, but that still adds up. It used to keep the house at 80F during work hours, before I started working here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Less Reliable Internet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corporate offices often have business internet connections, which are more reliable and quicker. I have a 150MB home internet connection, which is fast, but tends to be less reliable. I also had to supply my own internet connection hardware, like the modem and router. These are expenses I would have had normally, but when you’re home 24/7, you care more about a great internet connection than normal. Therefore, I bought a nicer, expensive router recently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Less Connected to Co-Workers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a shared office, you can walk up to your coworkers to get advice or help, and you see them in person at meeting often. In a remote work environment, I occasionally see my team members on Skype video, but it’s usually just audio. We communicate mostly via chat platforms at work, which is a bit more difficult to get things done than if you are sitting next to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Conflicting off days&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife has Tuesdays and Sundays off. I work on Tuesdays. This means that I’m at home trying to work, and she’s at home not working on Tuesdays.   I also used to have a roommate that would have every other Friday off, and I worked those Fridays. He would sit around and play video games all day, which was annoying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Snacks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This could be a pro for some, but I’m always 20 steps from my kitchen, stocked with snacks and food. And I have terrible self control with food, so I am always snacking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, the last 2.5 years working from home have been a wonderful way to work (if you have to work), and I would take remote work over an in person shared office every day. I have learned a few lessons on how to manage working from home though, like setting boundaries on when to start and stop working, how to focus more and be more productive, and to talk to your team members more, even if it is just about their personal lives. Working from home is a great move in the IT and Software disciplines, and I’d recommend employees and managers alike to give it a shot.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I’ve been working from home full time for over 2.5 years, and it is a major benefit of my current position. Remote work offers some great benefits, but also some notable cons.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Honeymoon in Costa Rica</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Honeymoon-In-Costa-Rica/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Honeymoon in Costa Rica" /><published>2019-06-18T09:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-06-18T09:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Honeymoon-In-Costa-Rica</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Honeymoon-In-Costa-Rica/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/map.png&quot; alt=&quot;Map&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife, Elizabeth, and I got married on May 26, 2019, and left for our honeymoon to Costa Rica the next day. We drove from Melbourne, FL to Ft Lauderdale, FL to fly on JetBlue. A direct flight from FLL to SJO, it was about $500 for both of us, and bags were included with my JetBlue credit card. We spent 7 days and 6 nights in Costa Rica, and visited 5 provinces: San Jose, Alajuela, Guanacaste, Heredia, and Puntarenas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/tacobell1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;TacoBell&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;rental-car&quot;&gt;Rental Car&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We rented a Toyota Land Cruise Prado (the Toyota version of my Lexus GX470) from National Rental Car in San Jose, but not at the airport. The pickup location was Hotel Marriott Costa Rica, which was about 10 minutes away from the SJO airport. We found a free shuttle from National at the rental car kiosk in the airport. If you pick up outside of the airport, you avoid a large airport pickup tax. We also used promo code “MEMPHIS” for 10% off, prepaid with a Visa Signature credit card for another 10% off, and declined the LDW insurance. Car rentals require both SLC and LDW insurance. However, you can decline the LDW if you have a credit card that covers it, and you print out and bring the credit card agreement. My Capital One Venture is a Visa Signature, so we paid with that. The Prado was awesome, and we only paid about $340 to drive it for a week. We put 850 miles on it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/prado1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Prado&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/prado2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Prado&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;day-1---san-jose&quot;&gt;Day 1 - San Jose&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Landed in San Jose, got our rental car, checked in to Apartotel La Sabana. It was so rainy, so we did nothing but get room service and stay in. This place was $76/night, and was nothing fancy. The pool looked great (but it was rainy) and there was a sauna, but the room was cramped and not great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/view2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;View&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;day-2---san-jose-to-la-paz-to-heliconias&quot;&gt;Day 2 - San Jose to La Paz to Heliconias&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Woke up and got a great Costa Rican breakfast at Apartotel La Sabana. That made the room worth it. We drove about 1.5 hours to the La Paz waterfall gardens, which was incredible. La Paz entrance was $125 for 2 people. We saw lots of birds, sloths, jungle cats, and beautiful waterfalls, and also had an awesome buffet. This might be our most recommended attraction we visited in Costa Rica.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lapaz11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LaPaz&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a lot of hours here, we drove another 2 hours (stopping at McDonalds along the way) to the Heliconias Nature Lodge, and checked in to their Deluxe Treehouse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mcd1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;McDonalds&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mcd2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;McDonalds&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We ordered room service, and enjoyed the awesome room! This room at Heliconias was $270/night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lodge1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lodge&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;day-3---la-fortuna&quot;&gt;Day 3 - La Fortuna&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Woke up and had another great Costa Rican breakfast at the Heliconias Nature Lodge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lodge2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lodge&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drove in to La Fortuna and did some white water rafting with the Desafio Adventure Company down the Balsa River. Afterwards, they provided a lunch buffet at their restaurant. This trip was $150 for 2 people, which we though was a great value. The guides and the food were great!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lodge3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lodge&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lodge4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lodge&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We drove back to the Nature Lodge, relaxed a bit, then drove back in to La Fortuna to visit the EcoTermales Hot Springs. It was $80 for 2 people. We loved the hot springs, but were disappointed with the food. We paid $20 each for a below average buffet. Other than the food, the hot springs were awesome. Great drinks, not too crowded, lots of hot water. Then we drove back to the Nature Lodge and went to sleep early.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/hs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ecotermales&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;day-4---la-fortuna-to-secrets&quot;&gt;Day 4 - La Fortuna to Secrets&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Woke up super early and went on a 6AM Bird Watching Tour, which cost $135 for 2 people and included some fruit. We saw lots of local birds (and dogs) and our guide was very knowledgable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/bird1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bird&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/bird2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bird&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This close up picture of a bird is a Motmot, taken on a Galaxy S8 through a monocular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/bird3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bird&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, we had another Costa Rican breakfast at Heliconias Nature Lodge. The staff here was super friendly. We checked out of this hotel and drove to the La Fortuna Waterfall. It was a ton of stairs to get there, but it was beautiful. It poured here, but luckily not until we were about ready to leave. The waterfall entrance was $36 for 2 people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lafortuna1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;La Fortuna&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lafortuna2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;La Fortuna&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lafortuna3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;La Fortuna&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/lafortuna4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;La Fortuna&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then we drove to the Mistico Arenal Hanging Bridges Park. This place was actually closed for bad weather when we got there, so we got some food at their restaurant, and they opened about 30 minutes later. There are lots of hanging suspension bridges, great views of the Arenal volcano, and wildlife. It involved lots of hiking. We were already pretty exhausted from all the walking and hiking we had done the last few days, so we didn’t even see the whole park. We did see coati though, which we had never seen before! Mistico was $80 for 2 people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mistico1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mistico&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mistico2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mistico&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mistico3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mistico&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mistico4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mistico&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mistico5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mistico&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mistico6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mistico&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/mistico7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mistico&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, we drove to the Secrets Papagayo resort, about a 3 hour drive. Google Maps sent us down this insane mud road that was about 60 degrees uphill. Our car could handle it, but I could not. We turned around and took a detour, which added about 30 minutes. We got to our resort pretty late at night, and checked in to our room. They had prepped it for our honeymoon, with a sign and a bottle of champage!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/secrets1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Secrets1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;day-5---secrets&quot;&gt;Day 5 - Secrets&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This all inclusive resort was full of other couples on their honeymoons, and that was about it. Everyone had a honeymoon on their door! It was $430/night for 2 people, and of course included all of our food and drinks. So that’s what we did. We ate and drank and sat by the pool. We ordered room service, like 5 times. Then we went to their spa that night, my first time at a spa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/secrets2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Secrets1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/secrets3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Secrets1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/secrets4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Secrets1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/secrets5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Secrets1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;day-6---drive-back-to-san-jose&quot;&gt;Day 6 - Drive back to San Jose&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We just drove from Secrets back to San Jose this day. We stopped at another Taco Bell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/tacobell2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;TacoBell&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We stayed at the AC Hotel, which my Dad bought for us as a gift using points. Well, he is some sort of fancy membership level at Marriott, so they upgraded us to their penthouse suite and gave us free breakfast! It was probably one of the coolest hotel rooms we’ve every stayed in. It had a bedroom, living room, kitchen, 1.5 baths, and the biggest master bathroom I’ve ever been in. We walked around the area that the hotel was in, which is a new upscale shopping area. They also had a Lexus dealer with a LFA in stock. We ate dinner at PF Chang’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/sanjose1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Jose&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/sanjose2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Jose&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/sanjose3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Jose&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/sanjose4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Jose&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;day-7---return-home&quot;&gt;Day 7 - Return home&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The breakfast buffet at the AC Hotel was great. We checked out of the hotel late, dropped off the car at National, then got a ride on their shuttle to the airport. We ate at Smashburger, which was crazy expensive. Like $20 for a burger. We also tried a few local beers in the airport. Landed in FLL later, then drove back to Melbourne to get a few hours sleep before work the next day!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/sanjose5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Jose&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cr/beer.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Beer&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;other-things-to-know-about-costa-rica&quot;&gt;Other things to know about Costa Rica&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a credit card with no foreign transaction fees, we used my Capital One Venture Card for everything. The drive from Papagayo (west coast) to San Jose has toll roads you have to pay with cash. You can pay with USD and get change back in colones, the local currency. When driving, there are many 1 lane bridges. There is a sign on one side that shows which side has to yield, and the side without a yield sign gets to go without yielding. The roads are all very windy. Our rental took diesel, and all of the gas stations were not self serve. They had an attendant who would fill you up. People who work in the hospitality and tourism industry in Costa Rica are very nice and, in general, have very good English. We did not know much Spanish, but only had to bring out Google Translate once. Download Google Maps and Google Translate for offline usage fore you go if you have limited international data, like we did. We used 0MB of data the whole week, since each hotel had Wifi.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Keto Recipe Collection</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Keto-Recipe-Collection/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Keto Recipe Collection" /><published>2019-06-17T09:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-06-17T09:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Keto-Recipe-Collection</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Keto-Recipe-Collection/">&lt;p&gt;My wife and I have been doing a Keto diet for about 9 months. We have both lost over 30 pounds doing this diet. Since this involves cooking using lots of low carb recipes, I have bookmarked a large collection of recipes we like, here they are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;breakfast&quot;&gt;Breakfast&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ruled.me/jalapeno-popper-egg-cups/&quot;&gt;Jalapeño Popper Egg Cups&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;snacks&quot;&gt;Snacks&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.isavea2z.com/no-carb-cheese-wrap-folios-copycat-recipe/&quot;&gt;Cheese Wraps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wholesomeyum.com/recipes/8-ingredient-spinach-artichoke-dip-low-carb-gluten-free/&quot;&gt;Spinach Artichoke Dip&lt;/a&gt;- We dip &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2KVZHVX&quot;&gt;Whisps&lt;/a&gt; into this.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ruled.me/bbq-bacon-wrapped-smokies/&quot;&gt;Bacon Wrapped Lil Smokies&lt;/a&gt; - If you omit the BBQ sauce, it has less carbs and is still great.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wholesomeyum.com/recipes/keto-low-carb-sushi-rolls-recipe-healthy/&quot;&gt;Sushi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;chicken&quot;&gt;Chicken&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://laughingspatula.com/pesto-mozzarella-and-tomato-stuffed-chicken-breasts/#wprm-recipe-container-5260&quot;&gt;Pesto Mozzarella and Tomato Stuffed Chicken Breast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.delish.com/cooking/recipe-ideas/recipes/a51442/chicken-zucchini-alfredo-recipe/&quot;&gt;Chicken Zucchini Alfredo&lt;/a&gt; - If you have a mandolin, you can cut up zucchini to make pasta that’s amazing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/b7uso3/keto_chicken_parm/&quot;&gt;Chicken Parmesan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/aktsqw/the_best_keto_butter_chicken_over_cauliflower/&quot;&gt;Indian Style Butter Chicken over Cauliflower Rice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/bnxnwj/spicy_thai_peanut_chicken/&quot;&gt;Thai Peanut Chicken&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.savorylotus.com/pesto-chicken-avocado-salad/&quot;&gt;Pesto Chicken Avocado Salad&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/a4g6iw/creamy_tuscan_chicken_with_roasted_asparagus/&quot;&gt;Tuscan Chicken&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/9ag2pw/bacon_avocado_and_chicken_sandwich/?st=JLB65CHQ&amp;amp;sh=24d06f0a&quot;&gt;Bacon, Avocado, Chicken Sandwich&lt;/a&gt; - Using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/GifRecipes/comments/9scjzq/lowcarb_keto_bagels_fathead_dough/e8nph5x/&quot;&gt;fathead buns&lt;/a&gt; recipe in the link below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;beef&quot;&gt;Beef&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.delish.com/cooking/recipe-ideas/recipes/a52731/cheese-taco-shells-recipe/&quot;&gt;Cheese Taco Shells&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lowcarbmaven.com/low-carb-taco-seasoning-keto-gluten-free/&quot;&gt;Taco Seasoning&lt;/a&gt; - Brown some beef with this and put it into those cheese taco shells, you’ve got Taco night.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/9h93rf/guacamole_bacon_burger_on_cheesebuns/&quot;&gt;Guac Bacon Burger&lt;/a&gt; - Also using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/GifRecipes/comments/9scjzq/lowcarb_keto_bagels_fathead_dough/e8nph5x/&quot;&gt;fathead buns&lt;/a&gt; recipe below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;crab&quot;&gt;Crab&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.savorytooth.com/crab-stuffed-mushrooms/&quot;&gt;Crab Stuffed Mushroom&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://lowcarbyum.com/keto-crab-cakes/&quot;&gt;Crab Cakes&lt;/a&gt; - This is our most made meal. We use Alaskan faux crab (krab), and I just brown it in a pan, no making cakes. But the combination of ingredients here is great.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;fish&quot;&gt;Fish&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dietdoctor.com/recipes/keto-thai-fish-curry-coconut&quot;&gt;Coconut Curry Thai Fish&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.allrecipes.com/recipe/228056/parmesan-crusted-tilapia-fillets/&quot;&gt;Parmesan Crusted Tilapia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;shrimp&quot;&gt;Shrimp&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://keto-daily.com/keto-sheet-pan-shrimp-recipe/?fbclid=IwAR0zDUl6Q5PvkRquoFq99Xwzjjanm02ZhBHrzbuPznWzzozyDNafztqTc1M&quot;&gt;Sheet Pan Cajun Shrimp&lt;/a&gt; - I usually add some Andouille sausage to this.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/c1mr1y/crispy_shrimp_0g_carbs/&quot;&gt;Crispy Shrimp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;other&quot;&gt;Other&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/GifRecipes/comments/9scjzq/lowcarb_keto_bagels_fathead_dough/e8nph5x/&quot;&gt;Fathead Buns&lt;/a&gt; - I make these all the time, and they taste great for a week! I usually make these into balls to make buns, instead of bagels.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://culinarylion.com/recipes/zucchini-fried-ravioli/&quot;&gt;Zucchini Fried Ravioli&lt;/a&gt; - This is our absolute favorite recipe, period. But it’s really annoying and time consuming to make, so I don’t make it often.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/409b7q/homemade_innoutinspired_animal_style_salad/&quot;&gt;In N Out Style Salad&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wholesomeyum.com/recipes/baked-healthy-buffalo-cauliflower-bites-wings-recipe/&quot;&gt;Buffalo Cauliflower Bites&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/99p88p/lasagna_stuffed_portobello_mushroom_with_bacon/&quot;&gt;Lasagna Stuffed Mushrooms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;desserts&quot;&gt;Desserts&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/Keto-Chocolate-Milkshake/&quot;&gt;Chocolate Milkshake&lt;/a&gt; - My favorite keto dessert.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mooreorlesscooking.com/2015/06/17/lo-carb-pudding-dessert/&quot;&gt;Pudding&lt;/a&gt; - We make this weekly.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/9ur8un/keto_pecan_pie/&quot;&gt;Pecan Pie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rskelton.com/keto-cookie-dough-balls/&quot;&gt;Cookie Dough Balls&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://prettypies.com/recipe/low-carb-chocolate-pizza/&quot;&gt;Chocolate Pizza&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/bj4dtu/snickerdoodle_crepes/&quot;&gt;Snickerdoodle Crepes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ketorecipes/comments/bxgfgh/peanut_butter_and_chocolate_mug_cake_no_flour/&quot;&gt;Peanut Butter and Chocolate Mug Cake&lt;/a&gt; - We use low sugar peanut butter instead of PB2.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lowcarbspark.com/keto-lava-cake/&quot;&gt;Chocolate Lava Mug Cake&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hip2keto.com/recipes/3-minute-keto-cinnamon-roll-mug-cake/&quot;&gt;Cinnamon Roll Mug Cake&lt;/a&gt; - Noticing a trend with the mug cakes?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wholesomeyum.com/recipes/low-carb-keto-cream-cheese-frosting-recipe/&quot;&gt;Cream Cheese Frosting&lt;/a&gt; - Use this frosting recipe on the cinnamon roll above.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://peaceloveandlowcarb.com/keto-pumpkin-spice-chocolate-chip-cookies/&quot;&gt;Pumpkin Spice Chocolate Chip Cookies&lt;/a&gt; - October and November only.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">My wife and I have been doing a Keto diet for about 9 months. We have both lost over 30 pounds doing this diet. Since this involves cooking using lots of low carb recipes, I have bookmarked a large collection of recipes we like, here they are.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Plasti Dip GX470 Grill</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Plasti-Dip-GX470-Grill/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Plasti Dip GX470 Grill" /><published>2019-05-07T09:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-05-07T09:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Plasti-Dip-GX470-Grill</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Plasti-Dip-GX470-Grill/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/done.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Done&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I plastidipped the grill on my Lexus GX470, and I am very happy with the results. It took about 30 minutes of active work, and about 4 hours of waiting, and this was my first time using &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2H7U2dj&quot;&gt;Plasti Dip&lt;/a&gt;. I used 1 can of black &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2H7U2dj&quot;&gt;Plasti Dip&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the full Chrome grill, before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/before.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The labor is pretty simple - remove about 10 10mm bolts around the grill, up under the hood. I also had to remove 2 bolts on the hood release that were attached. Then just slip the grill off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/back.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also removed the Lexus logo, so that it stayed chrome instead of black. I think the contrast looks better. I’ve seen some other people &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2H7U2dj&quot;&gt;Plasti Dip&lt;/a&gt; the whole grill, and it doesn’t look as good to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/back2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Lexus logo removal involved 2 Phillips screws behind the logo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/remove_logo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make sure you clean your grill really well. You don’t want any bugs or dust on the grill before starting. I applied 8 coats of &lt;a href=&quot;https://amzn.to/2H7U2dj&quot;&gt;Plasti Dip&lt;/a&gt; on, with 15-30 minutes of drying in between in each coat. It was just like using spray paint. This is after 2 coats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/coat1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this is 6 coats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/coat2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And re-installed the grill! Huge improvement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/grill/done.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Done&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My Georgia Tech OMSCS Experience So Far</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/OMSCS-Experience-So-Far/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Georgia Tech OMSCS Experience So Far" /><published>2019-04-22T09:00:14-04:00</published><updated>2019-04-22T09:00:14-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/OMSCS-Experience-So-Far</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/OMSCS-Experience-So-Far/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/gt/gt.png&quot; alt=&quot;GT&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was accepted to, and enrolled in, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.omscs.gatech.edu/&quot;&gt;Georgia Tech’s OMSCS&lt;/a&gt; (Online Master of Science in Computer Science) in January 2016. This post is meant as a recap as the classes I’ve taken, and my experiences throughout this program. Every class is a 3 hour credit. You need 10 classes, or 30 hours, to earn this degree, which you have to complete within 6 years of admission. There is no thesis requirement, just pass all the classes and you’ve earned the degree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I transferred in 3 hours that I didn’t use from my undergrad at Auburn. I needed 5 engineering elective hours to graduate at Auburn, and I passed 12. I had too much free time then. One class, ELEC5150-Intro to Information Security at Auburn, transferred as credit for CS6035-Intro to Information Security at Georgia Tech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I only take 1 class at a time, since I also work full time and like to do things besides be in front of the computer. I’ve dropped a few classes, and got a D in 1 class, which doesn’t count towards your graduation credits, but, unfortunately, does count towards your GPA. Anyways, here’s the classes I’ve taken, grades I earned, if I recommend the course, and my thoughts on each.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;spring-2016---cs6300---software-development-process&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6300-software-development-process&quot;&gt;Spring 2016 - CS6300 - Software Development Process&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: B&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Would recommend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a great first class to take in OMSCS. It eases you into the concept of working at your own pace, working with groups of people that you never meet in person, and the basics of using Github in a small group. I got a B, but was really close to an A. I wish I had put a little more effort into this class. Dr. Orso is a interesting professor, and you learn a bit of Java and how to build a simple Android app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;summer-2016---cs6310---software-architecture-and-design&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6310-software-architecture-design&quot;&gt;Summer 2016 - CS6310 - Software Architecture and Design&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: B&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a software architecture course. I work in cloud architecture, more along the infrastructure lines, but I didn’t learn much in this class. The lectures are boring, the content is boring… it’s just a whole course on UML.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;fall-2016---cs6250---computer-networks&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6250-computer-networks&quot;&gt;Fall 2016 - CS6250 - Computer Networks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: Dropped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is considered to be one of the easiest classes in OMSCS, but it wasn’t for me. It’s all about writing networking algorithms in Python, and it just didn’t click for me. I dropped this one pretty early.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;spring-2017---cs6475---computational-photography&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cs6475.wordpress.com/&quot;&gt;Spring 2017 - CS6475 - Computational Photography&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: D&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Advice against&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This class with Dr. Irfan Issa has been my worst Georgia Tech class, and second worse classroom experience ever (no one will ever top Dr. Baginski’s Analog Electronics at Auburn). So this class I really struggled in, but I put in a ton of effort, and expected to make a mid C. A bad grade, but at least credit towards graduation. This class is heavy on Python and matrix algebra, both topics I am not strong in. So I go into the final project with a 75, and I just have to get about a 10 (out of 100) to keep my C. One annoying thing about Dr. Issa is that he gives you the assignment file as something like final_project.pdf, and wants the deliverable to have the exact same name (final_project.pdf). You can see how this can cause issues if you’re keeping your projects in the same directory, like a logical person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I uploaded my final project after completion and did an OK job, not A material, but definitely more than a 10 material. When grades came back a few weeks later, I saw that I had a D in the class. I asked the TAs and professor why, and it was because I uploaded the final_project.pdf that was the instructions, not my actual final report. When I selected the file to upload, I was in the wrong directory. I received a 0 on the final project, they would not accept my completed final_report.pdf, and therefore I failed this class. I brought this up to Georgia Tech as a Official Grade Dispute, and it was not re-graded. My D stood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, I would recommend not taking this class unless you have a very strong interest in Computational Photography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;summer-2017---cs6400---database-systems-concepts-and-designs&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6400-database-systems-concepts-and-design&quot;&gt;Summer 2017 - CS6400 - Database Systems, Concepts and Designs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: A&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Would recommend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is another really good class, and it was nice to take a interesting class after my awful previous semester. I had considered dropping the whole program after getting a D in my previous course. In this database course, I learned a bunch, and worked with a really great group on my projects in this course. Dr. Mark is funny and keeps lectures interesting. This class also helped me in my work, as I’ve been working more with databases now than ever before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;fall-2017---none&quot;&gt;Fall 2017 - None&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UgOu1zPtW2I&quot;&gt;Why do school when you can watch football?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;spring-2018---cs6460---educational-technology&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6460-educational-technology&quot;&gt;Spring 2018 - CS6460 - Educational Technology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: A&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This class is taught by Dr. David Joyner, who is highly liked in the OMSCS community. He is a interesting professor, but this wasn’t the most interesting topic for me. This class has a decent amount of busy work, like weekly status reports and required meetings, but it made for the easiest grade in OMSCS so far. I didn’t learn a whole lot in this course, but it is a decent course and good for padding your GPA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;summer-2018---cs7646---machine-learning-for-trading&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://quantsoftware.gatech.edu/Machine_Learning_for_Trading_Course&quot;&gt;Summer 2018 - CS7646 - Machine Learning for Trading&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dropped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I signed up for this thinking it was a really interesting sounding course. The content is interesting, but it gets tough, quick. The first project was easy, then it became super difficult. The course deals with stock trading, AI, and utilizes Python, numpy, pandas, and other Python libraries. I also had a lot of things going on in my personal life, so I couldn’t devote as much time as I needed to this course, so I dropped it. Dr. Balch’s lectures are interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;fall-2018---cs6440---intro-to-health-informatics&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6440-intro-health-informatics&quot;&gt;Fall 2018 - CS6440 - Intro to Health Informatics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grade: B&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This class was not fun or educational for me. The class is 100% run by a TA, there is no instructor involvement. The lectures are dry, and the content is not interesting for me. You spend most of the course learning about FHIR, a healthcare API, but every time we were had an assignment to do any development with it, the API was not functioning. Luckily, you don’t have to use FHIR for your final project, and I think 0% of my class ended up using it. We were allowed to pick any healthcare related project that was given to us, and it ended up being a simple team project. I came away with a B, but was close to an A. I would not take this class again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;spring-2019---cs7646---machine-learning-for-trading&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://quantsoftware.gatech.edu/Machine_Learning_for_Trading_Course&quot;&gt;Spring 2019 - CS7646 - Machine Learning for Trading&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dropped… again&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got a promotion at work and my work load started going up, I got engaged, ended up doing more home remodeling, more car stuff, and less school. Same as the first time I took this course, the second project was overly difficult. I won’t try to take this one a 3rd time, but the content does still interest me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;summer-2019---none&quot;&gt;Summer 2019 - None&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Honeymoon for a week in Costa Rica, no way I’m doing school then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;fall-2019---cs6238---secure-computing-systems&quot;&gt;Fall 2019 - CS6238 - Secure Computing Systems&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the first time this class has been taught, so it’ll either be super easy or the worst class ever. I’ll let you know in December.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So as of April 2019, I have 18 credits out of 30. I need to pass 4 more classes by Spring 2022 in order to graduate.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>